I don't know if it was destiny
yo no sé si fue el destino
I don't know how it happened
yo no sé cómo pasó
but I saw a picture of you
pero vi una foto tuya
and this song was born for you
y me nació esta canción para ti
It was only a matter of time a walk
solo fue cuestión de tiempo un paseo
by the river you left I left but
junto al río tú te fuiste yo me fui pero
I had to call you to tell you yes
te tuve que llamar para decirte que si
Do you want to travel the world?
quieres viajamos por el mundo tú si
you want Forget everything if you prefer
quieres Olvídate de todo si prefieres
Every day we start over
cada día Volvemos a empezar
ours if you want
lo nuestro si quieres
[Music]
[Música]
wear your color with little Lula likes it
lleven tu color con poca Lula gusta la
may your heart remain
que le quede tu corazón
tell me if you want
dime tú si quieres
[Music]
[Música]
Give me what I wanted for so long
de mí Dame lo que tanto tiempo quise
feel that tickle
sentir esa cosquil
that I give you because I know that you, no one
que yo te doy porque sé que tú tú nadie
like you You
como tú Tú
You go in your own body and as I say Camilo
vas de cuerpo tuyo y como digo Camilo
that I sing to you like this
que yo te canto así
So
así
it was only a matter of time
solo fue cuestión de tiempo
a walk along the river that you left and
un paseo junto al río que tú te fuiste y
I left but I had to call you to
yo me fui pero te tuve que llamar para
tell you that if you want
decirte que si quieres
We travel the world if you want
viajamos por el mundo tú si quieres
Forget everything and if you prefer every day
Olvídate de todo y si prefieres cada día
We'll start our thing again if you want.
Volvemos a empezar lo nuestro si quieres
in that
en eso
wear your color in low light, heart
lleven tu color con poca luz corazón
[Music]
[Música]
It was only a matter of time a walk
solo fue cuestión de tiempo un paseo
by the river you left I left but
junto al río tú te fuiste yo me fui pero
I had to call you to tell you that you are
te tuve que llamar para decirte que eres
We travel the world if you want
viajamos por el mundo tú si quieres
forget everything and always prefer
olvídate de todo y siempre prefieres
every day we start over
cada día volvemos a empezarlo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
I'll build you a mansion
te monto una mansión
[Music]
[Música]
Let your heart put the color that Dime
que tu corazón ponga el color que Dime
you if you want
tú si quieres
If you want
Si quieres tú
tell me if you want
dime tú si quieres
If you want, tell me if you want.
Si quieres Ay Dime tú si quieres
[Music]
[Música]
what I thought I was to love is no longer
lo que pensé que soy de amar ya no
It used to be that kisses were given in
existía que los besos se regalan en
any corner
cualquier esquina
I who thought I was to love was only a
Yo que pensé que soy de amar solo era un
I play but I look at you and I'm dying for
juego pero te miro y es que muero por
have you
tenerte
next to me
junto a mí
I will not invest my life nor
invertiré mi vida ni
excite you and me
ilusionarte y yo
I will win the game as long as it takes
ganaré la partida el tiempo que se
lost
perdió
and I ask every day that my day until the
y pido Cada día que mi día hasta el
last kiss that bids farewell to this life and I ask
último beso que despida esta vida y pido
every day I can always love you waiting
cada día siempre poder amarte esperando
the moment of having you in front of me
el momento de tenerte yo delante
[Music]
[Música]
If the world separates, I'll stay with you.
si el mundo se separa me quedo contigo
If tomorrow doesn't dawn I'll stay with you if
si mañana no amanece me quedo contigo si
You want me to stay, I'll stay with you.
tú quieres que me quede me quedo contigo
[Music]
[Música]
that I care about things and when
que me importan las cosas y cuando
I smile, turn around and I'm
sonrío me doy media vuelta y estoy
with you
contigo
I will invest my life Well family I will
invertiré mi vida Bueno familia voy a
cut the song here because we're going
cortar por aquí la canción porque vamos
to the mess that I don't have time to live today
al lío que hoy no me da tiempo a vivir
I don't have time to live, okay? I don't know if
no me da tiempo a vivir vale No sé si
start with the video you just uploaded
empezar por el vídeo que acaba de subir
dala putting a little context to everything
dala poniendo un poco de contexto a todo
the issue of Beijing and the situation I don't know
el tema de Beijing y la situación no sé
if you take it and see what happened with it
si y ver lo que ha pasado con
Pereira and with all these people
Pereira y con toda esta gente
Let's see
A ver
It's just crazy today
es que es una locura el día de hoy
It's crazy today
es una locura el día de hoy
let's see, there has been one
a ver ha habido una
Let's start with the thing about crashing and
vamos a empezar con lo de chocas y
Pereira like that because there is a series
Pereira así porque es que hay una serie
of things that I won't have time for today
de movidas que no me va a dar tiempo hoy
to treat them all and I'm going to have to
a tratarlas todas y voy a tener que
continue commenting on this tomorrow because
seguir comentando esto mañana porque
Of course I want to stop and I want to record video
claro quiero parar y Quiero grabar vídeo
from this to the main channel Many
de esto para el canal principal Muchas
Thanks anonymous I want to record video of
gracias anónimos Quiero grabar vídeo de
this for the main channel
esto para el canal principal
with all the news today and so on and so forth
con todas las noticias de hoy y demás y
I want to record the lollipop, so I don't know if
Quiero grabar la piruleta o sea no sé si
I'll spliced ​​all night or how will I do it
empalmaré toda la noche o cómo lo haré
but you crash
pero chocas
I'm filtering a little bit, I'm giving myself
ve filtrando un poquito me estoy dando
a little bit and I'll give the gossip little by little
un poquito y voy dando los chismes poco
little by little each day is worth it But well, let's go
a poco cada día vale Pero bueno vamos a
seeing all the fuss that has happened I'm leaving
ver toda la movida que ha pasado me voy
to find out here with you so that we can
a enterar aquí con ustedes para poder
Record in noti and then we talk
Grabar en noti y luego hablamos
oh well
pero bueno
He's here to defend himself
está por aquí para ir a defendiéndose
that I had
que tenía
So what do you want me to come?
O sea qué quieres que venga
is that he shouts at me in person
es que haga grítame a mí en persona
you crash what conversation do you want to have with me
chocas qué charla quieres tener conmigo
It's a [ __ ] conversation like a person
es una charla como una persona
I want to have you go from moralist so
quiero tener que te vas de moralista tan
that you are a good person, add chicken
que te vas de buena persona Échale pollo
talk to me stop yelling you are
habla conmigo Deja de gritar estás
bathed
bañado
They told me they have evidence
me han dicho que tienen pruebas
enough to tell me that I have done mg
suficientes para decirme que he hecho mg
that I am bathed for 24 hours is
que estoy bañado durante 24 horas es
say I'm not going to play anymore I'm not going to be
decir no voy a jugar más no voy a estar
24 hours without playing and I'm leaving the
24 horas sin jugar y que me vaya del
server and I can't do anything
servidor y que no puedo hacer ningún
type of appeal possible or above Well
tipo de apelación posible o encima Pues
Nothing, I'm leaving, dude, you guys are awesome.
nada me piro tío sois unos cracks
Thanks, I think it's pathetic, man. Please pass me.
gracias me parece lamentable tío pasadme
the tests But what is your mother mine
las pruebas Pero qué es tu madre mía
I'm freaking out, it's that in no [ __ ]
estoy flipando es que en ningún
I have never been a guy in any [ __ ] moment
momento he hecho tío en ningún
moment this is done, my goodness
momento hecho esto madre mía
I'm really pissed off, man.
tengo un cabreo tío
five five
cinco cinco
My goodness, how is the atmosphere?
madre mía cómo está el ambiente no
[ __ ] hours
horas
to tell me what I do
para que me digan que hago
which has 100 hours played
que tiene 100 horas jugadas
stop stop I'm going to see it
para para Voy a verlo
Bot let's see it Bot you know here is the
Bot vamos a verlo Bot sabes aquí está la
Czech then
checo entonces
I think the door
Yo creo que la puerta
This here is worth this here and has
esto de aquí vale esto de aquí y tiene
one down Okay and there is the Core
un para abajo Vale y ahí está el Core
This is it and they come
es esto y vienen
and the worst thing is that you know why I
y lo peor lo peor que sabes por qué me
they do mg because the [ __ ]
hacen mg porque el
accidentally put it in plan put it for when
puso sin querer en plan puso por cuando
I had said this put Look what it was
yo había dicho esto puso Mira qué fue lo
that happened to me Look at this put a mod by
que me pasaron Mira esto puso un mod por
They say that the fault of a nickname is chipped
culpa de un Mote pone chipe dicen que la
descent of garages there and the same
bajada de garajes por ahí y el propio
mod happened to me yesterday This photo happened to me yesterday
mod me pasó ayer Esta foto me pasó ayer
This photo telling me
esta foto diciéndome
in the conversation with the mustafi who
en la conversación con el mustafi que
was one who was helping me how
era uno que me estaba ayudando a cómo
raid without giving me any kind of
raidear sin darme ningún tipo de
information was not even using It's that
información no estaba ni usando Es que
really dude it really pisses me off that
de verdad tío de verdad me jode que
you flip out, it's regrettable any admin who
flipas es lamentable cualquier admin que
I'm sorry I don't love myself when I'm watching this.
esté viendo esto lo siento no me quiero
warm up but it's unfortunate because I swear
calentar pero es lamentable porque juro
for my mother who at no [ __ ] time
por mi madre que en ningún momento
I have taken advantage of doing meta Gaming
me he aprovechado de hacer meta Gaming
not one kind of cheat took 100 [ __ ]
ni un tipo de trampa llevo 100
hours almost when this [ __ ] server
horas casi cuando este servidor
so that you come and tell me what I have done
para que vengáis a decirme que he hecho
mg I find it regrettable and painful a mistake
mg me parece lamentable penoso una falta
of respect towards me towards my work and
de respeto hacia mí hacia mi trabajo y
I'm not going to play faster towards everyone, man.
hacia todo tío no voy a jugar más veloz
Thanks for the invitation, Recoy Carola.
gracias por la invitación recoy Carola
Thanks but I'm not playing anymore because I
Gracias pero no juego más porque me
It seems pitiful, pitiful uncle that I
parece lamentable tío lamentable que me
you have disrespected us in this way
hayas faltó el respeto de esta manera
that I look like a little kid having to
que parezco un niño pequeño teniendo que
cry over a game, my goodness
llorar por un juego tío madre mía
heart
corazón
It seems regrettable to me, uncle.
es que me parece lamentable tío me
It seems extremely regrettable that I
parece sumamente lamentable que me
It seems disrespectful to me
parece una falta de respeto hacia mí
towards my uncle like what is happening to me
hacia mí tío en plan lo que me está
[ __ ] that's what's [ __ ] me
jodiendo es eso lo que me está jodiendo
That
Eso
I think it's a [ __ ] lack of respect, man.
me parece una falta de respeto tío
and I'm going to see the whole [ __ ] voice and I'm going to
y voy a ver toda la voz y le voy a
shut the [ __ ] mouths of those [ __ ] [ __ ]
callar la boca a los de
[ __ ] man With all due respect man Yes
tío Con todo el respeto tío Sí
all due respect, eh, because they haven't
todo el respeto eh Porque no se han
I've seen the 8 hours, no, no, no, Charlie.
visto las 8 horas no no se toca Charlie
our chair is not touched impossible that
nuestra silla no se toca imposible que
have watched eight hours of Stream me the
hayan visto ocho horas de Stream me la
gifted the lordship eh No you eh or
regalado la señoría eh No ustedes eh o
be our chair is not touched But why
sea nuestra silla no se toca Pero porque
Your honor gives it to me, you don't give it to me
me la regala la señoría ustedes no me
you have given away a piece of [ __ ], don't you
habéis regalado una no os
you do not even members are going to take right now
hacéis ni miembros van a ya mismo
The Lordship is member 24, 130 are missing
la señoría es miembro 24 faltan 130
members to reach 2000 we could
miembros para llegar a 2000 podríamos
arrive tonight this intense night of
llegar esta noche esta noche intensa de
gossip
salseo
from a moderator with a simple guide
de un moderador con un simple guiazo
because a moderator puts a message in my chat
porque un moderador pone en mi chat un
moderator who has no idea of ​​the
moderador que no tiene ni idea ni del
roast that got in because you had uncle
roast que se metió porque habías tío
does not want to insult Sorry for the
no quiere insultar Perdón por los
insults but it's incredible 8 hours
insultos pero es increíble 8 horas os
I'm going to put you here
voy a poner os voy a poner aquí
because I told him off. I later
porque yo le eché la bronca Yo después
I gave him a [ __ ] scolding about this later
de esto le eché la bronca después
What is happening in this mess?
de este guiazo qué es lo que pasan
After this great guide, what is it?
después de este guiazo qué es lo que
they pass okay
pasan vale
After this [ __ ] day, what is it?
después de este díazzo qué es lo
What happens to say that mg says it is
que pasa para decir que dice mg que es
my moderator saying says that it is the
mi moderador diciendo dice que es la
On the way down I gave him a hard time and I put him
bajada yo le pegué un broncón y le puse
chip for the last time you do it again
chip por última vez que vuelves a hacer
This is via chat while he's giving nicknames
esto por el chat mientras está de motes
last time and my moderator So that
última vez y mi moderador O sea que
on top of that I had the chat in emote mode dude
encima tenía el chat en modo emote tío
complying with my moderator's rule
cumpliendo la norma de mi moderador me
sent this via WhatsApp
mandó esto por WhatsApp
He sent me this on WhatsApp and what I
me mandó esto por WhatsApp y lo que me
you [ __ ] with the kids on top of you
jodes con encima la chavalería te
will give away the mixer that How much is the
regalará el mezclador que Cuánto vale el
Tessa mixer, that's worth very little, eh?
mezclador tessa eso vale poco eh o sea
how much is the mixer the mixer is
cuánto vale el mezclador el mezclador es
the String deck not like that for there here I
el String deck no así para ahí aquí yo
I had the keyboard here and changing the
tenía aquí el teclado y cambiando las
scenes not good Never calls me the
escenas no bueno Nunca me llama la
attention, I haven't needed that.
atención tener eso no me ha hecho falta
oh well
pero bueno
They don't let me appeal to me, not to me, not to me
a mí no me dejan apelar a mí no a mí no
why I don't have biggers I'm not a
por qué yo no tengo biggers yo no soy un
big fish then I can't I'm me
pez gordo entonces yo no puedo yo es me
how I eat that you leave me bad in front of you
como me como que me dejéis mal delante
everyone likes me not being able to do
todo el mundo me como el no poder hacer
Streaming my work and I can't appeal
streaming mi trabajo y no puedo apelar
That's why it always seems the same to me, man.
Por eso siempre lo mismo tío me parece
very bad guy I would like if some
muy mal tío me gustaría si algún
administrator listen to me I would like you
administrador me escucha me gustaría que
You'll leave me talking with a shock perhaps
me dejaras en hablar con un shock acaso
with rich and a call because he throws it
con rico y un llamado porque le eche
thief that I chipped, you know that
ladrón que le puse chipete que sepas que
because of you, because of that message I am
por tu culpa por ese mensaje estoy
convinced that they are going to ban me and it is
convencido que me van a banear y se lo
I said and I told him and he told me Pepe Diles
dije y se lo dije y me dijo Pepe Diles
Don't let them [ __ ] you up because this is what it was
que no te jodan porque esto fue lo que
He sent me to Gustavy for eh whisper Tell him
me mandó a gustaffy por eh susurro Dile
that the garage is the 100% descent if you
que la de garaje es la bajada 100% si tú
you know the Ruth you know that two for one is
sabes el Rut sabes que el dos por uno se
put it up like that So tell him
pone hacia arriba de esa forma Así dile
who is right after me
que tiene razón después de que yo
After I commented on this I came
después de que yo comentase esto yo vine
here I came here
aquí yo vine aquí
and there were two doors Oh the one that leads to the hq or
y había dos puertas Oh la que da la hq o
the one that has been left on the other side
la que ha quedado a otro lado
Okay, yes, moderator, what's my fault?
vale sí moderador qué culpa tengo yo
dude, what's my fault dude, when I'm already
macho qué culpa tengo yo macho cuando ya
I already knew it, I was going to do that, man.
yo ya lo sabía yo ya iba a hacer eso tío
I was going to do that, man, I think
yo ya iba a hacer eso tío me parece
pathetic uncle Because I've been carrying I don't know how much
lamentable tío Porque llevo No sé cuánto
I've been live for 70 hours.
llevo de directo llevo 70 horas 70 horas
Streaming for the people who are my pop and
streando para la peña que es mi pop y le
Tell me, man, what do I really think I'm going to do?
cuente tío de verdad pienso hacer
cheating no longer for taking 70 hours
trampas ya no por llevar 70 horas
You think I'm a [ __ ] random
pensáis que soy yo un Random de
[ __ ] a [ __ ] random no dude no [ __ ]
un Random no colega no
work this is my [ __ ] job and I know it
trabajo esto es mi trabajo y sé lo
that there is what I know to do and I know what
que hay sé lo que hay que hacer y sé lo
that a professional and that you play with that
que un profesional y que juguéis con eso
It pisses me off that you're freaking out, really freaking out.
me jode que flipas pero que flipas
because I am convinced that if it were eh
porque estoy convencido que si fuese eh
I'm wandering around if I were River if I were
yo andojeo si fuese River si fuese
Mariana or if it were one of the fish
Mariana o si fuese alguno de los peces
Fat man, you drop your [ __ ] jaw, you shut up
gordo os cayáis la boca os calláis
the [ __ ] mouth I'm convinced man but
la boca estoy convencido tío pero
Since I am not, since I am not going to have one
como no lo soy como no voy a tener un
[ __ ] viral tweet how could I not have one
tweet viral como no voy a tener un
trending topic nothing will be said nor
trending topic no se va a decir nada ni
It's going to be talked about because he always does.
se va a hablar porque él siempre lo
same because you just screwed the [ __ ]
mismo porque acabáis de la
weeks missing me and my people
semanas a mí a mí y a mi gente faltando
more respect And thank you I don't have to say
más respeto Y gracias No tengo que decir
further
más
I don't do it for anything else nor do I do it for
no lo hago por otra cosa ni lo hago por
nothing like I do it because it is
nada en plan lo hago porque porque es
so because it pisses me off man Because I have
así porque me jode tío Porque lo he
repeated 45,000 is not enough
repetido 45.000 es que no es suficiente
test for
prueba para
a meta Gaming Javi We also have
un meta Gaming Javi Tenemos también
Stream deck barbajota you have everything
Stream deck barbajota tienes de todo
but what is that flea market that is
pero que es aquellos mercadillo que es
what beard jota a kiss King
lo que barba jota un beso Rey
There was no greater illusion a thousand times no
no había ilusión más grande mil veces no
We are invited to many series when we
nos invitan a muchas series cuando nos
We invite you. We try our best.
invitan lo Tratamos de lo mejor posible
playing a cool role by playing a
haciendo un papel que mole haciendo un
paper that for people dies without
papel que para la gente le muere sin
to get into an inequality of respect
meternos con una desigualdad al respeto
[ __ ] yeah [ __ ] yeah but that's the
jodiendo sí jodiendo Sí pero eso es la
that there is but it would never ever happen to me
que hay pero nunca nunca se me pasaría
Never ever cheat on your head
por la cabeza hacer trampas nunca nunca
in my life and that you put me to bed like this
en mi vida y que me acuestes de esta
manner
manera
I promise you that they only give me
os lo prometo que es que solo me dan
want to cry another moderator who is
ganas de llorar otro moderador que está
In the chat it happened to me how I throw it
en el chat me pasó cómo le echo la
anger at the chipete himself What's happening No
bronca al propio chipete Qué pasa No
do mg it's not mg don't say what you
hagas mg no es mg no digas lo que te
People say that I know and you put it
dice la gente que yo sabe y le pones
chipete
chipete
And to all this I remind you that this
Y a todo esto viene os recuerdo que este
great guide this great guide is after I
guíazo este guíazo es después de que yo
I would have confirmed it myself without
hubiese confirmado por mí mismo sin
no kind of information I am
ningún tipo de información estoy
ruined that the base and the thing of
arruinada que la base y que la cosa de
reality It's wrong and I was going to raid it
realidad Está mal y que lo iba a raidar
that way but oh well
de esa manera pero bueno
Let's see the Choco
A ver vamos a ver al choca
let's see the chocas
vamos a ver al chocas
a problem in any case I
un problema en cualquier caso Yo
I understand that you are upset and that
entiendo que le esté disgustado y que
insults the admis and insults everything
insulte a los admis y que insulta todo
the world, let's say
el mundo digamos
a live show is worth it, it's a very live show
un directo vale es un directo muy
short in which he explained
cortito en el que explicó
in the end we finished
al final acabamos
from the series And That's Fine
de la serie Y eso está bien
but I hope so
pero espero eh
Really
De verdad
I want to make a couple of comments
quiero hacer un par de comentarios
about what you said help
acerca de esto que ha dicho usted ayuda
it's incredible
es increíble
It's amazing what all the [ __ ] don't
es increíble lo que todos la pollas no
You have live shows on Twitch, I'm freaking out
tienes vivos en Twitch estoy flipando
Well, guys, it's the one that finally yes
Pues nada chavales es la que al final sí
that it will be true that the beagle is
que va a ser cierto que los beagle es
important man
importante hombre
24 hours is done, I'll send you three great guides
24 horas ya está te mando tres guiazos
don't appeal and suck it to your little house
no apelas y a chuparla para tu casita a
keep going Hala and what pisses me off man is this
seguir Hala y lo que me jode tío es esto
what was left as it was wrong is that I am
que quedó como quedo mal es que estoy
looking bad that maybe they say no more
quedando mal que a lo mejor dicen ya no
I can put one in another [ __ ] series
puedo meter a una en otra serie
because he's going to do this to us. This is what I
porque nos va a hacer Esto es lo que me
[ __ ] you guys you know that's what's bothering me
jode tíos sabéis es lo que me está
The street looks [ __ ] up, I think. Look.
se ve la calle yo creo mira
you stock a [ __ ] clip right away
estocas un clip justamente
Don't [ __ ] with me, man. You're the first one who
no me jodas tío Eres el primero que
You know how to speak You are the first one who is
sabes hablar Eres el primero que es
do these things
hacer estas cosas
This guy, this [ __ ] clown, is a guy who
este tío este payaso es un tío que
is all day on the Canal de
está todo el día en el Canal de
of the bases only the only thing that does
de las bases solamente lo único que hace
It is to say no no or yes yes yes up to here
es decirle no no o sí sí sí hasta aquí
It's wrong because a moderator would already have
está mal porque ya un moderador Tendría
that this clown should have been banned but it is
que haber baneado este payaso pero es
that doesn't happen what happens is that you don't
que no pasa eso lo que pasa es que no te
you find out nothing of yours that is called chipete
enteras nada suyo que se llama chipete
Mustafi tells him that the garage is
le dice dice mustafi que la de garaje es
the 100% drop And I say yes yes again
la bajada 100% Y le vuelvo a decir sí sí
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes Now I hit
sí sí sí sí sí sí sí sí Ahora pegué
Alexa and the chat returns Read everything that
Alexa y vuelve el chat Lee todo lo que
It's happening but let's see if it would be a goal
está pasando pero a ver sería meta
Gaming that people are or are for you
Gaming que la gente te esté o sea para
that it is meta Gaming has to be that
que sea meta Gaming tiene que ser que
knows what you will find in the
sabe lo que va a encontrar en las
indications they are giving would not be
indicaciones que están dando no sería
meta Gaming also that they are you
meta Gaming también que te estén
advising and giving opinions on what you do
aconsejando opinando de lo que haces
and looks straight ahead again and to the other side
y vuelve a mirar a recto y hasta el otro
The moderator himself tells him what the [ __ ]
propio moderador le dice chipe qué
you do because chipe is saying says
haces porque chipe está diciendo dice
who is right and says Mustafa that the
que tiene razón y dice mustafa que la
from the garage is the descent. So what?
del garaje es la bajada O sea qué
You want Pereira to do what you want
quieres que haga Pereira qué quieres que
make me scream after so many series
haga grítame después de tantas series a
over the years and the messes that have
lo largo de los años y los líos que ha
It seems that in this series there is
habido Parece ser que en esta serie se
They have put the admins in guillotine mode
han puesto los admins en modo guillotina
No, no, they have put themselves here
no no aquí se han puesto
sensitive administrators eh
sensibles los administradores eh
they ban, they ban quickly
banean banean rapidito
That is to say, this would be meta gaming, that is to say,
o sea esto sería meta Gaming o sea el
fact that the chat is telling you
hecho de que el chat te esté diciendo
come open and open there or if they are there
venga abra y abra ahí o sea si están
watching you play is not that they are
viéndote jugar no es que te estén
indicating why they have been saying it
indicando porque lo vengan diciendo de
other side because they have seen something in
otro lado porque hayan visto algo en
another String
otro String
Yes it would be meta gaming or what it is
Sí sería meta Gaming o sea lo que está
doing Yes it would be meta Gaming I mean already
haciendo Sí sería meta Gaming O sea ya
the fact that the kids or me
el hecho de que los chavales o sea yo
I'm playing Tetris here and you're playing me.
estoy jugando aquí al Tetris y usted me
You say Javi the square on the left
decís Javi el cuadrado a la izquierda el
square to the left would already be a goal
cuadrado a la izquierda ya sería meta
Gaming
Gaming
okay okay
vale vale
you want to have a [ __ ] chat with me
quieres tener conmigo es una charla
As a person I want to have
como una persona quiero tener
so many of a person made of chicken
tantas de una persona hecho de pollo
talk to me stop yelling you are
habla conmigo Deja de gritar estás
banned brother
baneado hermano
You are Well, there is no more Or so, if that's it
eres Pues es que no hay más O sea si eso
meta Gaming and the tests are the ones that
meta Gaming y las pruebas son las que
They are one putting it with emojis but yes yes
son uno poniéndole con emojis sino sí sí
no no yes yes no no and then just in case you don't
no no sí sí no no y luego por si no le
It has become clear that the moderator translates it
ha quedado claro el moderador lo traduce
who are you speak I'm tired then you
quién eres habla Estoy cansado luego te
You go on your Stream that you are the [ __ ] boss
vas en tu Stream de que eres el amo
that you are the best speak like a
de que eres el mejor habla como una
person who is 12 years old crashes
persona que tienes 12 años chocas
Screaming and making fun of you, uncle, is pathetic.
gritando y burlándote tío es penoso tío
then you ask for respect, [ __ ], then you ask
luego pides respeto cabrón luego pide
respect uncle please the only thing that I
respeto tío por favor lo único que me
you are proving and a hypocrite uncle is
estás demostrando y una hipócrita tío es
The only thing, dude, is the only thing you're doing to me
lo único tío es lo único que me estás
proving, man, that you're a bastard
demostrando tío que eres un
moralist
moralista
Uncle you would be like me because if you see me
tío estarías como yo porque si me ves
That's because you know that I really
así es porque sabes que de verdad me
[ __ ] if not I would be there on the street
jode si no yo estaría allí en la calle
now it would be What is sunny that I am carrying
ahora estaría Qué hace sol que llevo
five days locked up here
cinco días Aquí encerrados
to your series you and I respect you and you
a tu serie tú y yo te respeto a ti y tú
not to me because you have to be by
a mí no porque tienes que estar por
above and you are not above you are the same
encima y no estás por encima eres igual
that I that I and you are nobody for
que yo que yo y no eres nadie para
shout it out nobody nobody balls
gritarlo nadie nadie
Thank goodness I still think I'm going to
Menos mal que aún creo que me voy a
to be able to defend because I have everything
poder defender Porque todo lo he
I found out before but because of that message
averiguado yo antes pero por ese mensaje
you screwed them up but since you don't have a [ __ ]
las cagado pero como no tienes ni
idea you collide and judge by a clip you judge
idea chocas y juzgas por un clip juzgas
for a clip because you haven't seen the
por un clip porque no te has visto a las
You haven't seen 8 hours of raiding.
8 horas de raideo no te las has visto
you have taken out a clip and you judge on top
has sacado un clip y juzgas encima
You have the decency to yell at me and
tienes la decencia de gritarme y de
Make fun of me, tell me to talk to me even more
burarte de mí decirte hablar conmigo aún
above please bye because it has to do with
encima por favor chao pues tiene que ver
moralism has a lot to do with it here
mucho el moralismo aquí tiene que ver
a lot of moralism Because if you crash my
mucho el moralismo Porque si chocas mi
situation would be like me and I would ask that
situación estaría como yo y pediría que
let him talk to admin because yesterday
le dejase hablar con admin porque ayer
They said it now I put a tweet in
lo dijeron ahora pongo un tweet en
Twitter goes viral and what are they going to say?
Twitter se hace viral y que van a decir
Pereira Pereira but we don't have to talk
Pereira Pereira pero no tenemos hablar
yesterday Carola said it yesterday Carola told him
ayer lo dijo Carola ayer Carola le dijo
I ask to speak to trucks and I can't.
a camiones pido hablar y no puedo pido
talk and he sends me [ __ ] and yells at me
hablar y me manda la y me grita
Ah, it's not moralism, it's not moralism.
Ah no es moralismo no es no es moralismo
Hypocrisy is not my balls, it's my
hipocresía no es mis huevos son mis
Pickled eggs go guys please
huevos en vinagre va tíos por favor la
holy [ __ ]
ostia
24 hours 24 hours doing live yesterday
24 horas 24 horas haciendo directo ayer
eh eight hours of roundup and they judge me for
eh ocho horas de redeo y me juzgan por
a clip is pitiful man I hate people
un clip es penoso tío odio las personas
I hate cheaters and liars.
tramposas y mentirosas las odio al
top level people who are on my Stream
máximo nivel la gente que está mi Stream
He knows me and he knows how I'm going to leave.
me conoce y lo sabe cómo me voy a ir yo
I'm going back to a place where I don't
voy a volver a un sitio en donde no me
They want this a place where the crashes
quieren este un sitio en el que choca el
who is the creator yells at me and mocks me
que es el creador me grita se burla de
He tells me not to talk to me, that I
mí me dice que no hablar conmigo que me
I have to [ __ ] him so he can [ __ ] her, bro.
tengo que que se la pelo hermano
I have a little bit of dignity, I have
tengo un poquito de dignidad yo yo tengo
a little dignity Eh I don't think that I
un poquito dignidad Eh no pienso que yo
I'm a [ __ ] like 90% of people
soy un chupa pollas como el 90% de
people that I can see I am not a
personas que pueda ver yo no soy un
[ __ ] [ __ ] sucker, little ass from behind no
putísimo chupa colita por atrás no
If you're mistaken, I'm 10 and I've already done it.
se equivoquéis yo tengo 10 y ya lo
You know that for my cousin, [ __ ] respect
sabéis que para mi prima el respeto
and the values ​​and for me this is key now
y los valores y para mí esto es clave ya
that they don't let me talk because guys it's the
que no me dejan hablar pues tíos es la
What's up, eh, of course, the rich one, and you crash yourself
que hay eh claro la ricoy mismo chocas
but he was wrong or so
pero es que se ha equivocado o sea
I understand that you take it badly and that
entiendo que se lo tome mal y que
explode okay but it has been
explote vale pero es que se ha
sincerely wrong If that is so the
equivocado sinceramente Si eso es así el
meta Gaming works like this
meta Gaming funciona así
Well, you've made a mistake, there's nothing else.
pues se ha equivocado no hay más
I understand that it makes you angry and almost [ __ ]
entiendo que te dé coraje y casi
a mistake that is born with bad intentions or
un error que nace con mala intención ni
with the intention of getting them to tell you tricks
con intención de que te chivaran trucos
or anything like that But
ni nada por el estilo Pero
[ __ ] you've messed up. That's it, nothing's wrong.
la has cagado Ya está no pasa nada
neither
tampoco
24 hours and then it comes back. So
24 horas y luego vuelve O sea que
They weren't definitive bans either. No, neither.
tampoco eran baneo definitivo No tampoco
were they a definitive ban?
eran baneo definitivo no
Explain to me what this situation is, Pereira.
explícame qué es esta situación Pereira
As you will understand As you will understand with
Como comprenderás Como comprenderás con
the situation that just happened with your
la situación que acaba de pasar con tus
moderators what the hell is that
moderadores qué es eso
They have me at a price they have been for five years
me tienen a precio llevan cinco años
watching and they have gotten hot if you think that
viendo y se han calentado si crees que
I have to pay the bills too
yo también tengo que pagar los platos
broken because of some Mods
rotos por culpa de unos Mods se
warm up kids 18 years later
calientan chavalitos 18 años después de
I will be repeating directly please
yo estar repitiendo directo porfa
You insult. Well, that's what you want me to ask you.
insultáis Pues eso quieres que te pida
sorry for them I ask your forgiveness and I
perdón por ellos te pido perdón y me
I'm sorry, do you want me to remove them?
disculpo quieres que los quite de
moderation I apologize and remove them from
moderación te pido perdón y los quito de
moderation but you too you too
moderación pero tú también tú también
I think you have to apologize, okay?
Creo que te tienes que disculpar vale
real real volarista after
volarista De verdad de verdad después de
two hours insulting the administration
dos horas insultando a la administración
telling us that we have done wrong
diciéndonos que hemos hecho fatal
our work
nuestro trabajo
just once in the ban and
una vez nada más en el baneo y al
moment he asked for forgiveness because I said sorry
momento pidió perdón porque dije perdón
I got heated, I shouldn't insult a
me he calentado no debería insultar un
insult is a figure that does not appear in
insulto es una figura eso no figura en
the ticket does not show that
el ticket eso no figura
dude, I'm going to read your own ticket to you.
colega te lo voy a leer tu propio ticket
We have made you open a ticket and in your
te hemos hecho abrir un ticket y en tu
ticket the first thing you said is that
ticket lo primero que has dicho es que
I think it looks normal to you from behind
me parece que te parece normal de atrás
and Normal Administration of a supposed
y Administración normal de un supuesto
In case of cheating, tell me that Pereira
caso de trampas que me digan que Pereira
You can't, there's nothing to defend
no te puede no hay nada que defender
but there is nothing to defend there is nothing
pero no hay nada que defender no hay
nothing
nada
and 24 hours of Stream is not that the kid
y 24 horas de Stream no es que el chaval
the same kid has been talking
el mismo chaval lleva hablando
effectively five [ __ ] hours
efectivamente cinco horas
Since they are youngsters, they have not moderated one
como son chavalines no han moderado una
[ __ ] all over and you crash into some
en toda y estás chocas con unas
screenshot and with a clip
screenshot y con un clip
I only took one, I only took one
eches solo saqué una solo saqué una sola
and one because I opened the rest of them in
y una porque el resto las abrimos yo en
game because I repeat again you are
game porque vuelvo a repetir tú eres
streamer like me You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
streamer como yo Eres un
professional like me and you know very well
profesional como yo y tú sabes de sobra
that if I gave the word for you I will not go
que si yo di la palabra por ti yo no voy
to cheat on your [ __ ] series and that
a hacer trampas en tu serie y que
judge me and call me a cheater
me juzgues y que me taches de tramposo
in front of 30,000 people it seems to me
delante 30.000 personas me parece
regrettable
lamentables
You have a moderator you have a moderator
Tienes un moderador tienes un moderador
you have but why is he calling you
tienes pero porque le está llamando
hypocrites who do not understand the
hipócritas que no entiendo lo del
hypocritical term because it is being used
término hipócrita porque se lo está
saying
diciendo
that you have that I don't understand Where is the
que tiene que no entiendo Dónde está la
hypocrisy here or because the term
hipocresía aquí o sea porque el término
hypocrite Where is the hypocrisy In
hipócrita Dónde está la hipocresía En
What other time has Chocas allowed?
qué otro momento el chocas ha permitido
has forgiven This is worth it
ha perdonado Esto vale
It could be because of Gorko, or rather,
puede ser por lo de gorko no O sea pues
however
sin embargo
However, of course, you crash.
sin embargo Claro sin embargo el chocas
Yesterday with the Gorko thing I was saying that
ayer con lo de gorko estaba diciendo que
It wasn't meta Gaming maybe that's why not
no era meta Gaming puede ser por eso no
You can't tell me I'm a hypocrite
no puedes decirme que soy hipócrita
because it's the truth you can't tell me
porque es la verdad no puedes decirme
that
eso
you would understand me and what you are saying to me
me entenderías y lo que me estás
doing It's that I can't understand you
haciendo Es que no te puedo entender
because my moderators moderate the channel
porque mis moderadores moderan el canal
[ __ ] I can't understand you I have
No te puedo entender yo tengo
people who do their job well
gente que hace bien su trabajo
You pay them money, I don't. I have a lot.
les pagas dinero yo no Yo tengo mucha
less people than you and I'm 25
menos gente que tú y tengo 25
moderators who stop by when they can
moderadores que se pasan cuando pueden
help me point I have 25 or 30 are
ayudarme punto tengo 25 o 30 son
Boys, yes, I have to pay for it.
chavalitos sí la tengo que pagar por
They then paid for it because
ellos pues la pago por ellos porque
Up to that point, I am not Pereira.
hasta ese es el punto Pereira no soy
hypocrite Then you are paying for
hipócrita Entonces estás pagando por
them but it seems to me to be
ellos pero es que me parece ser
hypocritical
hipócrita
because I'm not defending the [ __ ]
porque yo no estoy defendiendo el
On the contrary, I am not the [ __ ] opposite
contrario yo no soy el contrario
but but you have to understand that what
pero pero tienes que entender que lo que
I'm saying it's true and not hypocrisy
estoy diciendo es verdad y no hipocresía
Your moderators have shat themselves
tus moderadores se han cagado encima son
[ __ ] children it seems to me
niños me parece
or not only during During
o no solo durante Durante
This debate a guy what did he tell you
este debate un tío Qué te ha dicho lo
that you have to do and has justified
que tienes que hacer y ha justificado
the comments of a Rank that you
los comentarios de un Rango que te
I was saying that if you were doing
estaba diciendo que si estabas haciendo
the right thing not for 5 hours a guy 5
lo correcto no durante 5 horas un tío 5
hours searching for what I had to farm
horas buscando lo que tenía que farmear
and only when I After all if not
y solo cuando yo Después de todo si no
He can tell you anything, he doesn't have to.
te puede decir nada no te tiene que
say nothing
decir nada
an hour an hour knocking on the door with
una hora una hora picando la puerta con
a stone, bastard. Do you really think that?
una piedra cabrón De verdad te crees que
I'm cheating, I'm going to set an hour
soy hago trampas me voy a poner una hora
with a [ __ ] stone a [ __ ] stone
con una piedra una piedra
you do
hagas
at the moment you read in the
en el momento en el que tú lees en el
chat something that is information about
chat algo que es información acerca de
I come up with it and you don't say anything and you don't throw it away
la ideo y tú no dices nada y no echas a
that person you remove moderation or
esa persona le quitas la moderación o
you do whatever at that moment you don't do it
haces lo que sea en ese momento no lo
you said a lot later Well then
dijiste muchísimo después Bueno pues
There is a lot of effort involved in that
muchísimo esfuerzo es lo que hay a ese
dude that guy can't be a moderator of
tío a ese tío no puede ser moderador de
your channel and you can't have a guy like
tu canal y no puedes tener un tío como
Mustafa telling you if not to the
mustafa diciéndote si no a las
decisions you make period This is not
decisiones que tomas punto Esto no es
This is neither hypocrisy nor nonsense
hipocresía ni tontería esto
It's also 24 hours of
es que además encima son 24 horas de
ban dude you're going to come back and that's it but the
baneo tío vas a volver y ya está pero la
you have done wrong
has hecho mal
I want you to have a person telling you
quiero que tenías una persona diciéndote
what you had to do and you pay attention to it
lo que tenías que hacer y le hagas caso
I have paid attention, it is not against the
he hecho caso no está en contra de las
rules of the series and you deserve it
normas de la serie y te mereces la
The penalty is that you cannot find the rules
sanción es que no encuentras las normas
Having information about other people
Tener información de otras personas
on the server is not a standard in
sobre el servidor no es una norma en
against allowing people to do it to you
contra de permitir que la gente te lo
I've been saying it on a raid too
esté diciendo en un raideo también lo he
explained yesterday I'll let you talk
explicado ayer te dejo hablar
To me the boy at all times
a mí El chaval durante todo momento
Because you have no idea, I can pass you
porque no tiene ni idea te puedo pasar
the chipete screens which is the
las screens de chipete que es el
moderator who puts that talking to him
moderador que pone eso hablando con el
Mustafa, the balls he got into
mustafa de los que se metió
because he was a pro of rouste and he told me
porque era un pro de rouste y me dijo
Pereira I don't know you at all but I
Pereira no te conozco de nada pero me
Your popi is talking, I'm going to help you
está hablando tu popi te voy a ayudar
because you are missing little things, he got in
porque te faltan cositas se metió
during that [ __ ] night to give me
durante esa noche a darme
game information about the [ __ ] game
información del juego del juego
you crash dude and you're judging some
chocas tío y tú estás juzgando unas
captures instead of 24 hours man I'm going to
capturas en vez de 24 horas tío me voy a
see a 24-hour dress
ver un vestido de 24 horas
We do not moderate the channel, come on, you have yours.
no moderamos el canal venga tienes tu
reason we do not model anything we leave the book
razón no modelamos nada dejamos el libro
free will and we eat ourselves stridently 24
albedrío y nos comemos estridente 24
Pereira hours Of course you're right
horas Pereira Claro que sí tienes razón
We don't moderate anything, not that there isn't mg
no moderamos nada no que no haya mg
Pereira, [ __ ] yeah, we'll see each other 24 hours a day, man.
Pereira sí nos vemos 24 horas tío
[ __ ] and on top of that he doesn't have it and on top of that he doesn't
y encima no tiene y encima no
you got the [ __ ] buddy [ __ ] again
tienes los colega otra vez
with the [ __ ] and I've told you 40 times
con los y os lo he dicho 40 veces
your group was The [ __ ] uncle Because
hacía tu grupo Los tío Porque
Well, man, we have to look at it in
Bueno pues tío pues hay que mirarlo en
Google Pereira is what it is, uncle me.
Google Pereira es lo que hay tío yo
I need you not to throw me tools
necesito que no te eche herramientas
to be able to work, colleague. And it is not
para poder trabajar colega Y es que no
you put nothing of your [ __ ] part
ponéis nada de vuestra parte los
What other problems do you have but yes
que más problemas tenéis pero si
He is absolutely right, he clashes with everything
tiene toda la razón el choca en todo lo
what are you saying
que estás diciendo
the moment but it doesn't matter but I don't
el momento pero da igual pero yo no te
I have to ask Pereira, I don't have to ask you
tengo que pedir Pereira no te tengo que
ask
pedir
he also became proud too
también se puso orgulloso también
out of almost 30,000 people I didn't
durante de casi 30.000 personas no me
It seems good because I take the [ __ ]
parece bien porque me tomo la
party to the max Thank you for everything
fiesta al máximo Gracias por todo me
It really sucks to have this problem with you
jode mucho tener este problema contigo
especially with rich and that I appreciate it with
sobre todo con rico y que lo aprecio con
Carola, I appreciate all the work.
Carola que lo aprecio con todo el curro
It pisses me off that you're freaking out and I apologize.
me jode que flipas y yo me Disculpa mi
part for having made you great but that
parte por haberte hecho genial pero que
Knowing that you are wrong is the only thing
sepas que estás equivocado es lo único
Well, it's fine, it seems fine to me, but I
pues está bien me parece bien pero yo
I think I'm not and all the
creo que no lo estoy y toda la
administration and all internet that does not
administración y todo internet que no lo
I'm so sorry that you
estoy así que siento mucho que tu
position yes Look
posición sí Mira
if you want to generate more [ __ ] first
si quieres generar más primero
I mean, it seems wrong to you that I tell you that everything
o sea le parece mal que le diga que todo
the world is saying what it is doing
el mundo está diciendo que está haciendo
rag that is cheating but he
trapo que está haciendo trampas pero le
It seems wrong to tell him that he is
parece mal que le diga que está
generating more [ __ ] when it is
generando más cuando está
exceeding the call to avoid generating more
excedando la llamada para no generar más
[ __ ], well, well, I don't know very well.
bueno bueno pues es que no sé muy
Well these are the problems of the
bien estos son los problemas de las
series I already tell you that if people
series yo ya os digo que si la gente se
wants to take things this way when they come to him
quiere tomar así las cosas cuando se le
They are making you dizzy with reason, so perfect
están mareando con razón pues perfecto
Uncle, that's what there is, a very easy attitude
tío es lo que hay una actitud muy fácil
For my part, I repeat, it seems good to me.
por su parte repito yo ya me parece buen
kid Look at Twitter Look at private Twitter
chaval Mira Twitter Mira Twitter privado
for the future But oh well
para el futuro Pero bueno
It's obvious that he cheated, we're done and
es obvio que ha hecho trampas acabamos y
It is obvious there is no possibility
es obvio no existe una posibilidad
I mean, there's nothing to discuss either.
o sea tampoco hay nada que discutir
if it's exploding and everything you
si está explotando y todo lo que tú
you want but
quieras pero
I think it's a role and now
Yo creo que es un papel y ahora
Do you understand why people
entendéis porque la gente
He's right, he crashes, honestly, no
tiene la razón el chocas sinceramente no
there is a way to
hay manera de
Yes, Pereira is serving very badly when
Sí si el Pereira sacando muy mal cuando
It's cold, I imagine, I imagine, eh
esté en frío me imagino me imagino eh
Because maybe he doesn't care but I
Porque a lo mejor le da igual pero yo
I think it's going to be cold when it's here
creo que va a estar en frío cuando esté
When you think about it, you'll regret this.
en frío se va a arrepentir de este
show every day because it is a
espectáculo cada hoy porque es un
quite an embarrassing spectacle on top
espectáculo bastante bochornoso encima
tells him that he is making a mistake.
le dice que se está equivocando Pues
Of course he has done it, it is not about
claro que lo ha hecho es que no se trata
of cheating because let's see, cheating is not a cheating
de trampa porque a ver trampa no es una
trap as such No because it is not being
trampa como tal No porque no se está
benefiting would not be benefiting
beneficiando no se estaría beneficiando
of
de
that they are telling him things about the other
que le estén chivando cosas del otro
team that they are advancing things to
equipo de que le estén adelantando cosas
that cannot be overtaken
que no se pueden adelantar
but he's talking to the chat and he doesn't know
pero está hablando con el chat y no se
you can talk to the chat okay
puede hablar con el chat vale
Yes, let's see the Dallas video and
Sí vamos a ver lo del vídeo de Dallas y
the end of Beijing we will see it and with
el fin de Beijing vamos a verlo y con
That I take a little more context about
eso Cojo un poco más de contexto sobre
Everything that is happening today is worth it
todo lo que está pasando hoy vale para
Well basically for
Pues básicamente para
[Music]
[Música]
bro calm down it's just one day you don't either
bro Cálmate solo es un día tampoco te
you're going to die of hunger XD
vas a morir de hambre XD
Exactly, on top of that, one day
Exacto es que encima además un día
I want to see also
Quiero ver también
a [ __ ]
una
but a [ __ ] but a huge [ __ ]
pero una pero una pollísima enorme
So you're telling me that it's still there.
O sea me estás diciendo que todavía está
in the premiere of the video or Dallas For me
en estreno el vídeo o sea Dallas Para mi
surprise I had no idea okay ha
sorpresa que no tenía ni idea vale ha
went in person to this podcast at
ido presencialmente a este podcast al
It was Ricky Eddy the other day that
que fue el otro día Ricky Eddy que
We were talking about it, okay?
estuvimos comentándolo vale que por
true The boy the boy put
cierto El chaval el muchacho puso
one posted a comment posted a video no
un puso un comentario puso un vídeo no
in one of the videos that what
en uno de los vídeos que lo que
we were reacting The kid put a
estuvimos reaccionando El chaval puso un
comment and I fixed it okay but it's that
comentario y lo fijé vale pero es que
It's been four [ __ ] hours since its premiere and
lleva cuatro horas de estreno y
It's not over yet and the piece I've
todavía no ha acabado y el trozo que he
been watching
estado viendo
has been headline after headline after headline
ha sido titular tras titular tras
holder
titular
headline after headline
titular tras titular
How the hell am I going to finish watching that?
Cómo voy a terminar yo de ver eso
in parts But well let's see
por partes Pero bueno vamos a ver
some
algunas
you can say it
puedes decirlo
And besides, I mean, I had never seen
Y además ya o sea yo nunca había visto
so open
un tan abierto
How much confidence
Cómo tanta confianza
testimonies lies that I have come here
testimonios mentiras que he venido aquí
It is out there in Spain that is not
está está por ahí en España que no
We are in Andorra recording then
estamos en andorra grabando entonces
I was working not things things of
estaba trabajando No cosas cosas de
retailers So what is the Hero?
minoristas Entonces cuál es el Héroe es
Please don't give me classist humor
un humor clasista por favor no me ponen
The point is that he, for example,
ya el punto está en que él por ejemplo
He also says, damn, I've seen from your
también dice yo he visto desde tus
beginnings until now then you want that
inicios hasta ahora entonces quieras que
This does not connect with the person and it becomes
no esto conecta con la persona y se hace
there is the problem and it is the problem of
ahí el problema y es el problema de
as long as the victims do not report
siempre cuando las víctimas no denuncian
Then it cannot be perceived criminally
Entonces no se puede percibir penalmente
because it is enough for the accused to say it was
porque al acusado le basta con decir era
every assembly was a theater and that's it
todo montaje era todo un teatro y ya
It is there but I don't know which part to watch
está pero es que no sé qué parte ver
I don't know what part to see but it was he
no sé qué parte ver pero es que era he
been watching for like an hour or so
estado viendo como una hora o por ahí
skipping past some things And it was
pasando saltando algunas cosas Y era
headline after headline that has to do with it
titular tras titular que eso tiene que
be
ser
that they don't know how to speak but many times
que hablar no sepan pero muchas veces
I try to focus on things
trato de centrarme en las cosas
fun I play a lot because I say [ __ ]
divertidas juego mucho porque digo
Uncle, are you healthy? You have your life or people?
tío tú estás sano tienes tu vida o gente
that for example without more will be absurd to me
que por ejemplo sin más serán absurdo me
It all seems like a ridiculous little thing
parece unas cositas ridícula todos
We know that your friends and I think that
sabemos que sus amigos y yo creo que lo
is saying
está diciendo
Then I was in a very bad head
Entonces yo estaba muy mal la cabeza en
that moment and what I came to do was
ese momento y lo que llegué a hacer fue
several nights and also insulin
varias noches y también insulina
fall asleep and wait to wake up topic was
dormirme y esperar despertarme tema era
Yes, I've seen it, I think Michael
sí que la he visto creo que Michael
Jackson, I've left this here anyway.
Jackson esto igual por aquí lo he dejado
and then Dallas talked about that it has been
y luego Dallas hablado de que se ha
tried to commit suicide and things like that
intentado suicidar y cosas por el estilo
eh, I mean it's very strong wherever it falls
eh o sea es muy fuerte donde caiga
name but I want to see a full topic
nombre pero quiero ver un tema completo
This part is Jordi Wild's part
esta parte la parte de Jordi Wild
to have how to have my relationships
para tener como tener mis relaciones de
certain dependency things like that that is
cierta dependencia cosas así que es
wismichu when you see that video
wismichu tú cuando ves ese vídeo
spokesperson true that if you don't have a loudspeaker
portavoz cierto que si no tienes altavoz
maybe it remains as if nothing has happened
quizá queda como que no ha pasado nada
but of life because it remains among the
pero de vida porque queda entre los
friends or acquaintances and that's it and the topic is
amigos o los conocidos y ya y el tema se
forget but in my case it is a
olvida pero en el caso mío pues es un
curious catalyst that yesterday is worth it, let's go
catalizador curioso que ayer vale vamos
Let's start seeing it from here, let's see
a empezar a verlo desde aquí vamos a ver
the topic is worth it, let's see the topic a bit
el tema vale vamos a ver el tema un
micho
micho
today he did
hoy hizo
Grandpa, that deserves an exclusive live broadcast for
abuelo eso merece directo exclusivo para
react to the most important parts
reaccionar a las partes más importantes
from the interview is that there is a lot of information
de la entrevista es que hay mucha info
XD
XD
The truth is, this has caught me.
Es que la verdad Esto me ha cogido
completely out of the game and on top of that in
completamente fuera de juego y encima en
today on this day that
el día de hoy en el día de hoy que
We are at our wits' end, we cannot cope
estamos que no podemos no damos abasto
to get all the gossip issues out
para sacar todos los temas de salseo va
and this kid without fear is released
y se estrena El chaval este sin miedo al
success without fear of success launches a
éxito sin miedo al éxito estrena un
podcast with Dallas in person, that is, in
podcast con Dallas presencial o sea en
person you go out before I go out in the
persona tú sales antes yo salgo en el
Fanny podcast Well, please tell me in
podcast Fanny Pues dime por favor en
minutes or whatever because it really is
minutos o lo que sea porque de verdad es
that I've been watching for a [ __ ] hour or more
que he estado viendo una hora más o
less skipping things
menos salteando cosas
I congratulate you without fear of success that you
felicito a sin miedo al éxito que el
another day he left us a comment this
otro día nos puso un comentario este
boy is the one we were with the other day
chico es el que el otro día estuvimos
seeing that I didn't like it very much
viendo que no me hizo mucha gracia
some of your comments but I
algunas de sus comentarios pero me
He clarified some things and gave me a
aclaró algunas cosas y me puso un
comment that I posted on the live stream
comentario que lo fijé en el directo
Okay when
Vale cuando
When this deserves an extensible uncle or
Cuando esto merece un extensible tío o
but I have no idea
sea pero es que no tengo ni idea
[Music]
[Música]
tomorrow is quietly called the
mañana tranquilamente se llama de los
delos is a fan of yours delux is a is a
delos es fan tuyo delux es una es un
colleague knows him in person somewhere
colega lo conoce en persona en alguna
occasion is a colleague I have seen in
ocasión es un colega lo he visto en
person several times Well indeed
persona varias veces Bueno de hecho
I was in my house when I lived in another
estaba en mi casa cuando vivía en otro
floor he was at my house one day ago
piso él estuvo en mi casa un día hace
many years but what does it speak of?
muchos años pero qué es lo que habla de
you in a good stretch Edgar talks about me in
ti en un buen tramo Edgar habla de mí en
a good stretch
un buen tramo
there's a cameo, look for me, look for me in
hay cameo buscarme buscarme en
minutes but it puts me on green or
minutos pero me pone me pone en verde o
good
bien
they make me green or well
me ponen verde o bien
who was his best friend but he is SAT Let's see
que era su mejor amigo pero es SAT A ver
Is it Sad or what? Good, I'm going to start watching it.
es Sad o qué Bueno voy a empezar a verlo
From here I think this part is the
desde aquí que creo que esta parte es la
From wismichu I think it's from wismichu
de wismichu creo que es la de wismichu
but obviously stays here without fear
pero evidentemente queda aquí sin miedo
I'm going to take a week to succeed.
al éxito me voy a sacar pues una semana
of friendly strata I think that
de estratos amigos Es que creo que
should be a live in sensitive
debería ser un directo en sensible
just to extract this
solamente para sacar extracto de esto
Because they were, that is, it is in premiere and
Porque eran o sea está en estreno y
It takes more than 4 hours
Lleva más de 4 horas
It's in its premiere and it's been over 4 hours
está en estreno y Lleva más de 4 horas
I don't know when I'm going to finish
no sé cuándo voy a acabar
I don't know when I'm going to finish. I'd have to go.
no sé cuándo voy a acabar Habría que ir
picking up the pieces and we'll see
cogiendo los trozos y vamos viendo
some pieces
algunos trozos
and another person comes into play who has
y entro en juego otra persona que ha
been I think the biggest speaker with the
sido Yo creo que el mayor altavoz con el
video of This is Dallas here basically
vídeo de Así es Dallas aquí básicamente
They just finished talking. Here they finish.
acaban de terminar de hablar Aquí acaban
to finish talking about the harassment that has
de terminar de hablar del acoso que ha
received Dallas and when has the sack been
recibido Dallas y cuando ha sido el saco
of boxing and internet bullying
de boxeo y el bullying de internet el
bullying not bullying the objective of
bullying no el bullying el objetivo del
bullying is okay, it's wismichu you when
bullying vale que es wismichu tú cuando
you see that video how do you feel
ves ese vídeo cómo te sientes
man there I would sit with a kick in
hombre ahí me sentaría con una patada en
the eggs are being reported to me
los huevos se está informando a mi
person with such delicate issues
persona con temas tan delicados tan
serious and as you later demonstrated with
serios y como luego tú demostraste con
false evidence some not that they were things
pruebas falsas algunas no que eran cosas
which were evident that later in the trial
que eran evidente que luego en el juicio
He says No, at that time I didn't know this.
dice No yo en esa época no sabía esto lo
another has been proven to be a lie
otro se ha demostrado que es mentira
So let's see Win micho's trial
entonces a ver Win micho el juicio de
slander wins because it is a trial
calumnias lo gana porque es un juicio
penal
penal
minute less 31
minuto menos 31
minus 331
menos 331
By the way, grandpa, I caught you giving me F to V.
Por cierto abuelo te pillé dándome F a V
to my tweet about Dallas when I posted
a mi tweet sobre Dallas cuando publiqué
an old screenshot from when I was 800k
una captura antigua de cuando tenía 800k
followers in 2017 a hug king
seguidores en 2017 un abrazo rey
asks you by giving it to you by giving it F What
te pide dándole que dándole F Qué
It means giving F did not understand your
significa dándole F no entendió tu
message to see Sorry forgive me
mensaje a ver Perdona perdonadme
Forgive me, I cut the layer again.
perdonadme he vuelto a cortar el estrato
I'm back, I've cut the extract again
he vuelto he vuelto a cortar el extracto
I've cut the extract again, okay, I'll go.
he vuelto a cortar el extracto vale voy
to start recording again because I
a empezar a grabar otra vez porque me
You guys are crazy, I'm going to start recording it.
tenéis loco voy a empezar a grabarlo
again because you have me crazy okay
otra vez porque me tenéis loco vale a
see
ver
It is that sincerely clear that if it is
es que sinceramente claro es que si lo
If I don't react now this part as
si no lo reacciono ahora esta parte como
It's still in its premiere, then we'll go
está en estreno todavía luego vamos a
lose the timing, come on, let's see it and
perder el minutaje venga vamos a verlo y
then we see the piece of wismichu today no
luego vemos el trozo de wismichu hoy no
if you fall asleep we make an extensible one here
se duerme hacemos aquí un extensible
we make an extensible one and [ __ ] off
hacemos un extensible y a tomar por culo
I join a couple of days
empalmo un par de días
I'll spend a couple of days to see. It turns out to be
empalmo un par de días a ver Resulta ser
that today is a crazy day if it were
que hoy el día es una locura si fuera
little if it were little all that is
poco si fuera poco todo lo que está
passing today the Pereira Beijing clash
pasando hoy el choca Pereira Beijing lo
that it is worth generating Thank you very much yes
que sea vale gerar Muchísimas gracias si
We reached 2,000 members and I stayed all
llegamos a 2.000 miembros me quedo toda
the night
la noche
2000 is very little, there are a hundred or so missing
2000 es muy poco faltan ciento y pico
nothing more But well 2100 if we get to
nada más Pero bueno 2100 si llegamos a
2100 members I stay all night
2100 miembros me quedo toda la noche lo
we see everything until the time it ends
vemos todo hasta la hora que se acabe
Okay, I don't know what time it will end.
vale No sé a la hora que se terminará
but we see that everything is worth it
pero lo vemos todo vale vale
the kid who the other day
el chaval que el otro día
I approve the extensible grandfather here my
apruebo el extensible abuelo aquí mi
contribution on Twitch XD But it has to be
aporte en Twitch XD Pero tiene que ser
a madness for me to see extensible
una locura para que yo a ver extensible
No, but I stayed up all night.
no pero que me quedo toda la noche dure
as long as it lasts counting all the topics
lo que dure contando todos los temas
reviewing all the topics
revisando todos los temas
For 1,2100 2,500 members I think about it
por mil 2100 2.500 miembros me lo pienso
2100 2,500 members I think about it but
2100 2.500 miembros me lo pienso pero
Well for now we're going to see this one
bueno de momento vamos a ver este
extract okay or so this is a [ __ ]
extracto vale o sea esto es una
madness this is [ __ ] madness It turns out
locura esto es una locura Resulta
be that the boy I give it to
ser que el chico este al que le doy la
Congratulations
Enhorabuena
without fear of the success that put us
sin miedo al éxito que nos puso un
comment pinned the other day that
comentario fijado el otro día que
we were relating him to the thing about
estuvimos relacionando a él con lo de
Ricky Eddy that Ricky also did this
Ricky Eddy que Ricky también hizo este
podcast last week It turns out that
podcast la semana pasada Resulta ser que
If the day's gossip were not enough,
si fuera poco el salseo del día por si
the gossip of the day was not enough
fuera poco el salseo del día
goes and puts on the premiere that is now
va y pone en estreno que está ahora
same takes four and a quarter hours
mismo lleva cuatro horas y cuarto de
premiere
estreno
4 hours and a quarter of premiere And still
4 horas y cuarto de estreno Y todavía le
And it is still quietly there
queda Y todavía está tranquilamente allí
Chatting the dala is worth it, that is, in person
Charlando el dala vale o sea en persona
in person
en presencial
as if the day were not enough
por si por si fuera poco el día
If the day were not enough, then let's go
por si fuera poco el día Entonces vamos
to see some of us some sections today but
a vernos algunas algunos tramos hoy pero
I think that during the week we are going to go
yo creo que durante la semana vamos a ir
seeing stretches and stretches and stretches because
viendo tramos y tramos y tramos porque
This is never over It's never like I was before
esto no se acaba Nunca es que yo antes
I've set an hour for you to sleep today.
me he puesto una hora hoy no duermes
old tasty and neither do we
viejos sabroso y Nosotros tampoco
it will depend on you
dependerá de ustedes
It will depend on you if I run out
dependerá de ustedes si me quedo sin
Whether you sleep through the night or not will depend on
dormir hoy toda la noche o no dependerá
of you as you command
de ustedes como ustedes ustedes mandáis
in me I am my boss okay it turns out
en mí Soy mi jefe vale resulta
Lola a kiss it turns out that well yes
Lola un beso resulta que bueno si
we reached 2000 2500 members not Teresa
llegamos a 2000 2500 miembros no Teresa
If we reach 2,500 members we stay
si llegamos a 2500 miembros nos quedamos
all night we spliced ​​we spliced ​​all night
toda la noche empalmamos empalmamos toda
the night is worth it
la noche vale
We see all the topics and we finish at 7 a.m.
vemos todos los temas acabemos a las 7 a
8 to 9 in the morning or whatever
las 8 a las 9 de la mañana o lo que sea
yes there is I've been watching skipping
sí hay Yo he estado viendo salteando
like an hour or so and it was
como una hora más o menos y era
headlines after headlines was headline
titulares tras titulares era titular
after headline about wismichu about Jordi
tras titular lo de wismichu lo de Jordi
that's an outrage. So let's go
lo de una barbaridad Entonces vamos a
see this minute that you sent me
ver este minuto que me habéis mandado
that apparently about me we are going to see it
que por lo visto sobre mí vamos a verlo
Let's see this minute and it depends on how
vamos a ver este minuto y depende como
Let's see the night, let's see more
vaya viendo la noche vamos viendo más
Okay
vale
Let's see, you told me what I have here
a ver me habéis dicho que tengo aquí
cameo that I don't know if it's a little Sad no
cameo que no sé si es un poco Sad no
has given me the best community it can
me ha dado la mejor comunidad que puede
exist then no rigrets okay I don't
existir entonces no rigrets vale No me
I regret absolutely nothing about that
arrepiento absolutamente nada de eso
to finish
para terminar
About Javi, the truth is that but
sobre lo de Javi la verdad es que pero
Wait wait start before start
Espera espera empieza antes empieza
before about Javi it ​​starts earlier
antes sobre lo de Javi empieza antes
Look at the key point, I believe the Game Over
Mira el punto clave yo creo el Game over
from my area do you think it was video eye eye
de mi área crees que fue video ojo ojo
that there is that comes from before that comes from
que hay que viene de antes que viene de
previously flown Well in this case I believe
antes voladas Pues en este caso Yo creo
that you had an anime that we all
que tuvieras un anime que todos nos
we have swallowed it whole and from there then
hemos tragado entero y de ahí pues
You can have haters who are retractors and who don't
puedes tener haters retractores que no
They wanted to get soaked, they didn't want to see
han querido empaparse no han querido ver
both versions and that in the end they have
las dos versiones y que al final se han
left with the speech of the youtuber who
quedado con el discurso del youtuber que
They like it but the reality is that there are
les gusta pero la realidad es que hay
a person behind who has been
una persona detrás que ha estado
struggling for years to achieve today
luchando durante años para lograr hoy
day I think I have practically redeemed myself
día Yo creo ya redimirse prácticamente
I think you've reached a point where
yo creo que has llegado un punto en el
that people are already starting to agree
que ya la gente empieza a dar la razón
I was going to tell you because there is a video here
te iba a decir porque aquí hay un vídeo
key I believe the Game over of Minare
clave yo creo el Game over de minare
Do you think it was Javier Veira's video?
crees que fue vídeo de Javier veira el
point that made the turning point that
punto que hizo el punto de inflexión que
made people start seeing you with
hizo que la gente empezara a verte con
good eyes
buenos ojos
without listening to Dallas' response
sin escuchar la respuesta de Dallas
without listening to Dallas's answer is worth it
sin escuchar la respuesta de Dallas vale
I don't know what he'll say I don't know what he'll say but
No sé lo que dirá No sé lo que dirá pero
I think that I think that yes I think that
yo creo que yo creo que sí yo creo que
Game over is a turning point
el game over es un punto de inflexión
Even if it's mine, it's worth it even if it's mine
aunque sea mío vale aunque sea mío
although it is not Dallas himself who
aunque no es el propio Dallas el que
makes that video I think it's a great
hace ese vídeo Yo creo que es un gran
turning point because because great
punto de inflexión porque porque gran
April part Thank you very much forgive me
parte abril Muchas gracias perdonarme
that one of us personally thanks each other
que nos agradezca personalmente uno a
one is worth it I already do it We already do it at
uno vale Ya lo hago Ya lo hacemos al
final Although
final Aunque
[Music]
[Música]
Although not even though that video doesn't do it
Aunque no aunque no lo haga ese vídeo el
Dallas itself, whether you like it or not
propio Dallas quieras que no lo está
making a person very critical of
haciendo una persona muy crítica con
Dallas In fact I think that in that
Dallas De hecho yo creo que en ese
moment that was most critical with
momento el que más crítico era con
Dallas is worth it And the one who was most involved
Dallas vale Y el que estaba más metido
in history because whether you like it or not, I
en la historia porque quieras que no yo
had some contact even that arrived
tenía cierto contacto incluso que llegó
to be friends with the Dallas gang
a ser amistad con con el bando de Dallas
that is, the people who were there the most
o sea las personas que más estaban
making Dallas the escracharse or
haciendo que a Dallas el escracharse o
sea
sea
These people have done a lot for him
esta gente han hecho mucho por el por el
hate adala a long time ago in fact to this day
hate adala hace mucho de hecho a día de
today they still take care of talking to each other
hoy todavía se ocupan de hablarse con
people who are the ones who keep the accounts
gente que son los que llevan las cuentas
and I mean not only Twitter accounts
y O sea no solamente cuentas en Twitter
strange but strange channels in
extrañas sino canales extraños en
YouTube, which are the ones left hanging
YouTube que son los que quedan tirando
no then
no entonces
much much of what falls to Dallas and
mucho mucho de lo que le cae al Dallas y
that Dala was the punching bag
de que dala fuera el saco de boxeo de
the internet is on the part of the
internet es por parte de las
cancellations of these people are worth it or so
cancelaciones de esta gente vale o sea
behind the minors' complaint,
detrás de la denuncia de las menores el
trial that Dallas had of the minors
juicio que tuvo Dallas de las menores la
The one who filed that complaint is a lady, okay?
que pone esa denuncia es una señora vale
that you all know Who He is and that is not
que todos sabéis Quién es y eso no es
I say it because it has happened to me
que lo diga yo porque a mí me lo hayan
It is said that there are many people who take
contado es que hay mucha gente que coge
the part of the sentence that is that
la parte de la sentencia que está que
You can search for the sentence of the
ustedes podéis Buscar sentencia de la
review and you can read the sentence and it is
review y podéis leer la sentencia y se
they start to take the nonsense of the torso
ponen a la tontería del torso
naked when there are 500 million things
desnudo cuando hay 500 millones de cosas
more important in that sentence and more
más importantes en esa sentencia y más
revealing that this error because
reveladoras que ese error porque al
final was a mistake because the judges did not
final fue un error porque los jueces no
They understand the Internet well many times
entienden bien de internet muchas veces
and when it was time to pick it up he picked it up wrong
y a la hora de recogerlo lo recogió mal
because if you see the judgment in the judgment
porque si tú ves el juicio en el juicio
What Dallas says is that
lo que dice Dallas es que
the girl the only photo I could have
la chica la única foto que podía tener
This is a photo that was in his
de él Así es una foto que estaba en
internet of him shirtless And that caught
internet de él sin camiseta Y eso cogió
The judge translated it into astonishment but it is a
la jueza lo tradujo en pasmo pero es una
acquittal if it were true
sentencia absolutoria si fuera verdad
that Dallas is sending photos
que Dallas se está mandando fotos
sexual relations with a minor are condemned, not
sexuales con una menor lo condenan no lo
They acquit him and condemn him even if it was a
absuelven lo condenan aunque fuera una
sentence that does not include jail time although
condena que no entra en la cárcel aunque
was a sentence of 6 months of one year
fuera una condena de 6 meses de un año
but they condemn him so that the uncle remains
pero lo condenan para que el tío quede
marked
marcado
three judges okay And apart there are others
tres juezas vale Y aparte hay otras
many things that dismantle those of the torso
muchas cosas que desmontan los del torso
In the sentence itself it tells you that at
en la propia sentencia te dice que a las
three girls or four I'm not going back
tres chicas o cuatro No me vuelvo a
infect No I spoke to a couple of
contagiar No yo hablé con un par de
they
ellas
The police asked him passively to
le pidió la policía por pasiva que
They will hand over the conversations they had
entregarán las conversaciones que tenían
with Dallas and they never did it and then
con Dallas y nunca lo hicieron y luego
There was also a group where
Aparte también había un grupo donde se
The police were lying but I know
hablaba de mentira la policía pero sé
that whoever wants to take that sentence
que el que quiera esa sentencia
to attack Dallas
para atacar Dallas
is that he has not read it is that he has taken
es que no la ha leído es que ha cogido
only the piece that David Bravo
solamente el trozo que el David Bravo
He wanted to put it on Twitter without further ado.
quiso poner en Twitter sin más que lo
from the torso whoever wants to take the
del torso el que quiera la
sentence to attack Dallas is that
sentencia para atacar al Dallas es eso
What's the deal? The deal is that
Cuál es la movida pues La Movida es que
The game over amiare is a video
el game over amiare pues es un vídeo
very relevant in that story okay And I
muy relevante en esa historia vale Y yo
I think the video has a lot of merit in
creo que el vídeo tiene mucho mérito en
Yes because it is a completely video
Sí porque es un vídeo completamente
sincere
sincero
It is a completely sincere video of the
es un vídeo completamente sincero de la
person who was the hardest hitter in Dallas
persona que más caña le daba al Dallas
then
en ese momento
It is worth a lot because he had his head
vale gran parte porque tenía la cabeza
that kept getting hotter too
que no paraba de calentarme la también
but well, it's my fault and hey, I don't
pero bueno mucha culpa mía y Oye yo no
I swallowed it, I couldn't see the whole thing
lo tragaba no lo podía ver todo el rollo
That one is not And because I also joined the
ese no Y porque también me sumé a la
I'm not going to deny it, it's worth what it is.
turba no te lo voy a negar vale lo que
It was well seen on the internet to go to
estaba bien visto en internet era ir a
find Dalas and then well, hey yes
encontrar Dalas y entonces pues Oye si
everyone is against it for a reason
todo el mundo va en contra es por algo
It's not because the guy is an [ __ ]
no es porque el tío es un
what a mess I tell you what a mess Well what
qué movida os digo que movida Pues que
That video, the guinoveramiare, is a video
ese vídeo el guinoveramiare es un vídeo
how clear
que claro
even if it is a video that is not missing
aunque sea un vídeo que no falta al
respect is neither slanderous nor insulting nor
respeto ni es calumnioso ni injurioso ni
nothing like that is a video that
nada por el estilo es un vídeo que a la
another part hurt them so much it hurt them
otra parte les dolió tanto le dolió
so much the video that as of 2000
tantísimo el vídeo que a raíz del 2000
2019 I have had a lot of problems
2019 yo he tenido un montón de problemas
many of you who don't even know many that
muchos que ni siquiera sabéis muchos que
You don't even know but as a result of 2019
ni siquiera sabéis pero a raíz del 2019
I have experienced some episodes of
yo he vivido unos episodios de
try me
intentarme
really leave me off the internet
de verdad dejarme fuera de internet
offside
fuera de juego
okay, that is tremendous tremendous
vale o sea tremendo tremendo
[Music]
[Música]
One of the episodes was when
uno de los episodios fue cuando
They tried to have fulfilled the new one
intentaron que han cumplido con nuevo el
extensive smiling face
extensivo cara sonriendo
who have complied with the warning and
que han cumplido con la advertencia no y
I'm going to call it a warning for not having
lo voy a llamar advertencia Por no tener
more problems Although surely it
más problemas Aunque seguramente lo
I will always have this for life because this
tendré siempre y de por vida porque esto
It will be for life But when they sent me
será de por vida Pero cuando me mandaron
the warning not that I was silent
la advertencia no de que me callaba la
little mouth I shut my little mouth or
boquita me callaba la boquita o
they would publish some of my conversations
publicarían unas conversaciones mías
to destroy my family is worth it And then
para destrozar a mi familia vale Y luego
With time, it is no longer just that
con el tiempo pues ya no solamente que
I exploded in that live and said
yo explotas en aquel directo y dijera
the things I said but with the
las cosas que dije sino que con el
Time has proven me right in case there is
tiempo me ha dado la razón por si hay
someone who didn't believe I was being treated
alguien que no creía que me estaban
making those warnings Well with the
haciendo esas advertencias Pues con el
time what it has done has been to catch the
tiempo lo que ha hecho ha sido al
boyfriend post conversations [ __ ]
novio publicar las conversaciones
to the fool on duty who pays attention to him and
al tonto de turno que le haga caso y
publish and publish the
publicar y que publique las
conversations and he takes the fall
conversaciones y se coma él el marrón
now you know what you have done
ahora sabe o sea pero lo que ha hecho
with that it has been proving to me that
con eso ha sido darme la razón de que a
They were trying to intimidate me with
mí me estaban intentando amedrentar con
conversations are worth it
conversaciones vale
and of course even if they file 8000 lawsuits
y claro Aunque pongan 8000 demandas
Even if they file 8,000 lawsuits
Aunque pongan 8000 demandas
They will never be able to put that video in and
ese vídeo nunca lo van a poder meter y
with Lorena pregnant Yes yes the purpose
con Lorena embarazada Sí si el propósito
We already know which video is doing damage
ya sabemos Cuál es hacer daño el vídeo
That one from Game Over Even if they put 8000
ese de Game over Aunque pongan 8000
demand that video they can never put it in
demanda ese vídeo nunca lo pueden meter
and they never put him in any lawsuit
y nunca lo meten en ninguna demanda
You know why? Because it's a video, you'll see.
sabéis por qué Porque es un vídeo verás
everything that is said in the video where not
todo lo que se dice en el vídeo donde no
Respect is needed and where there is no way
hace falta respeto y donde no hay manera
that I delete that video What is the
de que yo elimine ese vídeo Cuál es la
pressure because taking out 8000 things from
presión pues sacando 8000 cosas de
context and that the video was out of spite
contexto y que el vídeo era por despecho
and finally a lot of things that today
y en fin un montón de cosas que a día de
today still the mother who pricks her a
hoy todavía la madre que la pincha un
little by little and he lets loose with all kinds of nonsense
poco y y te suelta cualquier barbaridad
Okay, so keep making mistakes and keep going.
Vale pues sigue metiendo la pata y sigue
Saying things like that is worth yesterday
diciendo cosas como esa vale ayer mismo
They sent me a tweet in which
me mandaron un tweet en el que en el que
the mother kept saying the same thing you know
la madre seguía diciendo lo mismo sabes
thinks he can convince people
cree que puede convencer a la gente de
that video out of spite is worth In fact
que ese vídeo por despecho vale De hecho
when when
cuando cuando
conversation is intimate the mother put
conversación es íntima la madre se puso
to tweet like that Haha look at session
a tuitear como que Jaja mira sesión
bizarrap of the spite what spite
bizarrap de la del despecho qué despecho
not like Shakira, there's no such thing as things like that
no como Shakira cosas así no hay como no
Lady, you are not going to accept what she is in life.
señora no va a colar en la vida qué es
What happens is that the video itself is
lo que pasa pues que el vídeo en sí es
from a person critical of Dallas
de una persona crítica con Dallas
and that has been involved in and that has
y que ha estado metido en y que tiene
a lot of information from the other party is worth
mucha información de la otra parte vale
That's the move That's the importance
Esa es la movida Esa es la importancia
that video had
que tuvo ese vídeo
Ah answer that but going back to it
Ah responde a eso pero volviendo lo
Previously, the thing about brands does bring me
anterior lo de las marcas sí me trae
problems with brands but at the same time
problemas con marcas pero al mismo
time has given me the best community that
tiempo me ha dado la mejor comunidad que
may exist then it is not worth more
puede existir entonces no vale más
seeing absolutely none of that
viendo absolutamente nada de eso
problems with brands yes
problemas con las marcas sí
obviously
evidentemente
Dallas is not called by the brands that
a Dallas no lo llaman las marcas que
You must give him the numbers that he has
debe darle los números que tiene el
reach that Dallas would have for
alcance que tiene Dallas Sería para
It would be to be much more infinitely
Sería para estar mucho más infinitamente
more more doing more madness you dodge in
más más haciendo más locura esquiváis en
plan to collaborate with Coca-Cola
plan de estar colaborando con coca-cola
with I don't know who making programs
con no sé quién haciendo programas los
The numbers that Dallas has are for that
números que tiene el Dallas son para eso
comic book I don't know what movies What
libro cómic no sé qué películas Lo que
It happens that the problem that you have is the
pasa que el problema que tiene es la
cover they make for you
funda que le hacen
and they organize themselves to have them done
y que se organizan para que se las hagan
Okay
vale
indisputably but it is true
indiscutiblemente pero sí que es verdad
that has a community that you want
que tiene una comunidad que quieras que
have not gone through this type of funas
no han pasado por este tipo de funas
It is then worth a filter that makes
Vale entonces un filtro que hace que
have some confidence in your community and
tenga cierta confianza en tu comunidad y
that they are not absurd, idiotic little sheep
que no son borreguitos absurdos idiotas
Okay, not just anyone can get through the hoop.
vale que no cuelan por el Aro cualquier
barbarity is a good filter there are people
barbaridad es un buen filtro hay gente
that on the other side, there are people who
que ya del otro bando vale hay gente que
only now you can grab onto them
solamente ya se puede agarrar a los
These pathetic channels for Twitter users
canales penositos estos a los tuiteros
These are the ones that are in bad shape, you know, or rather, in
estos que están fatal sabes o sea en
plan cannot aspire to any other type of
plan no pueden aspirar a otro tipo de
Defenders and supporters
Defensores y de apoyos
to finish
para terminar
upload it from Javi the truth is that
súbelo de Javi la verdad es que
There has definitely been a lot to
definitivamente ha habido muchísimo a
change that perception of myself above all
cambiar esa percepción de mí sobre todo
because he was the main spokesperson in
porque él era el portavoz principal en
that time of hatred against me had
esa época del odio en mi contra había
done many atrocities against me
hecho muchísimas barbaridades sobre mí
I have been threatened with death
me ha llegado amenazar de muerte
aldalá I got to tell him that I wanted
aldalá Le llegué a decir que quería
burst him or wanted to see him in a ditch
reventarle o quería verlo en una cuneta
not busted I don't remember what it was like
no reventado no me acuerdo cómo era
I long for a kiss from the gutter, the gutter, me
anhelo un beso el cunetas el cuneta me
call And then the fact that
llaman Y entonces el hecho de que
change that perspective definitively
cambiase esa perspectiva definitivamente
It helped a lot in that whole case 100%
ayudó mucho en todo ese caso al 100%
It is also true that it was not the only one or
también Es verdad que no fue el solo o
there were a series of things and it does
sea hubieron una serie de cosas y hace
things made him change and
cosas le hicieron cambiar a él y
so he ended up changing I think
entonces él terminó cambiando creo que
The biggest turning point was perhaps
el punto de inflexión mayor tal vez fue
all the lies they made with me
toda la mentira que hicieron con mi
dog I think people were already seeing
perro creo que ya la gente venía viendo
as if from me I started with the others
como que desde yo empecé con los demás
Look, you know what?
Mira sabes qué
What is true is the turning point A
qué sí es verdad el punto de inflexión A
see is a turning point for me
ver es que un punto de inflexión para mí
comes comes from before
viene viene de antes
There are live shows that are here in the canijo
hay directos que está aquí en el canijo
it's probably worth it
seguramente vale
Let's see, there is also a turning point
a ver hay un punto también de inflexión
that was
que fue
the debate I had with him first
el debate que yo hice con él el primero
okay in which I made a complete fool of myself
vale en el que hice el completo ridículo
okay why because I was signing
vale por qué porque yo estaba firmando
a series of situations and things
una serie de situaciones y de cosas
that had them completely
que las tenía completamente
internalized from conversations and
interiorizada de la de conversaciones y
the things he had talked about during
la de cosas que había hablado durante
hours on that subject than I
horas sobre ese tema que la que yo
I was perfectly convinced and as
estaba perfectamente convencido y como
Of course I don't consider myself an idiot.
claro No me considero una persona idiota
I was and I am also a made person
yo estaba y además soy una persona hecha
forward without fear because I said clearly
palante sin miedo pues yo dije claro
clear debate we debate no but of course there
claro debate debatimos no pero claro ahí
There were a lot of things that I couldn't do
hubo un montón de cosas que yo no pude
keep
mantener
Okay, there's a lot of stuff there that I
vale Ahí hay un montón de cosas que yo
I couldn't keep you know then I already
no pude mantener sabes entonces ya yo
said
dije
Okay, it was a debate with very good content.
vale fue un debate como contenido muy
epic worth Victoria a kiss on the face of
épico vale Victoria un beso la cara de
Javi watching Dallas talk about him kara
Javi viendo a Dallas hablar de él kara
smiling face in love smiling face
sonriente cara enamorada cara sonriente
outside of the joke a person who
fuera del cachondeo una persona a la que
I have a certain appreciation for him, okay, I'll be there.
le tengo cierto aprecio vale estaré de
I agree with him on many things and in others
acuerdo con él en muchas cosas en otras
Maybe not but he is a person that I
A lo mejor no pero es una persona que yo
is a person within my career
es una persona dentro de mi carrera
also very very important for
también muy muy importante para para
good I would say for the better
bien Yo diría para bien
Until now Twitch notified me
Hasta ahorita me notificó el Twitch
I arrived late a big strong kiss
llegué tarde un beso grande fuerte un
big kiss let's see The gallant can't be
beso grande a ver El galán no puede ser
a person who is left out of everything
una persona que queda fuera de todo lo
that has been my internet career worth it
que ha sido mi carrera de internet vale
Although I am now more focused on the
Aunque yo ahora esté más centrado en las
These are the things of gossip and of the
cosas estas de los cotilleos y de la
TV and so on we cannot forget where we come from
tele y demás no podemos olvidar de dónde
We came and how we went
venimos Y cómo hemos ido
entering the world of the internet and the
entrando en el mundo de internet y en la
History is worth it in that debate there was something
historia vale en ese debate hubo algo
there was something but as I still had
hubo algo pero como Todavía tenía
relationship and heading, well, good
relación y encabezamiento pues bueno
time passed and so on, then there was already
pasado el tiempo y demás luego ya hubo
another second debate then there were others
otro segundo debate luego hubo otros
another second debate that was more like
otro segundo debate que fue como más
calmed the first debate as content
calmado el primer debate como contenido
spectacular but today is the complete one
espectacular pero hoy es el completo
ridiculous or rather and be completely ridiculous
ridículo o sea y ser completo ridículo
a careful cani, that is, a cani that
un cani de Cuidado o sea un cani que
It has just arrived on the internet as if it were
acaba de llegar a internet como si se
I thought I was in the square
creía que estaba en la plazoleta del
Neighborhood, it's tremendous, okay?
Barrio O sea tremendo vale
but there was a second debate where there
pero hubo un segundo debate donde ahí
also something told me
también algo me dijo
[Music]
[Música]
I don't dislike this kid
este chaval no me cae mal
I actually have a conversation with
De hecho tengo una conversación con
Dallas in which he says you and I don't
Dallas en la que él me dice tú y yo no
we would actually get along, I don't know
en realidad nos llevaríamos bien no sé
These are some moves. Okay, what we talked about was
son unas movidas Vale qué hablamos fue
when they lied to you about going to a trial and
cuando te mintieron de ir a un juicio y
They never appeared and you came out to justify
nunca aparecieron y saliste a justificar
One kiss, one kiss is enough, that's it, that's it.
un beso ya un beso ya vale eso eso es
important what you just said I was going to
importante lo que acabas de decir lo iba
Now to comment on La Movida is that
a comentar ahora La Movida es que
[Music]
[Música]
the dog thing
lo del perro
for a few weeks I had the
durante unas cuantas de semana yo lo del
dog I knew it okay maybe I didn't
perro lo sabía vale a lo mejor no me
I agree if a couple of weeks or three don't
acuerdo si un par de semanas tres no me
agreed how long no But there was
acuerdo cuánto tiempo no Pero había
certain things about the dog that I knew
ciertas cosas del perro que yo sabía
Obviously that's why I have been a witness
evidentemente por eso he sido testigo
not now
ahora no
but
pero
with the dog
con lo del perro
They sold it to me in a way with
yo me lo vendían a mí de una manera con
one with some things no but there was a point
una con unas cosas no pero hubo un punto
which was key
que fue clave
that there were several lies, some by
que hubo varias mentiras algunas por
private things that I can't say and others
privadas que no puedo decir y otras
public
públicas
in which I felt used and not
en las que yo me sentí utilizado y no
There is something that really pisses me off.
hay algo que me toque mal los me
understand or that is why they take me for
entiende o sea porque que me tomen por
something for someone stupid Well the truth is
algo por alguien tonto Pues la verdad es
that I don't like it, it doesn't suit me, it's okay
que no me no me va no me va vale
First of all something happened, I don't know if
en primer lugar paso una cosa no sé si
You know it, I don't know if I say it in the
ustedes lo sabéis no sé si lo digo en el
equinover is fine but first it happens
equinover vale pero en primer lugar pasa
one thing
una cosa
I have already had several seasons in
Yo ya hubo varios varias temporadas en
the ones I stopped talking to them
las que me dejé de hablar con ellos nos
we stopped talking to each other several times
dejamos de hablar mutuamente varias
things were not were not were not only
cosas no no era no fue únicamente
After Game Over there were others
después del Game Over hubo otros
moments when I stopped talking to myself
momentos en los que yo me dejé de hablar
with them for being ugly and for things not
con ellos por por feos y por cosas no
but when the dog thing happened
pero cuando pasó lo del perro
I went through the Chrome thing in 2018, okay? And
yo pasé con lo del Chrome en 2018 vale Y
The dog's thing was the last day of
lo del perro fue el último día de
December 2018 when the incident happened
diciembre del 2018 cuando pasó lo del
dog
perro
It was December 28, 2018 and I was
fue el 28 de diciembre de 2018 y a mí me
diagnosed with Chrome disease
diagnosticaron Chrome enfermedad de
Crohn's would be because I don't remember if it was
crohn sería pues no me acuerdo si era
June
junio
It was before the summer of 2018, okay, it would be
fue antes del verano del 2018 vale sería
do the months of May and June all kinds of things
hacer los meses de mayo junio cosas toda
That time is fine. I was hospitalized for a month.
esa época vale Yo tuve un mes ingresado
very bad that they didn't know what it was
muy malito que no sabían qué es lo que
I had okay I was doing all the
yo tenía vale estuve haciendo todo el
world knew it and it wasn't a thing
mundo lo sabía además no era una cosa
private because I made videos from the
privada porque yo hacía vídeos desde el
hospital I was very sick because I didn't
hospital Yo estaba muy malito porque no
they found what they were first, which is the
daban con lo que eran primero que es el
colon first yes
colon primero que sí
ulcerative colitis I don't know a lot about
colitis ulcerosa no sé un montón de
tests and a lot of [ __ ] is worth the
pruebas y un montón de vale el
body rejecting everything from me in short
cuerpo rechazándomelo todo en fin una
move is worth it
movida vale
Nobody calls me for me, nobody knows
a mí nadie me llama por mí nadie se
it worries me okay
preocupa vale
To me sincerely So it is true that
a mí sinceramente Así que es verdad que
You are putting in Chano she went to
estáis poniendo en el Chano ella fue a
Seville signed a book and no te and no
Sevilla firmó un libro y no te y no
He wanted to stay with you, that's what it seemed to me
quiso quedar contigo a mí eso me pareció
a little ugly and such But well as it was going
un poco feo Y tal Pero bueno como iba
Since I was busy or whatever, I said
como iba liada o lo que sea pues digo
Okay, well, I'll be there. Okay, but it wasn't.
vale Bueno voy a estar Vale pero no fue
That episode, that is, for me there is also
ese episodio o sea para mí también hay
a very important and very episode
un episodio muy importante y muy
shameless and happened twice is worth one was
descarado y pasó dos veces vale uno fue
One was in October when Dallas starts
uno fue en octubre cuando Dallas empieza
to make videos looking for his dog
a hacer vídeos buscando a su perro
because they have told him that the dog is in
porque le han dicho que el perro está en
the bride's neighborhood
el barrio de la novia
Suddenly she sends me a message on
de repente ella me manda un mensaje en
October that suddenly
octubre que de repente
worrying because I have had
preocupándose porque yo he tenido
Chrome disease that I said now
enfermedad de Chrome que yo dije ahora
that Dallas is starting to give you a hard time
que él Dallas empieza está dándote caña
Now you come to the biggest gossip channel
ahora vienes tú al mayor canal de salseo
to worry about your health status Okay
a preocuparte de su estado de salud Vale
and
y
[Music]
[Música]
There was a thing similar to that like in
hubo una cosa similar a esa como en
January days before if it was not the same day
enero días antes si no fue el mismo día
It was a couple of days before Game Over
fue un par de días antes del Game Over
that Mario Tiberian apparently or
que el Mario tiberian por lo visto o
Someone found her and told her she's coming
alguien se la encontró y le dijo viene
the banana but I had already said it in
el guineo pero yo ya lo había dicho en
somewhere whatever and then she'll
algún lado lo que sea y entonces ella me
He spoke in the morning Oh Javi I realized
habló por la mañana Ay Javi me he dado
realize that I had not taken it away from you
cuenta que no te había quitado el
block I have unblocked you talk to me
bloqueo te he quitado el bloqueo háblame
I don't know if there was any movement on WhatsApp.
por WhatsApp no sé que alguna movida si
I don't remember, no
no me acuerdo no
and the point was the lies with what
y ya el punto fue las mentiras con lo
of the dog okay there is a there is a direct that
del perro vale hay un hay un directo que
I imagine that it will be in that it will be in
me imagino que estará en que estará en
public still surely
público todavía seguramente
Dallas starts to say in some videos
Dallas empieza a decir en unos vídeos
that my parents when they have been
que los padres de miare cuando han sido
caught with the dog have to go to
pillados con el perro tienen que ir a
testify to I don't know what played and also
testificar a no sé qué jugado y además
says the day and time in case people
dice el día y la hora por si la gente
wants to go see it because the view
quiere ir a verlo porque la vista
public no
pública no
then the mother who used to be
entonces la madre que solía estar
with me in contact same house now no
conmigo en contacto igual casa ahora no
that the mother is more involved in the
que está más la madre metida en la
controversy than the one that the own
polémica que la que la propia
protagonist the mother used to send me
protagonista la madre me solía mandar
things when I was live
cosas cuando yo estaba en directo
Speaking of Dallas, he only sends me things.
hablando de Dallas me sol le manda cosas
so that I could say and so on no
para que yo dijera y demás no
information because the mother tells me in
informaciones pues la madre Me dice en
live plenary session that of course they are going to
pleno directo que por supuesto que van a
go to court, at what point are they not going?
ir al juzgado que en qué momento no van
to go to court, which of course I will
a ir al juzgado que por supuesto que sí
Who the hell is thinking of this?
que quién se le pasa por la cabeza
that she they are not going to go play that
que ella ellos no van a ir a jugar que
Of course yes and
Claro que sí y
[Music]
[Música]
They were not worth everything they
no fueron vale ellos todo lo que
They tried to do as they had The Lie
intentaron hacer como tenían La Mentira
The thing about the dog was to postpone it, to postpone it
de lo del perro fue aplazarlo aplazarlo
postponing it is worth it
aplazarlo vale
with the debates that no one had done
con los debates que eso nadie lo había
made great
hecho grandes
I was a pioneer in making that garbage and
yo fui pionero en hacer esa basura y
Of course that's what people made him think, damn it
claro eso la gente le hizo pensar
someone who is guilty of doing this I
alguien que es culpable hacer esto Yo
I think that was the people and
creo que esa fue la gente y
obviously and that's why I could do it
evidentemente y por eso lo podía hacer
without any kind of problem always
sin ningún tipo de problema siempre la
phrase of nothing fears then I think that
frase de nada teme entonces creo que
those things happened and finally that
pasaron esas cosas y finalmente eso le
He made him change too and then he
hizo cambiar él también y entonces él
who was within that group and was
que estaba dentro de ese grupo y era
friend of that group because it ended
amigo de ese grupo pues terminó
distancing those people even coming
distanciando esa gente incluso viniendo
to declare judgment on my dog
a declarar juicio de mi perro
that I was never going to do it
que yo no iba a hacerlo nunca iba a
do it what happens that how that happened
hacerlo lo que pasa que como pasó eso
With my wife, as you will understand me
con mi mujer Pues como tú me entenderás
If you do it to me, if you go after my family
si me haces si tú vas a por mi familia
You already have her with me, Clara.
Ya conmigo la llevas Clara
If you go with my family, then that's it.
si tú vas con mi familia pues ya ahí ya
you lost is that you realize that
perdiste es que Tú date cuenta que
Look, what was I doing to him?
fíjate tú no que yo estaba haciéndole
videos to criticism to miares is that those
vídeos a críticas a miares es que esos
Videos disrespect us. It's that neither
vídeos nos faltan al respeto Es que ni
They haven't even filed any lawsuits
siquiera ninguna demanda han puesto esos
videos no
vídeos no
[Music]
[Música]
The mother started insulting me from her
empezó la madre insultarme desde su
account from a bunch of accounts okay And
cuenta desde un montón de cuentas vale Y
the attack of that thing, I mean, I wasn't there
ya el ataque de lo de o sea yo no estaba
to the attack not only for her but
al ataque ya no solamente por ella sino
because of the environment, the whole environment, no, and I
por el entorno todo el entorno no y yo
I noticed how the whole attack always
notaba como todo el ataque siempre Al
you yourself were in love you were
mismo tú estabas enamorado estabas
I don't know how much disappointed and it was clear
despechado no sé cuánto y claro era
because I already feel bad that this guy is in the
porque ya viplajo que este chico en el
my judgment
juicio mío
I had a call with Miare's mother
tenía una llamada con la madre de miare
in which Miare's mother
en la que la madre de miare
I told him to get ready because I'm going to
le decía que se prepare que voy a
publish we are going to be public some
publicar vamos a ser pública unas
captures of him we are going to destroy the
capturas de él le vamos a destrozar la
family I don't care what comes to me
familia Me da igual lo que venga que me
It doesn't matter if I have children, it doesn't matter to me
da igual que tenga hijos me da igual
knows
sabe
and there I exploded as it is logical and
y ahí yo ya exploté como Es lógico Y
Then I say, give it whatever you want.
entonces ya digo dala para lo que quiera
Here I am and in one of these live shows
Aquí estoy y en uno de estos directos
by dog ​​draw I don't remember how
por sorteo del perro no me acuerdo cómo
It was the move they called me for
fue la movida que me llamaron para
testify about the dog and there no longer
testificar lo del perro y ahí ya no
I can obviously lie
puedo mentir evidentemente
There I have to go with the truth and apart
ahí tengo que ir con la verdad y aparte
I mean, look at what they've done to me or
o sea fíjate tú no lo que me han hecho o
They have tried to do that to me.
me han intentado hacer ello no
Look at you, eh? Look at all the videos.
fíjate tú eh Que fíjate todos los vídeos
What do I do because I have another one
que hago yo porque yo tengo otra
thematic I don't know if you know that it is the
temática no sé si lo sabéis que es la el
content of ladies no and in the
contenido de señoras no y en el
content of Mrs. Rosi and everything is like
contenido de Señora Rosi y todo es como
if it were a miare there no, that is, it is a
si fuera una miare allí no o sea es una
controversial person who sells his entire life
persona polémica que vende toda su vida
and all that stuff and then I'm pink
y todo el rollo ese y luego rosadito yo
I meet her on the street, we are with
me la encuentro por la calle estamos con
the joke doesn't matter to him because you know
el cachondeo le da igual porque sabes
What content do you know is part of the
que contenidos sabes que es parte del
of selling his life You know and I have
del vender su vida Sabes y yo me he
seen with Rosita
visto con Rosita
I don't know if you've seen it, okay, look
no sé si la habéis visto vale mira
Now it's not going to open for me because I have
ahora no se me va a abrir porque tengo
to restart the browser but come on I
que reiniciar el navegador pero vamos yo
I dress in pink in person two or
me visto con rosito en persona dos o
three times and we have both been with
tres veces y hemos estado los dos con
joking around. I mean, I would have been
cachondeo O sea pues yo hubiera estado
well with Dallas and would have had some
bien con Dallas y hubiera tenido cierta
cordiality with miare Although I believed
cordialidad con miare Aunque yo creyera
to Dallas without any problems
a Dallas sin ningún tipo de problema
because it is not a personal issue of mine, it is of
porque no es un tema personal mío es de
they understand me, that is, there was a
ellos me entiende o sea yo hubo una
time
época
until wismichu became boyfriend of this one
hasta que wismichu se hizo novio de esta
girl that I followed on Twitter and
chica que yo me seguía en Twitter y
They sent me to Dallas and Wismichu
ellos a mí con Dallas y con wismichu a
the time I mean I think I'm one of the few
la vez O sea creo que soy de las pocas
people whom the two followed in
personas a las que los dos le seguían en
Twitter at the same time but
Twitter a la vez pero
These people with these people do not
estas personas con estas personas no
They can be whatever you put into it
pueden ser ellos es todo lo que te metas
against the story They have a
en contra del relato Ellos tienen un
story and a goal that is Dallas And for
relato y un objetivo que es Dallas Y por
That's not the case now either with Beijing.
eso ahora tampoco por eso con Beijing
you also know, I mean, billion, what is it?
también sabes O sea billín qué es lo que
Billy has done the only thing he has done is
ha hecho Billy lo único que ha hecho es
Beijing and Auron make peace with
Beijing y auron hacer las pases con
Dallas So you know nosy in
Dallas Entonces ya saben entrometido en
their way of wanting to sink the dala
su camino de que quieren hundir al dala
and anyone who gets in the way
y todo el que se intrometa en el camino
They have the power to sink Dallas
de hundir a Dallas se la tienen
life sentence And look at you, don't you think that
sentencia de por vida Y fíjate tú no que
When a few months ago Auron came out to
cuando hace unos meses auron sale a
Say no. Well, that's it, like in michu.
decir no Bueno ya está ya como en michu
your fixed and now wismichu to the
tu arreglado y ahora wismichu a la
minimal have been shoving Beijing another
mínima han estado funando a Beijing otra
maybe wismichu is there again
vez wismichu está ahí por medio otra vez
Yes, I knew he had gone, I don't know what
sí sabía que había ido no sé en qué
specific trials but I know that in
juicios en específico pero sé que en
Some have had to participate as
alguno ha tenido que participar como
witness and that really today
testigo y que realmente a día de hoy
remains a strong advocate of yours yes
sigue siendo un fuerte defensor tuyo sí
We have our pluses and minuses, but
tenemos nuestras más nuestros menos pero
That is something that disappointed me
a mí eso es algo que a mí me decepcionó
a little bit that will be lost a little bit that
un poco que se perderá un poco esa
relationship because I I must I must
relación porque yo yo debo yo debo
recognize that I really like Javi
reconocer que a mi Javi me Mola mucho lo
what are you doing
que hace
We have our ups and downs
tenemos nuestros más y nuestros menos
but they don't cross the lines, that is
pero no traspasan las líneas o sea
our pluses in our minuses are
nuestros más en nuestros menos son
There are no more disagreements for me
desacuerdos no hay más para mí
Personally I don't know what he's going to say
personalmente No sé lo que él va a decir
now but for me personally
ahora pero para mí personalmente
It weighs even more today
pesa más todavía a día de hoy
There is nothing that makes me think so
no hay nada que me haga pensar lo
contrary the good than the bad because
contrario lo bueno que lo malo porque a
I personally disagree on the subject
mí los desacuerdos en tema personalmente
I understand that maybe he can
Yo entiendo que a lo mejor a él le puede
bother any more of my opinion
molestar más alguna opinión mía
contrary because in the end the issue is
contraria porque al final el tema es de
He is not mine, the subject is his.
él no es mío el tema es de él
disagreement Imagine that he argues with
desacuerdo Imagínate que él se pelea con
Vegeta and I are against Dallas.
Vegeta y yo opino en contra del Dallas
Well maybe it might bother you because
Pues a lo mejor le puede molestar porque
is more yours not mine then to me
esté más suyo no mío entonces a mí me
It may not matter and he doesn't, but in the end
puede dar igual y él no pero al final
I think he also understands that it is my
creo que él también entiende que es mi
content is fine, I can't do it either
contenido vale que tampoco me puedo
be contradicting understands But he
estar contradiciendo entiende Pero él
You know that I'm there for what's important
sabe que para lo importante estoy ahí
I know that he then just these things And
sé que él luego recién estas cosas Y
That might give you good feedback.
puede que eso te comentarios buenos
bad in the end does its job no me no
malos al final hace su trabajo no me no
It bothers me but what I have seen
me molesta pero lo que sí que he visto
is that he is a person who will have committed
es que es una persona que habrá cometido
his failures like everyone else there will be
sus fallos como todos se habrá
wrong in the past But it has been
equivocado en el pasado Pero ha sido
rectify and I think it is something that there is
rectificar y creo que es algo que hay
that value it the same as you, for example
que valorarlo igual que tú por ejemplo
you may have made a mistake and you go out and
te puedes haber equivocado y sales y
You say Ok I was wrong about this
dices Ok me he equivocado de esto
I recently saw a video in which
recientemente veía un vídeo en el que
I said I was wrong about these
decía me he equivocado con estas
people I say it is okay and I think that
personas lo digo no pasa nada Y creo que
That also does a lot and says a lot about
eso también hace mucho y dice mucho de
you and him when he exposed himself to doing the Game
ti y él cuando se expuso hacer el Game
over of minars was put on a piece of land
over de minares se puso en un terreno
swampy because it was going to have already
pantanoso porque iba a tener ya en
against those who had been their allies
contra a quienes habían sido sus aliados
Therefore they could have taken [ __ ] from him or
Por ende le podían haber sacado o
whatever it was
lo que fuese
You can always get a lot of people out of me
de mí se puede sacar siempre mucha gente
which also says is something that I
que dice además es una cosa que me
It seems like a very big joke they say
parece una payasada muy grande que dicen
that Dallas and I don't fight because
que Dallas y yo no nos peleamos porque
we have a lot of [ __ ] about each other
tenemos mucha el uno del otro
but what the hell are we going to have one of the
pero qué vamos a tener uno del
other
otro
what the hell are we going to get from each other?
qué vamos a tener el uno del otro
First of all, neither of us are
en primer lugar ninguno de los dos somos
[Music]
[Música]
murderers that we have corpses In the
asesinos que tengamos cadáveres En el
freezer, that is, like, hey, what if we
congelador o sea en plan Oye que si nos
We fight, we can throw [ __ ] at each other
peleamos nos podemos tirar el uno
to the other Well yes Probably yes then
al otro Pues sí Probablemente sí pues
I'll probably take it and throw it in his face
probablemente yo cojo y le echo en cara
I don't know what And he to me I don't know how much and we
no sé qué Y él a mí no sé cuánto y nos
we say ugly things and what happens when
decimos cosas feas y lo que pasa cuando
people fight but none of them
la gente se pelea pero ninguno de los
We both have something from each other that will go to you
dos tenemos del otro algo que te vaya a
throw internet or something funable or
echar internet o que sea algo funable o
something like that Because we are not
algo por el estilo Porque no somos
criminals
criminales
Let's see what secrets we know each other
que a ver que sabemos secretos el uno
of the other Well of course like friends
del otro Bueno claro de como los amigos
No, I mean, but I think that when I
no O sea pero yo creo que yo cuando me
I fight with people no I'm not going to take that out
peleo con la gente no no voy a sacar que
I'll tell you an intimate detail about something
te digo yo una intimidad de algo
familiar
familiar
loving gossip I don't know Or is that it?
amoroso cotilleos Yo que sé no O sea eso
I have told something that someone told me
yo si he contado algo que alguien me
have told in private in some
haya contado en privado en alguna
occasion is worth as it could be for example
ocasión vale como pudo ser por ejemplo
with the other group is because they have
con el otro grupo es porque me han
attacked me first Or they have
atacaba a mí primero O lo han hecho
With me you understand me first but it's that
conmigo primero me entiendes pero es que
Even if we fought, what are we going to do?
aunque nos peleáramos es que que vamos a
have one of the other that can sink us
tener uno del otro que nos pueda hundir
the race to this [ __ ] what is it
la carrera a esta qué es lo que es
what can be taken from Dallas to this
lo que se puede sacar de Dallas a esta
[ __ ] height of life what is it
altura de la vida ya qué es lo que
I'm going to take it out of the dala if they called it
voy a sacar del dala si lo han llamado
all the crimes that exist
todos los crímenes que existen
If they have called him for all the crimes
si lo han llamado de todos los crímenes
that they all exist with Dallas what they have
que existen todos con Dallas lo que han
the entire penal code has been made
hecho ha sido todo el código penal
review it and accuse him of everything
repasarlo Y acusarlo de todos de todos
everyone's crimes are worth it. So what?
los delitos de todos vale O sea qué
Let's go for it. Let's throw each other in the face now.
vamos a qué Vamos a echarnos en cara ya
who also tried saying that
que también lo intentaron diciendo que
this style has arrived and then by
haya llegado este estilo y luego por
the other side was not guaranteed that you
otro lado no se garantizaba que tú
you were going to be with him because you could
fueras a estar con él porque podrías
have a grudge against him. Then I think that's it.
tenerle rencor Entonces yo creo que eso
It was an act of bravery for me, that's why
fue un acto de valentía por eso para mí
That video is a turning point for me.
es un punto de inflexión ese vídeo a mí
I loved it, it went like that day, let's go
me encantó se fue como ese día fue vamos
Let's put on the hot cinema to see what to see
a poner los hot Cinema a ver que a ver
what they tell each other and then from there
qué se cuentan y luego a partir de ahí
see that you started to have a good one
ver que empezaste a tener una buena
relationship I don't know if you ever got to be very
relación no sé si llegasteis a ser muy
friends or at least within what is in
amigos o al menos dentro de lo que es en
the video and on YouTube it seemed like you were
el vídeo y en YouTube parecía que erais
very good friends
muy buen amigos
he for a good while I did it
él durante una buena temporada yo lo
I considered my best friend
consideré mejor amigo
This is very salty, no
esto es muy sal no
eye eye eh
ojo ojo eh
We talk every day for many hours a day
Hablamos todos los días muchas horas al
exaggerated day, same as every day we talk 5
día exagerado igual cada día hablamos 5
hours according to these people Dalas to which
horas según esta gente Dalas al que
you've never seen has more secrets than
nunca has visto tiene más secretos que
my will and his mother with whom you have
mi haré y su madre con las que has
been in your house that you have never been
estado en su casa que nunca te han
been able to take out
podido sacar
and being less intelligent than now
y siendo menos inteligente que ahora
but apart from that it is not what it is
pero que aparte es que no que es lo que
Yes, let's see, I don't know the truth, no, I never
que sí a ver no sé la verdad no nunca me
I've started thinking about it because I don't think about
ha dado por pensarlo porque no pienso en
those things when I'm okay with it
esas cosas cuando estoy bien con la
people okay but yes, well surely
gente vale pero pues sí pues seguramente
yes yes you put on a pig and you
si si tú te pones en plan cerdo y te
you start wanting to get secrets out because today
pones a querer sacar secretos pues hoy a
the best there is something that can be
lo mejor hay alguna cosa que puede ser
ugly as gossip is worth either to humiliate or
fea como cotilleo vale o para humillar o
something but let's go
algo pero vamos
nothing there is nothing that any of the
nada no hay nada a lo que ninguno de los
two of us should not be afraid of him
dos no estuviéramos que tener miedo el
one to the other or else
uno al otro o sea si no
we fight. I mean, if we don't fight, let's see.
nos pelea O sea si no nos peleamos a ver
We have argued many times and we have
hemos discutido muchas veces no Y hemos
been without speaking much many times
estado sin hablar mucho muchas veces
sometimes I don't eat any relationship
algunas veces no como Cualquier relación
not as friends but so that we have
de amigos no pero para que tengamos
fear or what happens is that we I
miedo o sea lo que pasa que nosotros yo
I think we are people first.
creo que somos personas primero que nos
we respect that we have certain
respetamos que nos tenemos cierto
respect each other and second that we
respeto el uno al otro y segundo que nos
we have crossed any line one
hemos traspasado ninguna línea el uno
with the other so that it reaches
con el otro como para que llegue a
bleeding term is valid, meaning it is a
término sangrantes vale o sea que es una
tremendous joke to think something like that but
payasada tremenda pensar algo así pero
Well, we've left it as a best friend.
bueno ojo lo hemos dejado en mejor amigo
best friend
mejor amigo
or more I don't know and for me he was my best
o más no sé y para mí él era mi mejor
friend for a long time or more
amigo durante una larga durante o más
five hours no five hours well let's see
cinco horas no cinco horas bueno a ver
It also has a lot to do with it no longer
también tiene mucho que ver ya no
just that we connect very well in
solamente que conectemos muy bien en
many things no And that we have many
muchas cosas no Y que tengamos muchas
ways of thinking but also has
maneras de pensar sino también tiene
much to see undoubtedly that we
mucho que ver indiscutiblemente que nos
we dedicate ourselves to the same thing and on top of that more or
dedicamos a lo mismo y encima más o
less the same terms to the same
menos los mismos términos a los mismos
In the same terms we dedicate ourselves to
en los mismos términos nos dedicamos a
the same more or less and in the same
lo mismo más o menos y en los mismos
terms that also influences a lot no
términos eso también influye mucho no
Hey Javi, what do you think about this? Hey, come on.
Oye Javi qué piensas de esto Oye dala
Look at this, hey Javi, you're fed up with
mira esto Oye Javi tú estás ardida de
This Javi knows things like that. Hey, give it to me.
esto Javi sabe cosas así Oye dala me
you can give this information things like that
puedes dar esta información cosas así
two years, look at a person who
dos años fíjate una persona que le
I actually reported the threats that
denuncié de hecho por las amenazas que
made me and things like that like Yes yes this is
me hizo y cosas así cómo Sí sí esto es
public Yes yes it is public this does not matter to me
público Sí sí es público esto no me
I had found out you got it
había enterado yo lo llegaste a
reported because he said very things
denunciado porque él dijo cosas muy
barbarigas saying that he wanted to see me
barbarigas diciendo que me quería ver
dead in a ditch and a pile of
muerto en una cuneta y un montón de
things like this how this scenario occurs Well
cosas así cómo se da este escenario Pues
really when he changed at the beginning
realmente cuando él cambió al principio
We didn't start being friends, not even close.
no empezamos a ser amigos ni mucho menos
also many people thought he did it
también mucha gente pensó que lo hizo
because I had announced for nothing
porque yo había anunciado para nada yo
I'll just take the complaint off him and
simplemente le quitaré la denuncia y lo
The only thing that gave me change was what I have
único que me dio cambio fue lo que me ha
cost me to put it
costado a mí ponerla
In fact I don't know if that's called
De hecho yo no sé si eso se llama
complaint as such we were recently
denuncia como tal hace poco estuvimos
talking about this topic
hablando de este tema
[Music]
[Música]
I don't remember it's been a long time
es que no me acuerdo hace mucho tiempo
four years ago no or five years ago no
hace cuatro años no o cinco no hace
four more than four years ago
cuatro más de cuatro años hace
First of all, the game over was
en primer lugar que el game over fue
long before it came to me
mucho antes de que me llegara a mí la es
that I did not receive a complaint, I do not
que no me llegó una denuncia a mí no me
a complaint came to me and what I
llegó una denuncia a mí ya lo que yo
I made with him was a ballot of
hice con él fue una papeleta de
conciliation that is called that is like a
conciliación que se llama que es como un
procedure let's say not a thing that
procedimiento digamos no una cosa que
must be done before they transmit the
hay que hacer antes de que transmitan la
complaint to be processed is valid before you
denuncia a trámite vale antes de que te
admit this type of complaints for processing
admitan este tipo de denuncias a trámite
It's not like the civilians who admit it to you
no es como los civiles que te lo admiten
all directly but before
todo directamente no sino que antes de
that they admit this complaint to you
que te admitan este esta denuncia de
There is a procedure like a process that
trámite hay como un procedimiento que
It has to be a conciliation not
tiene que ser una conciliación no
so what we did was
entonces lo que nosotros hicimos fue
Well, directly when it arrived to me
Pues que directamente cuando ya me llegó
At first I was not going to accept that.
eso yo al principio no lo iba a aceptar
In fact I remember one email exchange and
de hecho me acuerdo uno cruce de email y
of comments and calls with him in
de comentarios y de llamadas con él en
the ones I went to, stubborn as a
las que yo iba que encabezonado como un
donkey is worth the game over of miare was
burro vale el Game over de miare fue
long before I did
mucho antes de hecho yo
In the Game Over of my air I did not have
en el Game over de mi aire yo no tenía
I had no idea that this was going to be raised or
ni idea de que eso se iba a plantear ni
nothing like that I think it was like
nada por el estilo creo que fue como
March two or three months after I
marzo a los dos o tres meses de que me
conciliation came not then when
llegó la conciliación no Entonces cuando
I read what the complaint is that he
yo Leí lo que es la denuncia que él
I raised no and
planteaba no y
What he proposed to me was
lo que él me propuso fue
simply
simplemente
fix it or in other words apologize for
arreglarlo o sea en plan disculparme por
the things that were wrong he didn't ask me for
las cosas que estaban mal no me pedía
nothing extra that was
nada extra que fuera
What do I tell you?
que te digo yo
He didn't ask me to say anything extra.
no me pedía nada extra que dijera
nothing that was his favor of the stick
ninguna cosa que fuera su favor del palo
He agrees with you on this even if I don't agree with you.
Dale la razón en esto aunque no la tenga
not what was the thing about the ditch, what was
no lo que fue lo de la cuneta lo de
abuser the things I said to him okay And
maltratador las cosas que le dije vale Y
that I would cover the expense that I had
que cubriera yo el gasto que había
had to put it okay or so it was a thing
tenido ponerla vale o sea fue una cosa
that the truth
que la verdad
that then there are many people who today
que luego hay mucha gente que a día de
Today he says, Oh, it's that with Wismichu
hoy Dice Ay es que con lo de wismichu
with the thing about
con lo de
My girlfriend has won And then how
mi chula ha ganado Y entonces como
wismichula has won. Well, you too.
wismichula ha ganado Pues tú también lo
You would have won if it had been forward
Hubieras ganado si hubiera sido palante
first of all
en primer lugar
say that wismichula has won the
decir que wismichula ha ganado la
report to Dallas and then I could
denuncia a Dallas y entonces yo podía
looking ahead seems like an outrage to me
verse adelante me parece una barbaridad
and a lot of money is worth all the topics here
y una burrada vale aquí todos los temas
It's not about having the biggest dick or having
no es tener la más gorda o tener
the longest [ __ ] and let's see who is bigger
la más larga y a ver quién es más
man no And who is more stubborn?
hombre no Y quién más cabezón vale
If I already know when that comes to me,
si yo ya sé cuando a mí me llega eso que
The things I have said are
las cosas que yo he dicho son
nonsense for what the [ __ ] for what the [ __ ]
barbaridades para qué para qué
I'm going to spend some money
me voy a gastar un dinero
in defending one thing and being three or
en defender una cosa y estar tres o
four or five years of litigation
cuatro o cinco años de pleito
when I myself know that I am not right
cuando yo mismo sé que no tengo la razón
118 members missing and 2000 thumbs up
faltan 118 miembros y 2000 pulgar hacia
up for a kiss Thank you very much
arriba para beso Muchísimas gracias
If I'm watching it now, it comes to me
si yo estoy viendo ya que a mí me llega
this and he is proposing something to me that
esto y me está proponiendo una cosa que
It is completely logical simply
es completamente lógica simplemente
remove the defamatory videos and I ask you
retira los vídeos difamatorios y le pido
sorry that it was going to be that way
perdón que además lo iba a ser
Equally heartfelt and covers the cat
Igualmente de corazón y cubre el gato
of the lawyer because obviously that
del abogado porque evidentemente eso
He has some expenses and he is not going to pay them.
tiene unos gastos no y no los va a pagar
Okay, it seems logical to me, but if it is
bueno vale me parece lógico pero si es
that also the people of you know that in
que además la gente de you know que en
At that time I didn't earn much.
aquel entonces yo no ganábamos poquito
I didn't have any money back then and the
dinero yo en aquel entonces no y la
people you know each put one
gente de you know pusieron cada uno uno
and we made the money and then I
y hicimos el dinero y encima luego yo
I made another video with which he has a
hice otro vídeo con el que tiene un
million and a half visits that that can
millón y medio de visita que eso pueda
having quietly generated the money
haber generado tranquilamente el dinero
what it cost me or what it cost us
que me costó o que nos costó
That is to say, it is absurd, it is a
o sea es que es absurdo es una
stupidity to be stubborn about something
gilipollez encabezonarte en una cosa
when you yourself know that you don't have the
cuando tú mismo sabes que no tienes la
I'm right, there are other times when
razón a mí hay otras ocasiones en las
that they have sued me that I believe that the
que me han demandado que yo creo que la
people what they have believed by suing me
gente lo que se ha creído demandándome
It's that I was going to tell myself that I wasn't going anymore.
Es que yo me iba a chantar que ya no iba
to discuss their issues that I was going to get off
a tratar sus temas que yo me iba a bajar
the pants that were going to reach a
el pantalón que iba a llegar a un
agreement that was going to try an agreement not
acuerdo que iba a intentar un acuerdo no
Why not in those other cases I know that
porque no en esas otras casos Yo sé que
I am right and I know I will win and
tengo la razón y sé que lo voy a ganar y
If I don't win it in the first instance
si no lo gano en una primera instancia
I will win it the second time but I know that
lo ganaré la segunda pero yo sé que
until the end that I will win it
hasta el final que lo voy a ganar yo
Okay, and in this Dallas thing it's not the same.
vale Y en esto de Dallas no es lo mismo
because I had already taken out the first one
porque yo primero ya había sacado el
Nobel already knew that I already knew what
Nobel ya sabía que yo ya sabía lo que
there was worth And secondly it was
había vale Y en segundo lugar es que era
an outrage
una barbaridad
It was an outrage what I told him
es que era una barbaridad lo que yo le
had told this man
había dicho a este hombre
okay so when I hear myself in
vale o sea que yo cuando me escucho en
those videos
esos vídeos
It's an outrage. How the hell had they done me?
es una barbaridad Cómo me habían
big head but it is more expensive yes
cabezona pero si es que es más caro si
It is more expensive if you fight it.
es que es más caro si es que pelearlo
having to go to Barcelona to testify
tener que ir a Barcelona a declarar
when they admit her to trial if so
cuando la admitan a juicio si lo
appeal is filed and dismissed.
archivan recurrirlo sobreseído abrirlo
in the procedure at the end you spend
en el procedimiento al final te gastas
a lot more
mucho más
Why come to that if we are in agreement?
para qué llegar a eso si estamos de
agreed to fix it
acuerdo en arreglarlo
There really are people who are very
de verdad que hay gente que es muy
stubborn there are people who are very stubborn
cabezona hay gente que es muy cabezona
There is very Although she is very obsessed with it
hay muy Aunque está muy obsesionada el
that is not but
que sea no pero
if it's going to cost me more money to continue
si me va a costar más dinero seguir
forward
adelante
for what? So that publicly of yes that
para qué Para que públicamente de sí que
I have beaten him as he has done
le he ganado yo como ha hecho el
wismichu it's not that I have won everything
wismichu no es que yo he ganado todo lo
What I said about Dallas is true. Not everything.
que he dicho de Dallas es verdad No todo
What you said about Dallas is true.
lo que ha dicho de Dallas tú es verdad
no what happened to you is that you
no lo que pasó con ustedes es que tú
You said that you believed those slanders
dijiste que tú creías esas calumnias
about those accusations about Dallas and
sobre esas acusaciones sobre Dallas y
that the two of you had a dispute in the
que los dos teníais una contienda en el
time that then was the spirit of
tiempo que entonces pues era ánimo de
offend or in any way in any way
ofender o sea para nada en ningún
moment of Wismichu's sentence
momento de la sentencia de wismichu
suppose that what wismichu said was
supone que lo que dijera wismichu fuera
real worth it or so what for? Or so I'm going to
real vale o sea para qué O sea me voy a
spend three times as much to be able to say
gastar el triple para poder decir
publicly that I have won when neither I
públicamente que he ganado cuando ni yo
even when I don't even agree with myself
mismo cuando ni yo mismo me doy la razón
It's absurd to fight that.
es que es absurdo pelear eso
It's absurd to fight that but I know that
es absurdo pelear eso pero si yo sé que
I'm bad in those videos Of course
estoy mal en esos vídeos Pues claro que
yes how do we fix that I think it is
sí cómo lo arreglamos esa Yo creo que es
the attitude
la actitud
but apart from that, imagine me in a
pero es que aparte Imagínate yo en un
judged wanting to defend a position
juzgado queriendo defender una postura
in which I myself do not believe I have the
en la que ni yo mismo creo que tengo la
reason
razón
Javi doesn't even say thank you, maybe you come
ni gracias te dice Javi quizás si vienes
Here to put [ __ ] on you. A lot of that.
aquí a meter te esa Muchísimas
thanks Oh, it's that Dallas hasn't given you
gracias Ay es que Dallas no te ha dado
not even funny but it was just said here
ni la gracia pero se acaba de decir aquí
that much of people's opinion
que gran parte de la opinión de la gente
changed thanks to me My son if you
cambió gracias a mí Hijo mío si te la
just said what videos you're watching
acaba de decir qué vídeos estás viendo
But if we go, thank me 8,000 times.
pero si vamos me da las gracias 8.000
times in a video and I don't even want to be given
veces en un vídeo y ni quiero que me den
thanks for something that turned out like this
las gracias por una cosa que salió así
because it had to come out that way it was natural and
porque tuvo que salir así fue natural y
without expecting anything in return is worth it
sin esperar nada a cambio vale
I remember now, that's right, I remember now.
ya me acuerdo cierto es ya me acuerdo
now I remember and at the beginning
ahora me acordado y al principio
We talked a lot but it was precisely to
hablábamos mucho pero fue justamente a
because then you try to screw him
raíz de que luego intentas en joderle
a few months later he was giving his [ __ ] up
unos meses después a él dando su
marriage and all that that we ended
matrimonio y todo eso Que terminamos
talking a lot at that time because
hablando bastante en ese momento porque
Well I expressed my support because
Bueno yo le expresé mi apoyo porque le
are doing And then it started happening
están haciendo Y entonces se vino dando
We also talked about many topics and such
también hablábamos de muchos temas y tal
We don't just talk, I remember that.
No simplemente hablamos me acuerdo que
Also I said He called me when he passed by
además yo decía Él me llamó cuando pasó
that they attacked my wife and that he
lo de que atacaron a mi mujer y eso él
He called me and
me llamó y
we went little by little as if talking I don't know
fuimos poco a poco como hablando No sé
I don't know how much Javi means that
que no sé cuánto Javi se refiere a que
you didn't thank tesa before
no le diste las gracias a tesa antes de
give it to Tessa, she's already fried
dársela tessa ya está frita de las
My thanks, if I don't do it for Tesa
gracias mía si a tesa no le hago yo
I don't give a damn about any of this jokes
ninguna gracia atesa se la sudo yo
I don't give a damn about that, that's enough.
atesa se la sudo yo ya vale
this roll, let's see
el rollo este a ver
I remember that I told him many things
que me acuerdo que yo le decía muchas
times
veces
but it also ends
pero también se termina
I remember that I told him well
que me acuerdo que yo le decía bueno
well but we are not going to be
bueno pero que nosotros no vamos a ser
friend not one like that eh We
amigo ni una por el estilo eh Nosotros
we have fixed things and cordial But
hemos arreglado las cosas y cordial Pero
You here I there I will follow you
tú Aquí yo allí yo te voy a seguir
criticizing him, I told him, I'm going to
criticando le decía yo yo te voy a
keep giving, I told him.
seguir dando eh le decía yo
we talked about many topics in general
hablamos de muchos temas en general
We always have an opinion
siempre pues tenemos una opinión
quite similar in 99% of things and
bastante parecida en el 99% de cosas y
Well, it literally ended up being my
pues literalmente terminó siendo mi
best friend without the slightest exaggeration
mejor amigo sin exagerar más mínimo
then the relationship was established
luego la relación se estableció
for several reasons
por varias varios
encounters we had in some
encontronazos que tuvimos en algunos
themes maybe and I think what ended
temas tal vez y creo que lo que terminó
to bury her maybe it was that he
de sepultarla a lo mejor fue que él
began to be friends with
empezó a ser amigo de
some youtubers specifically the same
unos youtubers específicamente al igual
which to me seems like a lot of fakes
que a mí me parece unos falsos de mucho
careful But he kind of focused
cuidado Pero él como que se centró
a lot in defending them And this I did not know
muchísimo en defenderles Y esto no sabía
I didn't know this
esto no sabía esto
I imagined but I didn't know it bothered me
me imaginaba pero no sabía me molestó de
true because it was like you don't know From
verdad porque era como no conoces De
Nothing Just Breadcrumbs are imitating
nada Solo Migajas de pan están imitando
one here there but only to have you
una si aquí allá pero solo para tenerte
on your side only and this is what I
de su lado únicamente y a mí esto me
It was obviously annoying and that's where we lost the
molestó evidentemente Y ahí perdimos el
almost complete contact and now good
contacto por completo casi y ahora bueno
we have a good relationship we talk about
tenemos una relación bien hablamos de
from time to time they actually tried the
vez en cuando de hecho intentaron el
My dog's judgment to say that it was my
juicio de mi perro decir que era mi
friend to try to break up his
amigo para intentar desbaratar su
testimony
testimonio
and I said we weren't really friends
y yo dije realmente no éramos amigos
you know and I made a comment I said and this
sabes y hice un comentario dije y esto
He could say it too And then he
lo podría decir él también Y entonces el
your lawyer when I said that he told me
abogado suyo cuando yo dije que me dijo
I just said that he was going to say
acabo de decir que él iba a decir
It's also because they are in cahoots
también es porque están compinchados
is that the judgment of the dog the dala
es que el juicio del perro el dala
I should be publishing chapter strata
debería ir publicando estratos capítulo
They asked me about the dog trial
del juicio del perro a mí me preguntaron
The same is true that they tried
lo mismo sí que es verdad que intentaron
break that up and it's like, let's see friends, I
desbaratar eso y es como a ver amigos yo
I haven't seen him in person, friends, well
no lo he visto en persona amigos bueno a
See, I call everyone a friend many times.
ver yo llamo amigo a todos Muchas veces
friend you can you can use the
amigo tú puedes tú puedes utilizar la
word friend to refer to you with which
palabra amigo para referirte con la que
They have a good friendship, that is, I have many
tienen buena amistad o sea yo muchas
times Well I called Juan Guarnizo
veces Pues he llamado a Juan guarnizo
friend to Ari friend well in fact Ari
amigo a Ari amiga bueno que de hecho Ari
He doesn't call me Friend anymore because he doesn't talk to me.
me llama Amigo ya no porque no me habla
but when Arico spoke to me at the same time
pero cuando me hablaba arico a la vez
that he sent me a WhatsApp or whatever
que me mandaba un WhatsApp o lo que sea
friend I don't know what friend I don't know how much you know
amigo no sé qué amigo no sé cuánto sabes
are terms but in reality the
son términos pero en realidad el
meaning of the word friend for me
significado de la palabra amigo para mí
It is much greater for me a complicity
es mucho mayor para mí una complicidad
a person who only with a look
una persona que solamente con la mirada
you understand me you understand me there are many
te entiende me entiendes son muchas
things no but well yes we have been friends
cosas no pero bueno sí hemos sido amigos
That is, even though we don't know each other in
o sea Aunque no nos conozcamos en
person we have been friends but
persona hemos sido amigos pero
at the time when I started in the
en la época en la que yo empiezo en la
time when I am called to be
época en la que a mí me llaman para ser
witness of this I am not a friend I have been more
testigo de esto no soy amigo he sido más
friends of other people than of him
amigos de la otra gente que de él de
fact that has not even existed
hecho no que ha existido incluso
in-person relationship
relación en persona
and outside it seems that I don't have any
y fuera parece que yo no tengo ningún
kind of I don't have any kind of
tipo de yo no tengo ningún tipo de
interest in someone losing or winning a
interés en que alguien pierda o gane un
trial I mean, I'm not interested in you
juicio O sea a mí no me interesa que tú
You ask me my opinion or I... Well, I...
me preguntas mi opinión o me Pues yo
I want justice to be done you know but
quiero que se haga justicia sabes Pero
That doesn't mean I'm going to
eso no quiere decir que yo vaya a
get involved or participate in that
involucrarme o a participar en que eso
does not happen organically
no suceda orgánicamente
okay, I mean if you ask me my
vale o sea si tú a mí me preguntan mi
opinion man, well I want it to happen
opinión hombre pues yo quiero que pase
what is fair is worth or I would like or I would
lo justo vale o me gustaría o me
I would be happy if the right thing happened but now
alegraría que pasara lo justo pero ahora
as if I have any interest
como que yo tenga algún interés como que
I don't give a damn about what happens to me.
yo quiera que pase a mí me suda la
The truth is that it is not my case, okay, I
la verdad no es mi caso vale Yo me
I'm glad about the good things that happen to you
alegro de las cosas buenas que le pasen
to my colleague just as if they happened to me
a mi colega igual que si me pasarán a mí
Okay, but that's what I come here for.
vale pero es que lo que yo vengo aquí a
testify is I was not even
testificar es yo ni siquiera era
testifying as such was more than anything
testificar como tal era más que nada
to deliver some conversations and some
para entregar unas conversaciones y unos
audios
audios
and a plan does not do it either because
y un plan de no lo hace también porque
It's the [ __ ] truth, you know, I mean, it's that already
es la verdad sabes o sea es que ya
We are not friends before we saw it now
no somos amigos antes lo vimos que ahora
himself has no interest in him now
mismo tiene ningún interés él ahora
same
mismo
interest to see interest is a word that
interés a ver interés es una palabra que
It has its meaning, I'm interested, I
tiene su significado yo interés yo
I have no interest in a
interés no tengo ninguno en que una
person wins or loses a trial yogurt a
persona gane o pierda un juicio yogur un
kiss okay if you ask me my opinion
beso vale si me preguntan mi opinión
Well, I want justice to be done, but
Pues yo quiero que se haga justicia pero
that justice be truly done. That is, no
que se haga justicia de verdad O sea no
Let's see if it's worth it for you to understand me.
que a ver si para que me entendáis vale
What they were trying to say with that is that
lo que intentaban decir con eso es que
I was going to lie or misrepresent the
yo iba a mentir o iba a tergiversar la
information so that the other would win
información para que el otro ganara
because I was interested let's see one
porque yo tenía interés vamos a ver una
which is what I would like
cosa es lo que a mí me gustaría que
happen or I would like it to happen or I
pasara o me gustaría que pasara o yo
I would consider it to be justice and another
considerara que fuera justicia y otra
It's a thing that I'm going to invent something
cosa es que yo vaya a inventarme algo
to manipulate the trial or outcome
para manipular el juicio o el resultado
of the trial you know in short is that I
del juicio sabes en fin es que me
I would love for Dallas, I don't even have it
encantaría que el Dallas no lo tengo ni
They haven't sent it to me, but I
yo no me lo han mandado ni a mí pero me
I would love for the dala to recover and
encantaría que el dala recuperara y
will react to various parts of the trial
reaccionará a varias partes del juicio
because that was the testimony
porque aquello fue o sea la testifical
you have to see mine, testify mine
mía tenéis que verla la testificar mía
you have to see it that was it that was it
tenéis que verla eso fue eso fue
That was tremendous. It was like a debate.
tremendo eso Fue como un debate
more than it is not his testimony It is that he comes
más que no es su testimonio Es que viene
to present audio conversations of
a presentar audios conversaciones de
Landonia saying that she was going to kill me
landonia diciendo que iba a matar a mi
dog I mean we are not talking about your
perro O sea no estamos hablando de su
testimony since they are audios of her
testimonio ya que son audios de ella
when ideas did not exist for
cuando las ideas no existían para
modify audios that return to others
modificar audios que volviendo a otros
turning points too
puntos también de inflexión
recently that you won the trial
recientemente que has ganado el juicio
precisely Antonia, the mother of Maria de
justamente Antonia la madre de María de
I'm looking at this dog theme today.
miare a día de hoy tema perro esto
I understand that it must have been for you
entiendo que habrá sido para ti en
a certain way after seven years they have
cierto modo después de siete años han
It will have been a relief
sido habrá sido un desahogo una
calm down no How things are today
tranquilidad no Cómo está la cosa a día
today's
de hoy
Let's see if they have thought of it
a ver si se les ha ocurrido
I don't know yet, I should know this week
aún no lo sé debería saberlo esta semana
we should know this week
deberíamos saberlo esta semana
I don't know if the one that comes
no sé si la que viene
The sentence was given on a Friday
Es que la sentencia se dio un viernes a
The best is yet to come, but
lo mejor la que viene pero
These days we have to know if it is
en estos días Tenemos que saber si se
resort
recurra
I sincerely hope they do not resort to it.
Espero que no recurran sinceramente
Well what they are claiming up to now
Bueno lo que están alegando hasta hasta
now as far as I understand
ahora hasta donde tengo entendido
publicly or among friends and others
públicamente o entre sus amigos y demás
What they are claiming is that they still
lo que están alegando es que todavía la
the sentence is not final
condena no es firme
This is what I think they are considering.
es lo que creo que están barajando ellos
or publicly defending but if
o defendiendo públicamente pero si
appealed the judge left it very well
recurriesen el juez lo dejó muy bien
tied and I think that if they appeal the
atado y creo que si recurren la
audience could chase my ex for
audiencia podría perseguir a mi ex por
another crime the judge said no
otro delito más el juez dijo que no
I could judge visceral no Yes, well that
podía juzgar viscería no Sí pues ese
I think it was four years, maybe
creo que eran cuatro años puede ser
up to six years up to six and this is one
hasta seis años hasta seis y este es uno
that it is not his responsibility No, he did not have
que a él no le compete No él no tenía
authority Exactly has no authority
autoridad Exactamente no tiene autoridad
to judge that
para juzgar eso
and I feel that the judge is in a plan of
y yo siento que el juez en plan de por
If you appeal to a hearing, know that
si recurres audiencia que sepas que
you did this I think he did it for
hiciste esto yo pienso que lo hizo por
That's nothing, I really liked the detail
eso nada a mí me gustó mucho el detalle
of the judge that you mention in your video and
del juez que comentas tú en tu vídeo y
I think that I think it's true. And
creo que yo a ver creo que es cierto Y
is that he is prioritizing what you
es que él está priorizando el que tú
you get your dog back something that doesn't stop
recuperes a tu perro algo que no para
that they then say that the judges are not
que luego digan que los jueces no son
animalists and do not understand animals or
animalistas y no entienden de animales o
be the judge the sentence makes it
sea el juez la sentencia la hace de
way to deliver to the dog Looking for
forma que entreguen al perro Mirando por
the dog that the dog does not get lost
el perro que el perro no se pierda
above them going to the
por encima de que ellos vayan a la
jail if that's why he also told them
cárcel si por eso también les ha dicho
If you behave well, we can go.
si vosotros portáis bien Podemos ir
By reducing charges we can make two
rebajando cargos podemos hacer que dos
years and a half are two years and not
años y medio sean dos años y que no
you go
vayáis
No yes Well what happens is that they
No sí Bueno lo que sucede es que ellos
They don't go to jail if they comply with all the
no van a la cárcel si cumplen todas las
sentences like that is in the part
sentencias como que eso está en la parte
of the sentence if you do not comply with that
de la sentencia si os No cumplieran eso
For example, if they did not comply with the fine that
Por ejemplo si no cumplían la multa que
They then put them
les ponen entonces
Do you honestly think they're going to go to the
tú sinceramente crees que van a ir a la
jail
cárcel
that what should happen if I haven't turned back
eso que debería pasar si no me he vuelto
My dog ​​is what he did like this But
de mi perro es lo que ha hecho así Pero
You understand that they are going to return it to you
tú entiendes que te van a devolver
Man, I think you have to be stupid.
hombre creo Hay que ser estúpido
It's that those people coming
Es que viniendo esa gente
that they can invent anything
que se pueden inventar a cualquier cosa
any roll that they in their
cualquier rollo que ellos en su
imagination and in your mind you create that
imaginación y en su mente se crea que le
It's going to turn out well, because they do
va a salir bien eh porque ellos hacen
things and make demands and put things that
cosas y ponen demandas y ponen cosas que
They believe in their imagination, I don't know.
ellos creen en su imaginación yo no sé
if the lawyer to charge you does not
si es que el abogado para cobrarle No lo
I know the truth but there are things that do
sé la verdad pero hay cosas que hacen
that I often do not understand them and
que yo muchas veces no las entiendo y
I say who the hell recommended them that
digo quién les ha recomendado que
do this you would eat you think they are
haga esto te comerías Tú crees que son
capable of eating two and a half years of
capaces de comerse dos años y medio de
jail in exchange for screwing you and not
cárcel a cambio de joderte y que no
have your dog
tengas tu perro
Of course, they wouldn't eat two years of
claro es que no se comerían dos años de
prison for two and a half years Because two years
cárcel dos años y medio Porque dos años
and a half is the sum of the three dry ones
y medio es la suma entre los tres secos
It would be 6 months the father was a year old and
sería 6 meses el padre era un año y
half but then I understand that
medio pero luego yo entiendo que
behaving well and so on, I mean, I don't know what
portándose bien y demás o sea no sé a lo
better go to jail but they would go in
mejor entran en la cárcel pero entrarían
maybe they would take weeks I don't know
a lo mejor entrarían semanas No lo sé la
true or months you see him capable
verdad o meses ustedes lo veis capaces
from heading to moving forward
de encabezado a tirar para adelante
with the consequences that may be thrown
con las consecuencias que sea tira
forward uncle
palante tío
I'm surprised you don't respond quickly.
me sorprende que no responda rápido es
that with these people never
que con esta gente nunca
They have done everything that a person
han hecho de todo es que una persona
Normally he doesn't get involved in these things anymore.
normal ya no se mete en estas cosas
Of course it's the same thing I said with Joan
claro es lo mismo que he dicho con Joan
flat today no because Joan flat Hey I
planas hoy no porque Joan plana Oye yo
Joan Plana is going to appeal today
en plana va a recurrir hoy Joan plana no
I know if you know tomorrow I will bring the lawyer
sé si lo sabéis mañana traeré al abogado
so that we can comment on the sentence today
para que comentemos la sentencia hoy
iban flat has lost another lawsuit that
iban planas ha perdido otra demanda que
put worth even more Absurd than mine
puso vale todavía más Absurda que la mía
yes it fits okay And of course this man doesn't
sí cabe vale Y claro este hombre no
never wants to admit that he didn't have
quiere reconocer nunca que él no tenía
the reason in the argument against us
la razón en la discusión contra nosotros
Okay, and people say, but they're going to appeal.
vale Y dice la gente pero va a recurrir
uncle is going to lose more money because of course
tío va a perder más dinero porque claro
when you resort Apart from the fact that you have
cuando tú recurres Aparte de que te ha
It cost money to file the lawsuit and now it's so
costado dinero poner la demanda Y ya tan
condemned to quilts of the first
condenado a colchas de la primera
instance when you appeal you have to
instancia cuando tú recurres tienes que
spend 50% of what you have
gastarte el 50% de lo que te hayas
spent in the first instance is worth in
gastado en la primera instancia vale en
lawyers and then they condemn you to pay costs
abogados y luego te condenan en costas
once again at even greater costs
otra vez a más costas todavía
That is to say, there is going to be a big mess
o sea se va a hacer una pelotera de
pasta in pasta among all the people who
pasta en pasta entre toda la gente que
has demanded that there will be a big fuss
ha demandado se va a hacer una pelotera
because he's not going to win any, okay? And
porque no va a ganar ninguna vale Y
Cautious says: Well, but that's normal.
cauto dice Bueno pero es que lo normal
It would be that I don't know what this says is that it
sería que no sé qué dice esto es que lo
It would be normal for a person not to have
normal sería que una persona no hubiera
At this point it is normal with people
llegado a este punto lo normal con gente
how is this that she would have continued
como esta es que ella hubiera seguido
succeeding on the internet and making their
triunfando en internet y haciendo sus
movies and making their projects in
películas y haciendo sus proyectos en
the internet and its brands and its things and not
internet y sus marcas y sus cosas y no
would have been trying and focusing
hubiera estado intentando y enfocándose
the whole family to sink the ex-boyfriend who
toda la familia en hundir al exnovio que
It's been 7 years now, I don't know if it's been
han pasado Ya pues no sé si 7 años de
that they left it, do you understand me then?
que lo dejaron me entiende entonces
part of the base of that not that if they were
parte de la base de esa no que si fueran
normal ones would not have arrived and not
normales no hubieran llegado y no
they would still be putting it today
estarían poniendo todavía a día de hoy
They are still filing lawsuits today.
están poniendo demandas eh todavía a día
Today we think about what demands to make and
de hoy se piensan demandas que poner y
things to put that already sound in your mind
cosas que poner que en su mente ya suena
well that's it
bien eso
By now I would have said today
a estas alturas ya habría dicho hoy
let's talk let's go
vamos a hablar vamos
to leave it at this point already Hey let's go
a dejarlo a estas alturas ya Oye vamos a
leave each other alone, let's each do it
dejarnos en paz vamos a hacer cada uno
our life that you hate me it doesn't matter
nuestra vida que me odies da igual es
as for you not for me but for you
como por tú no por mí sino por tu
mental health you say let's leave it here
sanidad mental dices vamos a dejar aquí
[Music]
[Música]
Well, I've already known for a decade.
Bueno ya he hecho una década que conocía
This lady
esta señora
It's hard a decade of obsession And still
es duro una década de obsesión Y todavía
you still have it
aún la tienes
but he doesn't have it and he continues. That is, if he is there
pero no la tiene y sigue O sea si está
You realize that if you are putting
Tú date cuenta que si estás poniendo
demands now
demandas ahora
If you are filing lawsuits now, these
si está poniendo demandas ahora Estos
These are procedures that can take 8
son procedimientos que pueden tardar 8
years
años
That is, if they are filing a lawsuit, now I
O sea si están poniendo demanda Ahora yo
I don't know if it's because there's something to it
no sé si será por tener algo a que la
grab something that I don't know the truth no
agarre algo que la No lo sé la verdad no
I know the truth is that he saw it through me
lo sé la verdad es que se lo vio por mí
I wanted to ask you because there is one
yo te quería preguntar porque hay una
something that I personally have my theory about
cosa que en lo personal tengo mi teoría
about Why my area is the way it is
acerca de Por qué mi área es como es
I also have friends in common with my
tengo además amigos en común con mi
areco
areco
This would be another extract, this would be
esto ya sería otro extracto esto sería
another extract no O is already the part
otro extracto no O sea ya la parte
with me would have ended family or there is
conmigo habría terminado familia o hay
Anything else
algo más
bread my part would have ended there
pan la parte mía habría terminado hay
something more family
algo más familia
the part I ask again the part of mine
la parte vuelvo a preguntar la parte mía
would have ended or is there something else
habría terminado o hay algo más
Okay
vale
so far so good
hasta aquí vale
You have cameos throughout the podcast
tienes cameos en todo el podcast
go to 3 4 10
ve al 3 4 10
but at 3410 real
pero al 3410 real
Let's see, the 3 4 10 has already finished, is it real?
a ver ya ha terminado el 3 4 10 es real
which is practically an increase. That is, yes
que es una subida prácticamente O sea si
you put 60% of my video 60% of my video
pones un 60% de mi vídeo 60% de mi vídeo
and you are 30%
y tú eres un 30%
you know then there is some channel of
sabes Entonces el Hay algún canal de
particular gossip that you see or that
salseo en particular que tú veas o que
you like what he does
te guste lo que hace
Yes, there are several.
Sí hay varios
Javi's main example is
de Javi está por ejemplo principal
eye eye Thank you very handsome Thank you very much
ojo ojo Gracias guapísimo Muchas gracias
there are several
hay varios
Javi's is fine For example
de Javi está bien Por ejemplo
main is very dead before I was
principal está muy muerto antes Estaba
very dead we have managed to renew it
muy muerto lo hemos conseguido renovar
Hey, we've managed to renew it, yes it is.
eh lo hemos conseguido renovar sí que es
It's true that it costs me a little more because
verdad que me cuesta un poco más porque
you can't do a thousand things, okay or you do
no puedes hacer mil cosas vale o haces
one or makes 5 but of course when you have
una o hace 5 pero claro cuando tienes
four channels five channels And you are
cuatro canales cinco canales Y estás
trying to get everyone active Well
intentando que todos estén activos Pues
someday There is something that will not open up to me now
algún día Hay que no se me abre ahora
Then I'll open it someday, I was going to show you
luego lo abro algún día os iba a enseñar
more or less the visits that no longer exist
más o menos las visitas que ya no hay
video that goes below 40-30,000 and there are
vídeo que baje de las 40-30.000 y hay
times that we spend 50 or 60 minutes
veces que se nos van para el 50 60 lo
whether it was super dead when
que sea si estuvo súper muerto cuando
we were only uploading deals
estábamos subiendo solamente tratos
edited was super dead already
editados estaba súper muerto ya de
Last time we barely reached 10,000
última casi no llegábamos ni a 10.000
views on videos
visitas en los vídeos
Come on, we've talked about that here a thousand times.
vamos eso lo hemos hablado aquí mil
times I was super dead because
veces estaba súper muerto porque
we were focused on other things
estábamos centrados en otras cosas
I was focused on the live shows that were
estaba centrado en los directos que era
What gives me the most money was and is today
lo que más dinero me da era y es a día
today what gives me the most money and above all
de hoy lo que más dinero me da y sobre
I'll tell you everything about the telesalseo that the
todo la te lo diré el telesalseo que el
tele salseo the cpm is incredible and
tele salseo el cpm es increíble y
then you can't be making videos
entonces no puedes estar haciendo vídeos
direct recordings telesalseo thousand
grabados directos telesalseo mil
news is fine but there with the newscast
noticias vale pero ahí con el noticiero
that there are many people who say you have
que hay mucha gente que dice te has
copied Uncle Sur let's see
copiado el tío Sur a ver
With all due respect, I really like the
con todo respeto Me gusta mucho los
newscasts of the uncle south and has part of
noticieros del tío sur y tiene parte de
its format but I haven't copied the guy
su formato pero no me he copiado el tío
Shure Uncle South makes the news
Shure el tío Sur hace los noticieros
but they already existed before, okay or
pero ya lo ya existían de antes vale o
whether it is what the candres channel does is like this
sea lo hace el canal de candres es así
the Cannes drama channel
el canal de candres drama
The Magician RG or rather I don't even know how many
El Mago RG o sea no sé ni Cuántos
channels I can mention to you that are like this
canales te puedo mencionar que sean así
Ok, but with all due respect to
vale Pero bueno que con todo respeto al
Uncle Sur, I'm glad things are going very well for you.
tío Sur que me alegro que le vaya muy
well it's worth it that he needed it too
bien vale que él también lo necesitaba
but
pero
but yes yes the truth is that we have known
pero sí sí la verdad que hemos sabido
renew it eh you are in good content
renovarlo eh estás en buen contenido lo
I consume all the videos then the one that
consumo todos los vídeos luego el que
Andrés I think is also quite
Andrés creo que también está bastante
well although it is full of scum
bien aunque está lleno de gentuza sus
comments an outrage Stay
comentarios una barbaridad Quédate
with me for tiktok and on tiktok people
conmigo para tiktok y en tiktok la gente
It's over there, there are people's comments
está para allá hay comentarios de gente
defending coscu and atrocities is not
defendiendo a coscu y barbaridades no es
It's his fault but it's true that the
culpa de él pero es verdad que los
comments are absolute aberration But
comentarios son aberración absoluta Pero
he is liked
él cae bien
It's okay, okay, let's add friends
está bien bien sumamos amigos
several times in fact he even came to me
varias veces de hecho hasta vino a mi
trial to say stupid things came to me
juicio a decir gilipolleces vino a mi
[ __ ] trial and they kicked him out of the room
juicio y le echaron de la sala
They kicked him out of the room, mind you, he didn't know that.
le echaron de la sala ojo no sabía eso
I knew what I had thrown at the door
yo sabía que había echado en la puerta
I knew he had been at the door
yo sabía que había estado en la puerta
but despite this I think it is now
pero a pesar de esto creo que ahora está
well what he does is also the
bien lo que hace también está el
I also detube
detubero también
who doesn't really give his opinion much, to be honest.
que no da mucho su opinión la verdad
Although it is also full of the
Aunque también está lleno de los
comments
comentarios
and
y
from Nauper
de nauper
What does this clown have to say next?
qué tienes que decir este payaso después
of harassing me for years
de llevar años acosándome a mí a mi
I extend the barbarities they have done, I will not
extiendo barbaridades han hecho no voy a
enter you already know you already know that with
entrar ya lo sabéis ya sabéis que con
other colleagues from the same guild I do not go
otros compañeros del mismo gremio no voy
to enter Okay
a entrar Vale
We are we are already quite up to the
estamos estamos ya bastante hasta el
neck we are already quite high the
cuello estamos ya bastante alta el
neck of controversy is worth family
cuello de polémica vale familia
incredible Congratulations to Congratulations this
increíble Enhorabuena a Enhorabuena este
boy without fear of success Thank you because
chico sin miedo al éxito Gracias porque
Well we will send you Amon without fear of
Bueno te mandaremos Amón sin miedo al
success I don't know if you're there in the chat
éxito no sé si estás por ahí por el chat
I thought I saw you but you
que me ha parecido verte pero te
We'll send Mom, I'll send you a ham
mandaremos a Mom te mandaré un jamón
When it happens I don't know where you live I don't know if
cuando pase no sé dónde vives no sé si
you live in Andorra or where but you
vives en andorra o dónde pero te
We will send ham because I don't know if it
mandaremos jamón porque no sé si lo
you know But from here I'm going to get it
sabes Pero de aquí voy a sacar pues
We are probably talking about four
seguramente estamos hablando de cuatro
hours because surely about 20 topics not
horas pues seguramente unos 20 temas no
about 20 extras no more or less no
unos 20 extrastos no más o menos no
We'll send you Monsete, I'll send you something.
te mandaremos a monsete te mandaré algo
king
rey
Thank you very much and a hug.
muchas gracias y un abrazo Muchas
thanks and a hug
gracias y un abrazo
Well, I don't know what I was saying.
Pues yo no sé lo que estaba diciendo
Aldala regarding the issue of strikes
aldala respecto al tema de los strike
Okay, I know I was talking about the
vale sé que estaba hablando respecto al
the issue of the strikes, there are people who
tema de los strike no que hay gente que
does not make legitimate content you know that
no hace contenido legítimo sabéis que
I partly agree with that and in
en parte estoy de acuerdo con eso y en
part not depending on the situation
parte no dependiendo de la situación
depending on the whole context and
dependiendo de todo el contexto y
depending on many factors, that is
dependiendo de muchos factores o sea
For me, fair use is no longer
para mí el uso legítimo ya no es
only the three requirements
solamente los tres requisitos
For me, fair use is no longer just
para mí el uso legítimo ya no solamente
It's for me and because it is like that
es vamos para mí y porque es así
objectively valid for me, fair use
objetivamente vale para mí uso legítimo
it's not
no es
exclusively
exclusivamente
the three requirements that are always
los tres requisitos que siempre se
They do not mention the time that you set.
mencionan no el tiempo que tú pongas el
video if you put maybe an excerpt
vídeo si tú pones a lo mejor un extracto
from a video or that you put the video
de un vídeo o que pongas el vídeo
complete for people to see
completo para que la gente lo vea
only on your channel Wait, I don't know
solamente en tu canal Espérate que no sé
Why doesn't my browser open now?
por qué no se me abre ahora el navegador
Uncle: For me fair use affects a lot
tío Para mí el uso legítimo afecta mucho
more content, that is, for example, me
más contenido o sea por ejemplo yo
I recently mentioned a case that I believe
mencionaba hace poco un caso que yo creo
that would be completely
que sería completamente
logical that it gives the knock down to that channel and
lógico que da las tumbar a ese canal y
I think he's actually going to do it in
creo que de hecho lo va a hacer en
any time Because also the type
cualquier momento Porque además el tipo
is putting content even that is
está poniendo contenido incluso que es
paid than for paying members
de pago que para miembros de pago
which is a channel that exclusively lives
que es un canal que exclusivamente vive
both in live shows and in videos
tanto en los directos como en los vídeos
that goes up from Dallas Vale and from Dallas me
que sube de Dallas Vale y de Dallas me
I mean not that I click and of the
refiero no que ponga clic y de las
news from Dallas but it is that it takes
noticias de Dallas sino que es que coge
your live content is watching the video
su contenido de directo es ver el vídeo
that Dallas has gone up to see it and that for
que haya subido Dallas verlo y eso para
I am not a legitimate so that is
mí no es un so legítimo o sea
Honestly, for me that is not a sole
sinceramente para mí eso no es un sole
legitimate that you one day put a video
legítimo que tú un día pongas un vídeo
Someone's whole Yes, it's worth a day is a
entero de alguien Sí vale un día es una
reaction reactions are allowed
reacción las reacciones están permitidas
as long as you are contributing no but
mientras que tú estés aportando no pero
Imagine that my channel covers all the
imaginaros que mi canal trata todos los
days of the video that Ricky Eddy uploads
días de el vídeo que suba Ricky Eddy
see it myself
verlo yo
It's like
es como
a little weird a little weird no Then
un poco raro un poco raro no Entonces
As we are already talking about the subject
como ya como estamos hablando del tema
of fair use and so on you know
del uso legítimo y demás ustedes sabéis
I don't normally watch the videos.
que yo normalmente los vídeos no los veo
integers okay In fact places makes me
enteros vale De hecho lugares me hace
one usually makes me a reaction worth it
una me suele hacer una reacción vale de
the videos even if they are from Dallas or
los vídeos aunque sean de Dallas o de
whoever and I see some parts a
quien sea y veo algunas partes un
little summary or whatever and I'll send it to
pequeño resumen o lo que sea y mando a
people who watch the full video but
la gente que vean el vídeo completo pero
Dallas today I'm not going to respect your custom
Dallas hoy no te voy a respetar un uso
legitimate and I'm going to eat your video
legítimo y me voy a comer tu vídeo
whole 29 minutes of Beijing to me
enterito 29 minutos de la Beijing me lo
I'm going to eat the whole thing because I have to
voy a comer enterito porque tengo que
record news ok Javi what have you
grabar noticiero vale Javi que te ha
invited to your little one whenever you want
invitado a su poca cuando tú quieras
When you want, OK, when you don't know.
cuando tú quieras Vale cuando tú no sé
where are you from to see if you live in the
de dónde eres a ver si vives en la
Patagonia the same No but if you live in
Patagonia lo mismo No pero si vives en
Andorra I don't know if it should be Andorra Barcelona or
andorra no sé si ser andorra Barcelona o
where
dónde
in one of these that I go to Barcelona
en una de estas que yo vaya a Barcelona
that they report me because they always report me
que me denuncien que siempre me denuncia
in Barcelona we do it
en Barcelona lo hacemos
That is to say that it has already been cancelled.
Es decir que ya se cancelé
Beijing has reached its end, it seems,
Beijing alcanzado su fin parece que para
The only thing that is talked about is Beijing
lo único de lo que se habla de Beijing
It is already time to cancel it As if we had
ya es para cancelarla Como si hubiéramos
back again to February
vuelto de nuevo otra vez a febrero de
this year in a tweet that in just a few
este año en un tweet que en solo unas
hours has achieved more than 13 million
horas ha conseguido más de 13 millones
of visits and if I update it it has been done
de visitas y si lo actualizo se ha hecho
Finally the last cancellation that stops
por fin la última cancelación que para
Who doesn't remember Beijing, which is the
quien no os acordáis Beijing que es la
auronplay couple both were
pareja de auronplay ambos fueron
canceled in February for the entire
cancelados en febrero por toda la
controversy of the
polémica de los
Andorra but I can move. Oh, okay then.
andorra pero me puedo mover Ah vale pues
whenever you want Whenever you want King then you
cuando quiera Cuando quiera Rey luego te
I search the net and follow you, man, when you
busco por la red y te sigo tío cuando tú
you want of course it would be missing more
quieras por supuesto faltaría más
Of course, yes, in this case, it would be missing more
faltaría más por supuesto que sí en esta
recent controversy you will know in this
reciente polémica sabrás en esta
recent controversy accuses her of doing
reciente polémica se la acusa de hacer
influence peddling by making
tráfico de influencias haciendo que
Poor little streamers
Pobrecitos streamers pequeñitos
innocent and who have nothing to do with it
inocentes y que no tienen nada que hayan
bad deed they have been expelled for
hecho malo se les ha expulsado por
try to make Beijing a
tratar a Beijing de ser una
cheese there have even been brands like
cheese hasta ha habido marcas como
Nesquik or this other company that has
Nesquik o esta otra empresa que se han
put against Beijing by canceling it
puesto en contra de Beijing cancelandola
for how evil the hour has been
por lo malvada que ha sido la hora de
get this poor kid banned
hacer que baneen a este pobre chico
position
puesto
there have been common marks
ha habido marcas comunes
name but this
nombre pero esto
This account is real
Esta cuenta es real
This is this account is from a real brand
esto es esta cuenta es de una marca real
I don't think so
de No creo no
Gaming
Gaming
name no no
nombre no no
squid or this other company that
squid o esta otra empresa que
tuxedo paper These are these are
esmoquin paper Estos son estos son
companies
empresas
you're touching my [ __ ]
me estáis tocando la
You're really pissing me off.
me estáis tocando los se dan
The thing is that now with the [ __ ] [ __ ]
cuenta es que ahora con la
This is verified against
esta del verificado puesto en contra de
Beijing canceling it because of how evil it is
Beijing cancelandola por lo malvada que
It's time to get them banned
ha sido la hora de hacer que baneen a
This poor boy from a game series
este pobre chico de una serie del juego
from rash let's take out all the peaks and the
de rash saquemos todos los picos y las
torches and let's end the
antorchas y acabemos con la
that's billing right let's do that all A
que es billing verdad hagamos eso todo A
We'd better investigate a little further.
lo mejor investiguemos un poquito más
Let's put it a little more confirmed, no no
pongamos un poquito más confirmado no no
I think the magnifying glass let's see who is this
creo la lupa veamos Quién es esta
person Who are the people who
persona Quiénes son las personas que
are promoting this and what is the
están promoviendo esto y cuál es el
true context behind all the
verdadero contexto detrás de toda la
escape because take out the torches and the
fuga porque sacar las antorchas y las
spades is very simple it only requires
picas es muy sencillo solo requiere
drop a random insult and cancel it and
soltar un insulto Random lo cancelen y
That's it, but research is for the people.
ya está pero investigar es para la gente
especially intelligent people who
especialmente inteligente la gente que
does not stay with the herd instinct
no se queda con el instinto de manada el
herd instinct that says Yes we will
instinto de rebaño que dicen Sí vamos a
make that cancellation and they don't bother
hacer esa cancelación y no se molestan
not for a moment to see the evidence for
ni por un momento en ver las pruebas por
that If you are watching This video
eso Si estás viendo Este vídeo
Congratulations you are one step closer
Felicidades estás un paso más cerca de
achieve mental enlightenment after
alcanzar la iluminación mental después
By watching this video you will not only understand
de ver este vídeo no solo vas a entender
Everything that is happening has more going for you
todo lo que está pasando tiene más te va
It's infuriating to see how disgusting people are
a dar rabia ver el asco que da la gente
Stay because this research is
quedaos porque esta investigación es
serious but before starting I want
seria pero antes de comenzar quiero
tell you that the subscription is totally
decirte que la suscripción es totalmente
closed no matter how hard you try
cerradas no importa cuando lo intentes
You can no longer subscribe to the channel.
ya no te puedes suscribir al canal es
that only Canal veterans can
que solo es veteranos del Canal pueden
remain subscribed here all the time
permanecer aquí suscritos todos los
new I'm so sorry but I've arrived
nuevos Lo siento mucho pero he llegado
late to be part of this select
tarde para formar parte de este selecto
Club that are the veterans of the Canal
Club que son los veteranos del Canal
cool, cool people who have been around for years
gente fachera facherita que lleva años
with me all the covers they have made
conmigo todas las fundas que han hecho
missing to win their medals
falta para ganar sus medallas de
veteran all the others I feel already
veterano todos los demás siento Ya os
you can subscribe you have to review
podéis suscribir tienes que revisar
manually
manualmente
Okay, let's get started.
bien Comencemos
what has happened recently
qué es lo que ha sucedido recientemente
There are many streamers who are playing
hay muchos streamers que están jugando a
a series of games called rust
una serie de un juego que se llama rust
This is not important but questions
esto no es importante pero cuestiones
that within this series there is both
que dentro de esta serie está tanto
auronplay as his partner bim the two
auronplay como su pareja bim los dos
are being cancelled Although more
están siendo cancelados Aunque más
Beijing that auron on this occasion but
Beijing que auron en esta ocasión pero
Auron is also being called out for
auron también lo están funando por
supposedly influence peddling is
supuestamente tráfico de influencias es
say that they are doing things not for
decir que están haciendo cosas no por
begin but why auron in this case
begin sino porque auron en este caso
would be the one who would have the power and
sería el que tendría el poder y
Obviously because of his past. Mmm yes
obviamente por su pasado de nada Mmm sí
for which people supposedly
para el cual supuestamente la gente
I would say that they were born for that
diría que ellos habían nacido para eso
but let's see what it really is
pero vamos a ver en realidad lo que está
people passing by is that a poor boy
pasando la gente es que un pobre chico
innocent who doesn't notice his little eyes
inocente que no le ojitos cuenta
verified but it is a verified account
verificada pero es que cuenta verificada
I will
lo haré
you will do it my son places How is it going
lo hares hijo mío lugares Cómo va el
news
noti
He had done nothing to anyone, the poor thing was
hecho nada a nadie el pobrecito fue
killed by Beijing in-game and
matado por Beijing dentro del juego y
like he made a little joke about it
como que le hizo una bromita de que lo
He mistook me for a Jew because Oh how bad
confundió con un judío pues Ay qué mala
that it is billion that they have banned me
que es billín que me han baneado el
I play because of the original title
juego por su culpa el título original
It says so on the part of a heel is that
dice así por parte de un talón es que
says baby mother she can do everything
dice bebé madre ella puede hacer todo lo
whatever he wants and I make a joke and
que le dé la gana y yo hago una broma y
I am expelled from p mother colleague since
se me expulsa de p madre Colega ya que
displays a message from the
muestra un mensaje de los
game administrators who say hello
administradores del juego que dicen Hola
trucks from administration we have
camiones desde administración hemos
had several mentions about your
tenido varias menciones acerca de tu
behavior and that of your chat is a
comportamiento y el de tu chat es una
mission a behavior With Beijing
misión un comportamiento Con Beijing
We understand that you don't care but
entendemos que a ti te dé igual pero
we don't make it so personal anymore
nosotros no hacerlo más tan personales
annoying and degrading is something that is not
molestas y denigrantes es algo que no
We will not allow under any circumstances in
vamos a permitir bajo ningún concepto en
the series is not Call Someone G and
la serie no es Llamar a alguien G y
get angry They are disgusting jokes and
enfadarte Son bromas asquerosas y
degrading and we are going to allow ourselves
denigrantes y nos vamos a permitir nos
we are forced to not allow entry
vemos obligados a no permitir la entrada
in the series a greeting to this basically
en la serie un saludo a esto básicamente
people turned against
la gente se volcó en contra
which has led to the expulsion of a
que ha provocado la expulsión de un
Poor innocent being who asks without
Pobrecito ser inocente que solicita sin
bad intention Total that people good
mala intención Total que la gente bueno
He went mega hyper with this saying Oh
se mega hiper volcó con esto diciendo Ay
how bad it is It's true what gold
qué mala que es Es verdad qué oro de
people blocked was an innocent is
personas bloqueado era un inocente es
humor and they have gone too far blah blah blah blah
humor y se han pasado bla bla bla bla
In short, this gum is an ally of
Total que este chicle que es aliada de
feminist posted saying
feminista publicó diciendo
is ally written with x
es aliade escribe con x
So cool then super
Entonces chupíguay entonces súper
highly approved
aprobadísimo
How can anyone hate this person?
como alguien puede odiar a esta persona
so nice and wonderful
tan maja y maravillosa
also really relevant we are going to
también realmente relevante vamos a
See him as a very good person.
verlo muy aliade buena persona que es
This gentleman because according to people what
este señor porque según la gente qué
insult Call a
insulto Llamar una
It is not insulting, it is telling the truth. So
no es insultar es decir la realidad Así
Let's see what this is
que vamos a ver qué es lo que es este
Feminine ally who writes with language
Aliado feminito que escribe con lenguaje
inclusive by doing a quick search
inclusivo haciendo una búsqueda rápida
We can see that he is such a good person
podemos ver que él es tan buena persona
who is dedicated to expressing himself from j k
que se dedica a expresarse de j k
Rowling, the creator of Harry Potter, with
rowling la creadora de Harry Potter con
things as good as insults like p
cosas tan buenas como insultos como p
like Z And he also wishes him the m Hey a
como Z Y además le desea la m Oye un
Very good feminist ally That's just it
Aliado feminista muy bueno Eso sí solo
for women who suit you with the
para las mujeres que le conviene con las
women who are not part of their
mujeres que no son de parte de su
political spectrum So it's very bad
espectro político Entonces está muy mal
This is the only thing because this has been with
esto es lo único porque esto ha sido con
five minutes of searching We have
cinco minutos de búsqueda Tenemos
also to him expressing himself The women
también a él expresándose Las mujeres
so this way if the tits were
así de esta manera si las tetas fueran
bricks nor m of Instagram would be a
ladrillos ni de m de Instagram sería un
castle in a series of tweets that do not
castillo en una serie de tweets que no
I ended up understanding the context very well
terminó muy de entender el contexto
saying photopé only sends ladies
diciendo photopé solo manda señoritas
with ortho you are a Zeta
con eres una Zeta
I don't know if I'm going to hold on, let's go now.
no sé si voy a aguantar ya vamos a f Ya
This Z is going slow, my money is not Zetas in it
esta Z va lenta mi dinero no Zetas en el
iPhone often p yaso gave you tit no
iPhone menudo p yaso te daba teta no
definitely a feminist ally of
definitivamente un Aliado feminista de
the classics of the classics the role of
los clásicos de los clásicos el papel de
the z of the woman Well it is a Z in the
la z de la mujer Pues es una Z en el
Francoism and one of the allies always
franquismo y una los aliados siempre
They have the same [ __ ] as these
tienen la misma además que estos
These are things from 2021. I thought it was
son cosas del 2021 Eh me creía que se
They were going to catch that it was 2013 like the
iban a agarrar que era 2013 como el
winchu no How strange in the Republic Ah
winchu no Qué raro en la República Ah
very well a great feminist ally Yes Yes
muy bien un gran Aliado feminista Sí Sí
definitely then dedicating himself to
definitivamente luego dedicándose a
make jokes the type who is dedicated to
hacer bromas el tipo que se dedica a
criticize Beijing because oh how good it is
criticar a Beijing porque ay qué bien es
What a wonderful girl She is tremendous
una chica qué maravilla Es una tremenda
Nachi Oh poor thing Oh what a curse
nachi Ay pobrecita Ay qué
while he is busy making jokes with
mientras él se dedica a hacer bromas con
the case of José Bretón which for the
el caso de José bretón el cual para los
that you don't know is a case of a guy who
que no sepáis es un caso de un tipo que
It was a shame that no one got a tattoo of José
quemó una pena que nadie se tatuara José
Breton or if he was a fan of yours wait for it
bretón ni si era fan suyas espérate a
that they make their own Netflix series
que hagan una serie de Netflix propios
In short, a really murky case
en fin un caso realmente turbio
They honestly dedicate themselves to making jokes
Honestamente se dedican a hacer bromitas
With him I am telling you names of
con él te estoy diciendo nombres de
unfaithful women and puts a lot of
mujeres infieles y pone un montón de
names ends up referring to a such
nombres termina refiriéndose a una tal
Maria as a p No no What a great
María como una p No no De qué gran
Feminist Ally Hear this tweet 10,000 likes
Aliado feminista Oye este tuit 10.000 me
like Hey but everything is fine because
gusta Oye pero todo está bien porque
As if he is left-handed. Of course he is about
como que es Zurdo Pues claro es de unos
political aspects we are going to applaud him
aspectos políticos vamos a aplaudirle
because oh, they're all just jokes, aren't they?
porque ay que son todo bromitas no
very healthy misogynistic sexist jokes
bromitas misóginas machistas muy sanas
then asking for something ugly like him
luego pidiendo alguna fea como el
demon But let it be G as for g
demonio Pero que sea G como para g
above by the place where I suppose that
encima por el sitio donde Supongo que
He is there, then you ask for it again sometime
está él luego la pedís de nuevo alguna
Ugly Zeta but I want it to be like that
Zeta fea pero con ganas que sea como
no one to cuddle with
nadie con la que acurrucarme por
Valencia This is the typical misogynist
Valencia Este es el típico misógino el
who hates women with all his soul
cual odia a las mujeres con toda su alma
refers to them with all the
se refiere a ellas con todos los
possible insults But he wants to finish
insultos posibles Pero quiere terminar
maintaining relationships with them very
manteniendo relaciones con ellas muy
wonderful the typical Ally the typical
maravilloso el típico Aliado el típico
Ally of the minister that we see daily in
Aliado de ministro que vemos a diario en
Twitter the worst thing is that the pipes
Twitter lo peor es que las pipas
they literally ask
literalmente preguntan
what level I take the opportunity to remind you of
qué nivel aprovecho para recordaros Por
true for any fool to say Oh
cierto para cualquier tonto que decir Ay
but in reality I was saying it as a joke and
pero en realidad Lo ponía de broma Y de
new this is a quick search with
nuevo esto es una búsqueda rápida con
just 5 minutes of searching any
solo 5 minutos de búsqueda cualquier
person who is able to tell me no but
persona que sea capaz de decirme no pero
They are healthy jokes, they are jokes
es que son bromitas sanas son bromitas
misogynistic and sexist But they are very healthy
misóginas y machistas Pero son muy sanas
you know, they are just jokes that are not
sabes o sea son solo bromitas que no
means that it really is sexist in
significa que realmente sea machista en
Reality is quite a feminist ally, eh?
realidad es todo un Aliado feminista eh
that you know Thank you all who
que lo sepáis Gracias a todos que me
You are supporting Oh what an Alliance I have seen
estáis apoyando Ay qué Alianza he visto
I think no one in this world thinks that
creo que nadie en este mundo piensa que
honestly Beijing is a yes
de forma honesta Beijing sea una sí
although the things I was doing already in 2013
aunque las cosas que hacía ya por 2013
They were in very bad taste humor which
eran de humor de muy mal gusto lo cual
I have already spoken a lot of times
ya he hablado ya un montón de veces
we can say that it is no longer objectively
podemos decir que ya no es objetivamente
what the Germans were like at the beginning
lo que eran los alemanes a principios
of the last century However, yes
del siglo pasado Sin embargo sí que
we have to think that this guy who is
tenemos que pensar que este tipo que se
dedicated to treating women of this
dedica a tratar a las mujeres de esta
way to wish the m to women who don't
manera a desearles la m a mujeres que no
They know only because it is not inside
conocen únicamente porque no está dentro
From its political aspect we have to
de su aspecto político tenemos que
to think that he is a complete Ally
pensar que él es todo un Aliado
feminist eh Don't make me because this
feminista eh No me hagáis porque esta
people are the same ones who are dedicated to calling
gente es la misma que se dedica a llamar
to Beijing which is a najaja yes for in its
a Beijing que es una najaja sí por en su
day having dedicated himself to making jokes
día haberse dedicado a hacer bromas al
style of trash that was dedicated to
estilo de la basura que se dedicaba hace
in 2013 it was already 10 years ago however this
en 2013 hace ya 10 años sin embargo este
uncle who just a few years ago
tío que hace solo unos pocos me
Remember that he is precisely a friend of
acordaros que Precisamente es amigo de
him and a piece of racist a piece of
él y un pedazo de racista un pedazo de
sexist and a piece of pork or rather in
machista y un pedazo de cerdo o sea en
Lanús is [ __ ] disgusting. The cloud is
lanús da putísimo asco Es que la nube da
[ __ ] disgusting and the guy is [ __ ] disgusting
putísimo asco y el tío va daliade el tío
Goodbye
vade bueno
the usual things do not fail if they are
lo de siempre sí que no fallan si es que
It never fails, they are always the same.
no falla siempre son iguales está
saying terrible things about women
diciendo barbaridades sobre las mujeres
even wishing m to women who don't
incluso deseando la m a mujeres que no
are within your political spectrum
están dentro de su espectro político
we have to understand that his is only
tenemos que entender que lo suyo es solo
It's dark humor with wine, no, no, good.
es humor negro a pelo de vino no no bien
yes he is those things but this guy is
sí que es esas cosas pero este tío es
It's just a little worm's edge now
solo es solo un borde de gusanito ya
you begin to see where this is going
empezáis a ver por dónde va la
cheap hypocrisy, this ridiculous rabble
hipocresía barata esta gentuza ridícula
from Twitter not well because there are worse things
de Twitter no bien pues hay cosas peores
still with which we can talk about
todavía con las que podemos hablar sobre
This guy And again I still haven't gotten into it
este tío Y de nuevo aún no me metido al
context when I get into giving everything
contexto cuando me meto a dar todo el
deep context You're still going to freak out
contexto profundo Vais a flipar todavía
more because this guy's friends are Me
más porque los amigos este tío son Me
I dare say even worse than
atrevo a decir que incluso peores de lo
What was Beijing like 10 years ago?
que era Beijing hace 10 años este tipo
This macawing is from here
de aquí es este macawing que está aquí
right after a party He meets with
justo después de una fiesta Se junta con
this other ridiculous one
este otro ridículo
the Green guy, that is to say, for me the [ __ ]
el Green tío o sea para mí lo del
trucks enough to throw him out of the
camiones tanto como para echarlo de la
series is not worth it I was giving you my
serie no es vale os estuve dando mi
I'm not going to give my opinion yesterday again.
opinión ayer no voy a volver a darla
complete but basically it seems to me that
completa pero básicamente me parece que
It's to give it a little touch. Hey, listen to me.
es para darle un toquecito Oye escúchame
This is not worth it, this way, not here
esto no vale esto por aquí no por aquí
A little touch is fine, but this guy's
un toquecito vale pero lo de este chico
I think it should be bannable.
Me parece que debería ser baneable de
Made on Twitch
hecho en Twitch
on the platform
en la plataforma
Personally, I think that
personalmente o sea yo creo que lo de
This guy what he said the joke he made
este chico lo que dijo la broma que hizo
He should be bannable on Twitch, I'm surprised.
debe ser baneable en Twitch me sorprende
that it is not in fact and let me
que no lo sea de hecho y déjame
explain to you who his little friend is because
explicaros quién es su amiguito porque
It has quite a lot of firecrackers, there are a series of
tiene bastante traca hay una serie de
words that are too sensitive that do not
palabras demasiado sensibles que no
I can say here but he literally
puedo decir aquí pero él literalmente
just a couple of days ago in a
hace tan solo un par de días en un
Stream that I was doing together
Stream que estaba haciendo en conjunto
with this ridiculousness here that this is the
con este ridículo aquí que este es el
that you have just seen the truck axis of
que acabáis de ver el eje de camiones de
Twitter is the one that is dedicated to treating the
Twitter el que se dedica a tratar a las
women as the worst trash and wish them
mujeres como la peor basura y desearles
the m for not being in all its appearance
la m por no estar en todo su aspecto
This thing here is political because its
político es esta cosa de aquí pues su
little friend from here put a Stream to
amiguito de aquí se puso un Stream a
I'm going to say the following outrage
decir la siguiente barbaridad voy a
having to censor almost everything, as I explained
tener que censurar casi todo ya explico
because
porque
almost everything not everything really
casi todo no todo realmente
gora means Long live in Basque and what
gora significa Viva en Vasco y lo que
He says that after that he mentions a
dice a continuación de eso menciona una
terrorist band is also a band of
banda terrorista también eh una banda de
people who are dedicated to installing artifacts
gente que se dedican a poner artefactos
explosives in Spain and that ended with
explosivos en España y que acabaron con
the lives of more than 800 people and this
la vida de más de 800 personas y este
clown from here who is again the
payaso de aquí que de nuevo es el
This guy's little friend here was
amiguito de este tipo de aquí estuvo
dedicating to say long live this band that
dedicando a decir viva esta banda que
all the things they did end with
todas las cosas que hicieron acaban con
the lives of more than 800 people in Spain
la vida de más de 800 personas en España
Here are some headlines he made
aquí tenéis algunos titulares que hizo
This band in Spain added to that this
esta banda en España sumado a eso este
ridiculous He's been posting things like this for years
ridículo Lleva años poniendo cosas como
that he is going to shout I imagine that he has not
que va a gritar me imagino que no ha
you have given the headlines
puesto los titulares os habéis dado
account that has said Here you have some
cuenta que ha dicho Aquí tenéis algunos
headlines of how strong they are
titulares de lo fuerte que son me
I imagine you haven't put them in the
imagino que no los has puesto de los
song gora sources the band was going
fuentes de song gora la banda iba
saying constantly throughout
diciendo constantemente a lo largo de
several years of one who is going to do the
varios años de uno que va a hacer lo
same to remove that and also talking
mismo para quitar eso y también hablando
with other colleagues that really the thing
con otros colegas que de verdad la cosa
more extremely racist than there is
más extremadamente racista que existe un
guy who dedicated himself to saying authentic things
tipo que se dedicó a decir auténticas
atrocities against the people
barbaridades en contra de la gente
Latin America and as you can see here
latinoamérica y como podéis ver aquí
This same guy here is dedicated to
este mismo tipo de aquí se dedica a
play with this guy who is now
jugar con este tipo que ahora está
dedicating themselves to functioning well because Oh
dedicándose a funcionar bien porque Ay
It's that Beijing is very, very good friends.
es que Beijing es muy son amiguitos son
the group no yes instead their little friends
el grupo no sí en cambio sus amiguitos
I'm not going to call them dog. Oh, nor am I going to call them dog.
no los voy a llamar perro Ah ni tampoco
he starts talking about the extremely
se pone a hablar de lo extremadamente
racist who is one of his little friends no
racista que es uno de sus amiguitos no
no no no no no better not to talk but
no no no no no mejor no va a hablar pero
Well the full video is in Dallas
bueno el vídeo completo está en Dallas
without filter
sin filtro
Ah, he has uploaded another short one in
Ah que ha subido otro más cortos en
Dallas Review
Dallas review
Ah, I'm seeing him walking in Dallas.
Ah yo lo estoy viendo andar en Dallas
I'm seeing it without a filter
sin filtro lo estoy viendo
Ah, there is another shorter one, that is, the one who gives
Ah que hay otro más corto o sea quien da
the review there is another shorter one
la review hay otro más corto
I didn't realize I put this
no me he dado cuenta he puesto este
pull because I haven't noticed but yes
tirón pues no me he dado cuenta pero sí
I want to talk about how J.K. Rowling deserves
quiero hablar de cómo j.k rowling merece
the m of how women are a piece
la m de cómo las mujeres son unas pedazo
from Zeta and treat them as p definitely
de Zeta y tratarlas de p definitivamente
That's what he's going to talk about, you're watching.
de eso sí que va a hablar estáis viendo
I no longer know where the hypocrisy here goes
ya no por donde va la hipocresía de aquí
Well wait, this hasn't even happened yet.
pues esperad que aún Esto ni siquiera ha
started it is possible that people will
empezado es posible que la gente se
still dedicated to calling Beijing that
dedique todavía a llamar a Beijing que
is a
es una
for jokes and black humor in bad taste and
por bromas y humor negro de mal gusto y
attacks that were made in 2013 However,
ataques que hacían 2013 Sin embargo a
some guys who are dedicated to this today
unos tipos que se dedican a día de hoy
just a few days ago to say long live one
hace tan solo unos días a decir viva una
gang that ended the lives of more than
banda que acabó con la vida de más de
800 people
800 personas
total total or so, look at you
total total o sea fíjate tú
It turns out they want to Cancel and
Resulta ser que quieren Cancelar y
Calling Beijing a Nazi for the jokes that
Llamar nazia Beijing por las bromas que
They spent 2013 But they spend that
gastaban 2013 Pero ellos gastan esa
joke as a joke today
broma como una gracia hoy
today
hoy
happy about drug racism
contento del racismo droga
Junior, whatever the [ __ ] you call yourself, you have a
Junior como se te llame tienes un
video Put a nuke on the League of racists
vídeo Pon a nuke en la Liga de racista
on my main channel put it people of
en mi canal principal ponlo gente de
Latin America to wish women the m
latinoamérica a desearle la m a mujeres
because they do not match my
porque es que no coinciden con mi
political spectrum as people can
espectro político como la gente puede
still devoting themselves to canceling
todavía estarse dedicando a cancelar
good for things that happened 10 years ago
bien por cosas que pasaron hace 10 años
that I was one of the victims of that
que yo fui una de las víctimas de eso
what happened at that moment that I was
que pasó en ese momento que yo he sido
able to forgive that Virginia lost
capaz de perdonar que Virginia perdió
Sorry a million [ __ ] times
Perdón un millón de puñeteras veces
about that topic and has not been around for many years
acerca ese tema y lleva muchos años sin
do none of that much Before even
hacer nada de eso mucho Antes siquiera
that you started to slow her down, she did it for
de que empezaste a frenarla lo hizo por
his own foot not because he started the cradle
su propio pie no porque empezó la cuna
But instead to a misogynistic stalker
Pero en cambio a una acosador misógino
sexist who acts like an ally
machista que se la está de Aliado
feminist that this guy is
feminista que es este tipo le están
applauding the nonsense as it is
aplaudiendo las tonterías cómo es
possible a type that by the way for
posible un tipo que por cierto para
double more The Bet that you believe it
redoblar más La Apuesta que lo creéis
This is on top of that, he says he supports
esto encima es que dice que apoya a
coscu what is that
coscu que es que
feminist ally but very total
aliade feminista pero totalísimo
feminist ally But you are totally
aliada de feminista Pero totalísimo te
Feminism has it all, Ally, and no
lo tiene todo el Aliado feminismo y no
just that is that it has more than that on top is
solo eso es que tiene más que encima es
fan of the criminal wismicook already
fan del delincuente de wismicook ya lo
that this guy was missing, let's go during
que le faltaba este tipo vamos durante
years he has dedicated himself to making fun of me
años se ha dedicado a burlarse de mis
fans this specifically from a girl who
fans esto en concreto de una chica que
decided to get a tattoo for a visit on his arm
decidió tatuarse para visita en el brazo
saying that he hates me so much when in
diciendo que me odia muchísimo cuando en
the life of when in the life of this
la vida de cuando en la vida de este
I have done nothing to him so that he hears me
enfermo le he hecho nada para que me oye
a lot of mentally ill people who
muchísimo pedazo de enfermo mental que
This guy is so sick, look how sick he is
está el tipo fijaos enfermo que se
dedicate yourself to watching my [ __ ] streams like
dedica a ver mis puñeteros streams como
you have to be crazy to hate me
de loco tienes que estar para odiarme
a lot and watch my damn streams
muchísimo y ver mis puñeteros streams
mocking my fans using arguments
burlarte de mis fans usando argumentos
you are so poor that you are what you are
tan pobres tú eres lo que estás
criticizing zero arguments comes from it
criticando argumentos cero lo viene por
part of a piece of sexist misogynist
parte de un pedazo de misógino machista
that an Ally is noticed or rather uncle you put
que fíjese un Aliado o sea tío te pones
to criticize Dallas with the mantras and
a criticar al Dallas con los mantras y
now you have those
ahora tú tienes esos
Lol
LoL
It doesn't fail to complete you, no, but it is
No falla para que te completo no pero es
that never fails is the typical one
que no falla es el típico
profile is the typical ready and worse pattern
perfil es el típico patrón listo y peor
wishing me the m look what it says
deseándome la m fijaos lo que pone
I am sorry to inform you of some very important news.
siento comunicaros una noticia muy
sad that I just got it, they just finished me
triste que me acaba de llegar me acaban
to say that they have just found
de decir que acaban de encontrar a
Dallas reviews home alone quiet
Dallas reviews solo en casa tranquilo
watching a movie before going to sleep and not
viendo una peli antes de dormir y que no
nothing bad has happened to him, you sick piece of [ __ ]
le ha pasado nada malo pedazo de enfermo
in 2021 in 2021 This makes less than
en 2021 en 2021 de Esto hace menos de
two years, a year and a half, nothing more than
dos años un año y medio nada más que
I've been wanting to have m for a while now
hace que me estaba deseando la m a mí
Why Because he is a piece of sick and
Por qué Porque es un pedazo de enfermo y
Another word to be able to say this class
Otra palabra para poder decir esta clase
They are real harassers.
de gentuza son Auténticos acosadores
This guy is a real stalker.
este tipo es un auténtico acosador es
friend of people who are dedicated to shouting at
amigo de gente que se dedica a gritar a
They are going to glorify bands that finished off
van a gloriar a bandas que acabaron con
the lives of hundreds of people to do
la vida de cientos de personas hacer
jokes with cases of children who
bromitas con casos de niños que
succumbed at the hands of their parents
sucumbieron a manos de sus padres a
mention cases like that of Marta del
mencionar casos como el de Marta del
Castillo that the case of was a horror
Castillo que fue un horror el caso de
a missing girl
una chica desaparecido
and they finished her off in the most
y acabaron con ella la forma más
horrible in Spain and the guy does
horrorosa dentro de España y el tío hace
reference when on Twitter in 2012
referencia cuando en Twitter en 2012
people were dedicating themselves to making fun of
estaba dedicando la gente a burlarse de
her and the family How fun No
ella y de la familia Qué divertido No
what a laugh a girl who by the way was
qué risas una chica que por cierto fue
victim of her boyfriend the clearest example
víctima de su novio el más claro ejemplo
of what they might consider the
de lo que podrían considerar la
sexist violence Ah but this is very
violencia machista Ah pero este es muy
ally eh he uses tongue like Marta
aliada eh él usa lengua lo de Marta
Castle
Castillo
[Music]
[Música]
would this be we also talked about it in the
sería esto lo hablamos también en el
documentary
documental
We also talked about this when the whole
esto lo hablamos también cuando toda la
documentary era
época del documental
Marta's castle would have been a
el de Marta el castillo hubiera sido un
case of
caso de
gender violence because they are
violencia de género porque están
talking about an ex-partner when they are
hablando de una expareja cuando son
ex-partner cases are gender violence
casos de expareja es violencia de género
always inclusive graphics
siempre inclusive gráfica
a stalker's heart has no more
corazón de acosador no tiene más
words to refer to him but Hey
palabras para referirse a él pero Oye
that he respects trans people a lot
que él respeta mucho a los trans qué
damn it's hard to respect pronouns and no
cuesta respetar los pronombres y no
use the Dead name you are really direct
usar el Dead name de verdad sois directo
something and I wonder what it costs him
algo y yo me pregunto qué le cuesta a él
don't wish bad things on people you don't know
no desearle la m a gente que no conoce
absolutely nothing like me as j k
absolutamente nada como a mí como j k
Rowling or other celebrities that He hates
rowling u otros famosos que Él odia
a lot because it's bad here Oh that's it
muchísimo porque está mal de aquí Ay eso
It costs him a lot, right? That's true.
le cuesta mucho verdad es cierto eso
It costs a lot now it is very feminist And
cuesta mucho ahora es muy feminista Y
respects trans people a lot and have a
respeta mucho a los trans ay ay tener un
crazy prize please eh Ah but
premio por favor loquísimo eh Ah pero
Wait a moment, he is so
Espérate un momento que él luego es tan
moral that takes a long time
moral que lleva muchísimo tiempo
attacking Beijing on his Twitter
atacando a Beijing en su Twitter
saying things like I haven't commented on anything
diciendo cosas como no he comentado nada
of the subject because I didn't feel like it but this
del tema porque no me apetecía pero esta
Capture seems like poetry to me, Sukan's tweet
captura me parece poesía el tweet sukan
referencing and subscribers
haciendo referencia y los suscriptores
that they won't even understand what it means
que no entenderán ni lo que significa
a lot and they are going to defend it
muchísimo y que van a defender hace lo
that it happens and ends scares me
que pase y termina me da miedo
Today I am truly afraid
a día de hoy tengo miedo hoy de verdad
How can you be so shameless not to
Cómo se puede ser tan caradura el no
I knew this about this guy, piece of
sabía esto de este tipo pedazo de
stalker who is dedicated to wishing you harm
acosador que se dedica a desearle la m a
people like me like jk rowling were going to
gente como yo como jk rowling iba a
talking about how this is what Beijing is
hablar de que ay es que Beijing es esto
definitely well totally is this
definitivamente bien totalmente es esto
because he was already dedicated to making humor
porque ya se dedicaba a hacer humor de
bad taste 10 years ago It is that it is a
mal gusto hace 10 años Es que es un
danger scares me Beijing Ah But you
peligro me da miedo Beijing Ah Pero a ti
you are not afraid of yourself that you
no te das miedo a ti mismo que te
you dedicate yourself to insulting women has been
dedicas a insultar a las mujeres ha sido
a piece of misogynistic sexist harasser
un pedazo de misógino machista acosador
That's not it, that's not what scares you. Oh and no.
eso no eso no te da miedo Ah y no
Let's forget By the way, who uses this from the
olvidemos Por cierto que usa esto de las
Guatemalan fans of auronplay for the
fans guatemaltecas de auronplay para los
that you do not know that to those who do not know
que no sepáis que a los que no sepáis
that you may not understand about America
que a lo mejor no entendáis de América
This thing about referring to someone's fans
esto de referirse a los fans de alguien
specifically speaking to God as
en concreto hablando a Dios Como
Guatemalans, there are many people from Spain
guatemaltecos hay mucha gente de España
who uses this term in a pejorative way
que usa Este término de forma peyorativa
that is, a xenophobic term for
es decir un término xenófobo para
referring to it is like when you say Panchito
referirse es como cuando dices
so that you understand me like when they say
para que me entendáis como cuando dicen
Panchito and when they give it back to him
y cuando se lo devuelven hasta
when can they do it Javi dark humor
cuándo pueden hacerlo Javi humor negro
of traca
de traca
Let's see, you have some dark humor.
a ver a mí hay humor negro que te tienes
to laugh Because let's see
que reír Porque a ver
Personally it's not my favorite humor anymore
personalmente no es mi humor favorito ya
I've said it I've said it many times
lo he dicho Ya lo he dicho muchas veces
[Music]
[Música]
It's not my favorite love but
no es mi amor Favorito pero
There are undoubtedly times when
indiscutiblemente hay veces que
It's not bad that you have to laugh
que no está mal que te tienes que reír
Because [ __ ] he tells a [ __ ] joke and
Porque dice un chiste cabrón y
tells a joke that is funny and you
dice un chiste que tiene gracia y te
you laugh, a laugh escapes you, okay?
ríes se te escapa una carcajada vale
but there are times when what you have is
pero es que hay veces que lo de usted Lo
we would have to see it's true Look it is
tendríamos que ver es verdad Mira es
It's true that there are times when
verdad hay veces que
simply shield Call someone
simplemente escudan Llamar a alguien
Panchito or being racist with dark humor
o ser racista con humor negro
Ok, Latinos, I don't know when they
vale los latinos no sé en qué momento se
popularized in using Guatemala as
popularizó en usar Guatemala como
insult but many Spaniards who use it
insulto pero muchos españoles que usa lo
of Guatemalan fans as a
de las fans guatemaltecas como un
xenophobic insult that you know and nothing
insulto xenofóbico que lo sepáis y nada
refers with this xenophobic insult to
se refiere con este insulto xenofóbico a
the Guatemalans and all because he has
las guatemaltecas y todo porque él tiene
a little bit of ego for himself since
una patita de ego por sí mismo ya que
grez invited him to his awards trash
grez lo invitó a su basura de premios de
the slam and he wanted them to vote for him
los slam y él quería que votarán por su
dance because he knows that his dance will humiliate
baile porque sabe que su baile humillará
to the ferret dancing xenophobic pepas
a la hurón bailando pepas xenofóbico
sexist misogynist friend of guys who
machista misógino amigo de tipos que se
They dedicate themselves to glorifying bands that are
dedican a vanaglorear a bandas que se
They dedicate themselves to ending life for a
dedican a acabar con la vida durante un
lots of years this guy tries
montón de años este tipo intenta
compete against auronplay Oh and also
competir contra auronplay Ah Y también
Of course attack because it scares him
por supuesto atacar Porque le da miedo
for more than a year saying that
desde hace más de un año diciendo que
look for third raid then the guy
busquen tercer raid luego el tipo
talking about Beijing being dedicated to
hablando de que Beijing se dedicaba a
encourage bullying And while this is
fomentar el acoso Y si bien Esto es
true 10 [ __ ] years ago you did it
cierto hace 10 puñeteros años tú lo
you do today that I know that it is
haces a día de hoy que sé que está
sick eh How many more times does he have to
enfermo eh Cuántas veces más tiene que
apologize Beijing Ah but wait
pedir perdón Beijing Ah pero Espérate
that these harassers like this one here
que estos acosadores como este de aquí
This today How much morality How good that
este hoy Cuánta moralidad Qué bueno que
I'm guys there and it's all the followers
soy chicos hay y es todos los seguidores
of this guy saying what insult Call
de este tipo diciendo qué insulto Llamar
n to an n is not insulting if they are
n a un n no es insultar si están
sick Call n yet n then call
enfermos Llamar n aún n entonces llama
which hospital are you going to call?
al hospital cuál va a llamar
a child seems degrading to me that for
un nene me parece denigrante que por
call n even n the rights are taken away
llamar n aún n se le quitan los derechos
to a person who is not n Not him To the
a una persona que no es n No él A lo
It's not better but it is a piece of
mejor no es n pero si es un pedazo de
stalker remains one to this day
acosador lo sigue siendo a día de hoy
misogynist sexist xenophobic who
misógino machistas xenofóbico que lo
you freak out because we are going to call Beijing n
flipas porque vamos a llamar a Beijing n
for making jokes about n and they want
por hacer bromas de n y quieren
grab Oh, he makes jokes
agarrarse Ay es que él hace bromitas
as if wishing me the m is a
como si desearme a mí la m sea una
joke Oh and again of course
bromita Ah Y de nuevo por supuesto
bringing up this topic of the mother with the
sacando el tema este de la madre con el
son for whom By the way Beijing Ya
hijo por el cual Por cierto Beijing Ya
fixed things with that girl Ah but
arregló las cosas con esa chica Ah pero
He can make jokes about the case
él él puede hacer bromitas con el caso
from kills to the castle when they were
de mata al castillo cuando estaban
making fun of her and also with the case
burlando de ella y también con el caso
from José Bretón a guy who has an ego
de José bretón un tipo que tiene el ego
so extremely high that it is dedicated
tan extremadamente subido que se dedica
constantly to hesitate and celebrate
constantemente a vacilar y celebrar
when you get new followers and
cuando consigue nuevos seguidores y lo
Worse is that this recent funita has
peor es que esta funita reciente le ha
gained a huge number of followers
hecho ganar una barbaridad de Seguidores
Look how you say it, "Oh, we already have five."
fijaos Cómo se dice Ay ya tenemos cinco
How much has been earned was already trucks 24
Cuánto ha ganado fue ya camiones 24
How much has he earned now with the nonsense?
Cuánto ha ganado ahora con la tontería
The other time was with the dance and now
la otra vez fue con el baile y ahora
doesn't come out
no sale
I don't have the numbers marked, sorry.
que no tengo los números marcado perdón
the mother who gave birth to me. Of course, until
la madre que me parió Pues claro hasta
against Beijing and this is without
en contra de Beijing y esto está sin
update
actualizar
165,000 appears now This is without
165.000 aparece ahora Esto está sin
Of course it will be positioned like that. That is.
Claro pues se va a posicionar así O sea
If this is what makes you win
si esto es lo que le hace ganar
This one is going to have a lot of followers
seguidores a saco va a tener esta
always clear position
postura siempre claro
pay attention to one thing
fijaros en una cosa
quite curious
bastante curiosa
When the number of followers increases, it is exactly the same.
Cuando sube de Seguidores justo el mismo
month that increases a lot of Followers that are
mes que sube mucho de Seguidores que se
became famous
hizo famoso
unfollowed 90 people
dejó de seguir a 90 personas
won 3000 more. That is, he has 13,000 in what
ganó 3000 más O sea lleva 13.000 en lo
It's day, pay attention to this detail.
que va de día fijaros en este detalle
each one interpret it as you wish
cada uno interpretarlo como queráis
the month that became famous
el mes que se hizo famoso
unfollowed 90 people Good more
dejó de seguir a 90 personas Bueno más
the new ones that would follow or that is
las nuevas que seguiría o sea
surely 100 people
seguramente una 100 personas
earned 6,000 more
ganó 6.000 más
50,000 followers and also people with
50.000 seguidores y además gente con
less than 143,000 followers commenting
menos de 143.000 Seguidores opinando
because he had it easy When you published
porque él tenía fácil Cuando publicaste
Thanks but 150,000 followers
opinar Gracias pero 150.000 seguidores
Now we can invade and come back. Look
ahora podemos invadir y vuelva Mirad
I have more followers than inhabitants and I
tengo más seguidores que habitantes y yo
come back Look, we have more than 120,000
vuelva Mirad tenemos más de 120.000
Followers we can invade this city
Seguidores podemos invadir esta ciudad
pathetic but extremely pathetic
patético pero extremadamente patético el
ego so excessive that he wants
ego tan desmesurado que quiere
also compare with auronplay XD It's
compararse además con auronplay XD Es
that I see the worst is that literally
que me veo lo peor es que literalmente
people actually famous this guy who
la gente de hecho famoso este tipo que
It is the most worrying thing of all
es lo más preocupante de todo una
such a hypocritical and harassing person as
persona tan hipócrita tan acosadora como
He who has become famous at the coast of being
él que se ha hecho famosa a Costa de ser
a stalker is amazing and alone and by
un acosador es increíble y solo y por
I want you to see this funita, eh had
esta funita quiero que veáis eh tenía
154,000 followers And now look how
154.000 seguidores Y ahora fijaos cómo
upload this Look for making a beiji
sube esto Mirad por hacer una beiji
auron look at the plate pla Of course yes
auron fijaos placa pla Claro que sí di
that yes making you famous at the cost of being
que sí haciéndote famoso a Costa de ser
a piece of stalker and a piece
un pedazo de acosador y un pedazo
hypocrite Bravo, wonderful these people
hipócrita Bravo maravilloso esta gente
From Twitter eh Very well people of Twitter
de Twitter eh Muy bien gente de Twitter
I like it, let's attack Beijing.
Así me gusta vamos a atacar a Beijing
because there is vikin that is that is a
porque hay vikin que es que es una
toaster but we are going to make this type
tostadora pero este tipo vamos a hacerle
famous a guy who uses insults
famoso un tipo que usa insultos
xenophobic who is a friend of people
xenofóbicos que es amigo de gente
racist is a friend and streams with people
racista es amigo y hace Stream con gente
which is dedicated to saying long live a band that
que se dedica a decir viva una banda que
ended the lives of hundreds of people
acabó con la vida de cientos de personas
and with a lot of kidnappings that
y con un montón de secuestros que
They did it in Spain Bravo. That's what I say.
hicieron en España Bravo Eso sí di que
Yes, such a misogynist, such a harasser.
sí que misógino machista un acosador tal
which is still the case today. Oh what
cual lo sigue siendo día de hoy Ay qué
Well, and all because why not what was it?
bueno Y todo por qué no qué fue lo que
exactly happened
pasó exactamente
that opens somewhere but I don't have any
que abre algún sitio pero no tengo ni
idea that's important guys I can
idea eso es importante chicos la puedo
selling for something is a [ __ ] house there
vender por algo es una casa hay
Hello people, come, we are of peace, come Peace
gente Hola ven son de paz ven Paz
Man, let's look at what it says and now
Hombre vamos fijaos que pone y ahora
Pay attention to what he is saying
Presta atención a lo que se pone a decir
Chuchat that Obviously the guy is a
chuchat que Obviamente el tipo es un
sick you can expect the kind of
enfermo podéis esperar la clase de
comments
comentarios
It doesn't bother you to dedicate yourself to publishing later.
no te jode después dedicarte a publicar
a bunch of pure harassment garbage no longer
un montón de basura de puro acoso ya no
against her but against
en contra de ella sino en contra de
anyone but it's that if not even
cualquiera pero es que si ni siquiera
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
the Beijing issue
el tema de Beijing
man who the [ __ ] is this turkey that comes out to me
tío quién es este pavo que me sale
now all the time people
ahora todo el tiempo la gente
criticizing him and all the time they come out
criticándolo y todo el tiempo me salen
a guy with 3000 followers
un tío con 3000 seguidores
because the other one keeps coming out and
porque no paran de salirme el otro y de
This man the issue of Beijing is that
este hombre el tema de Beijing Es que
Besides, Beijing doesn't kill him. I think so.
además Beijing no lo mata Yo creo que
Billín doesn't even realize that this guy is the one
billín ni cae en que este chico es el
[ __ ] trucks when the game kills him
camiones cuando lo matan el juego
kills him in the game and that's it. It's not because of the
lo mata en el juego y punto No es por lo
from Twitter or anything like that Tell me
de Twitter ni nada por el estilo Contame
or I'll even find JK Rowling herself.
o encontraré hasta la propia jk rowling
against all women while
en contra de todas las mujeres mientras
be an ally How you can tell that he is
seas de Aliado Cómo se le nota que está
not angry after what you've done
ardida no después de lo que has hecho
You'll still think it won't be up there
aún Pensarás que no va a estar arriba
with you is that he has a pair of balls a
contigo es que tiene un par de huevos un
a pair of eggs but this fat
par de huevos pero así de gordos
I'm going to put begin SS for you so that
te voy a poner begin SS para que lo
You know the SS Gestapo was like the
sepáis la SS gestapo era como el
personal army of a certain painter
ejército personal de un cierto pintor
that existed in Germany from back in the day
que existía por la Alemania de allá del
1300 of 1930, look what it says
1300 del 1930 fijaos que dice
Holy [ __ ], well, now we know that he's alive.
ostia Pues nada ya sabemos que vive
There it is easier to surround with a stone
ahí Es más fácil rodear con una piedra
that those of bellum and [ __ ] mother the stone
que los de bellum y madre la piedra
balls he's killed me with desire eh he has me
me ha matado con ganas eh me ha
killed me has killed me With consent
matado me ha matado Con consentimiento
how strong how strong now
qué fuerte qué fuerte ahora
dude is saying it the whole chat and me
tío lo está diciendo todo el chat y yo
I don't need to say anything, he's saying it
no necesito decir nada lo está diciendo
the whole chat what the chat says sss the
todo el chat lo que dice el chat sss la
n hostia had to be Beijing saw you
n ostia tenía que ser Beijing te vio
Peruvian face, a Lucky SS, be careful that
cara de peruano un Lucky SS cuidado que
Beijing thought you were mine.
Beijing se ha pensado que eras m te
He mistook you for a Jew and thought you were
confundió con un judío pensó que eras
Peruvian saw you as a Peruvian and that
peruano te vio cara de peruano y ese
guy was going to say Ah says it all
tipo se iba a decir Ah ya lo dice todo
the flat one Hahaha
el chato Jajaja
whole so that we have it left By the way
entero para que nos quede Por cierto
any kind of doubt about what it means
algún tipo de duda sobre Qué significa
gora here you have what it means
gora aquí tenéis Qué significa
Ideally, this is worth seeing.
idealmente Esto vale para que lo veáis
okay and I honestly don't know the
de acuerdo y yo no sé honestamente las
pathetic brands that are dedicated to
marcas de patéticos que se dedican a
hire sick bastards for their
contratar a puñeteros enfermos para sus
brands take them on Twitter there is a
marcas llevarlas en Twitter hay una
serious species dude
especie en serio tío
man, the thing about the brands, if this is a
tío lo de las marcas si esto es una
The truth is that I refuse to think
marca de verdad es que me niego a pensar
I refuse to think that this is a brand
me niego a pensar que esto sea una marca
really
de verdad
I want to think that it is someone who has
quiero pensar que es alguien que se ha
put the rabbit for the mockery of covid
puesto el conejo por la burla del covid
I mean, I refuse to think that it is
o sea es que me niego a pensar que sea
a true brand is that brands
una marca de verdad es que las marcas
They are stupid lately with the
son últimamente con la
nonsense of hiring the kid who
tontería de contratar al chavalito que
do these things to gain likes and
hagan estas cosas para ganar likes y
followers and so on and obviously the
seguidores y demás y obviamente las
pathetic brands that are dedicated to
marcas de patéticos que se dedican a
hire sick bastards for their
contratar a puñeteros enfermos para sus
brands take them on Twitter there is a
marcas llevarlas en Twitter hay una
a kind of fashion that they are dedicated to
especie de moda que se dedican a
hire a bunch of sick people to
contratar a pedazo de enfermísimos para
take their brands on Twitter and then
llevar sus marcas en Twitter y pues se
They dedicated themselves to supporting this guy who is
dedicaron a apoyar a este tipo que es
broadly sexist misogynist xenophobic
ampliamente machista misógino xenofóbico
and a friend of people who are dedicated to saying
y amigo de gente que se dedica a decir
gora eh You already know this because oh what
gora eh Ya sabéis está porque ay qué
bad is who wants to join the
malo que es quién se quiere unir a la
cause a Let's go to the cause for
causa una Vámonos a la causa para
defend this feminist Ally who
defender a este Aliado de feminista que
It's super sexist, let's unite. That's the one.
es súper machista unámonos Ese es el
level that has lowered your mark of course
nivel que ha rebajado tu marca claro
to go viral like a viral
para viralizar como es un viral
Oh, how disgusting it is to not know if
Uy qué asco vomitivo y no saber si
also other brands like this garbage
también otras marcas como esta basura
Here they say always virgin always has
aquí que dicen siempre virgen siempre ha
been more than concentration camps
sido más de campos de concentración que
of freedom of expression and have the
de libertad de expresión y tienen los
eggs to talk about fields of
huevos de hablar de campos de
concentration a brand garbage
concentración una basura de marca
stinky which is literally a brand
hedionda que literalmente es una marca
that literally causes cancer
que da cáncer de forma literal
muking paper official account
cuenta oficial de muking paper
no no no it is not the official account of the
no no no es la cuenta oficial de la
brand uncle
marca tío
very Thank you Green very strong
muy Gracias Green muy fuerte
Check it because it's not normal Marjorie anymore
revisa porque no es normal Marjorie ya
we live it with
lo vivimos con
[Music]
[Música]
KFC was that brand that he also carried
KFC era la marca esa que llevaba también
a jerk who was a fan device It's that
un que era fan device Es que
This can't be this is how it is now
esto no puede ser que esto es así Ahora
They are dedicated to selling cancer, I don't remember
se dedican a vender cáncer no recuerdo
When was the last time Billín
cuando fue la última vez que billín
put smoke inside your lungs But
metió humo dentro de tus pulmones Pero
They do it literally like this
ellos lo hacen de forma literal así
we have to talk about fields of
tenemos que hablar de campos de
concentration we can know that you
concentración podemos saber que vosotros
you are closer to gassing people with
estéis más cerca gaseando a la gente con
your cancer and you go through its garbage
vuestro cáncer y te pasas por su basura
from Instagram and you see that it is not only
de Instagram y ves que además ya no solo
is that they dedicate themselves to promoting the
es que se dediquen a promocionar el
tobacco but actively promotes
tabaco sino que promociona activamente
Mary and they put images of her as is
la María y ponen tal cual imágenes de
María's stuffed drunks, cakes of
borracos forracos de María pasteles de
Maria images of buds of all kinds
María imágenes de cogollos de todo tipo
more for racos you need Maria using the
más por racos necesitas María usando la
Minions brand that surely this
marca de los Minions que seguro que esto
You do not have a license to access this
no tiene licencia para acceder esta
disgusting garbage I hope they report them
asquerosa basura Ojalá les denuncien los
has the brand Maria's Minions or
tiene la marca los Minions de María o
ideally also create psychosis
sea idealmente además crean psicosis
because marijuana is much worse than
porque la marihuana es mucho peor que el
normal tobacco because it has all the
tabaco normal porque tiene todas las
consequences of normal tobacco added to
consecuencias del tabaco normal sumado a
I'm not really understanding anything.
no estoy entendiendo nada de verdad te
I say it eh
lo digo eh
I say it
lo digo
in
en
cucumbé that there are no laws are not the
cucumbé que no hay leyes no son la
psychosis
psicosis
natural also Mercury let's see what
natural también El mercurio a ver qué
What happens if you drink a glass of mercury?
pasa si te tomas un vasito de mercurio
really ridiculous scum but there yes
de verdad gentuza ridícula pero ahí sí
Of course people supporting this
claro la gente apoyando esto
very good that one had never had never had
muy buena esa nunca había nunca había
seen that comparison
visto esa comparación
Hey, that's a very good comparison.
oye muy buena esa comparación
As a brand, we support you a lot. Oh yes.
como marca Te apoyamos muchísimo Ay sí
we are going to support a piece of misogynist
vamos a apoyar a un pedazo de misógino
That it is said insults all women
que se diga insulta a todas las mujeres
support abusers to more criminals and
apoyar abusadores a más delincuentes y a
wishing women to die
desear que se queden sin vida mujeres
because they are not within their spectrum
porque no están dentro de su espectro
politician a guy who tries to compare himself
político un tipo que intenta compararse
with Auron and who has been wanting me for years
con auron y que lleva años deseándome
That I am no longer alive is wonderful, eh?
que yo ya no esté vivo maravilloso eh En
what social class of land we are
qué clase social de tierra estamos
I honestly don't finish getting into it
metidos yo honestamente no termino de
Understanding it is something that explodes my mind
comprenderlo es algo que me explota la
head does not finish understanding what it is like
cabeza no termina de entender cómo es
Beijing may bring a lot of
posible que Beijing lleve un montón de
years asking for forgiveness about this
años pidiendo perdón acerca de esta
garbage that I repeat again
basura que de nuevo vuelvo a repetir
change and stopped doing that long before
cambio y dejó de hacer eso mucho antes
long before being famous long before
mucho antes de ser famosa mucho antes
for the first time that I don't know how many
por primera vez que ya no sé cuántas
times has asked for forgiveness
veces ha pedido Perdón
what a piece of [ __ ]
qué gentosa de
what is [ __ ] then, let's see maybe you
que es entonces de a ver igual te
say
digo
for me for me
para mí para mí
It is not for an expulsion, it is worth it
no es para una expulsión vale lo del
[ __ ] trucks is to be hit
camiones es para que le peguen un
touch and prohibit him from doing it again or
toque y lo prohíban de hacérselo más o
a van but for 24 hours it's fine I imagine
un van pero de 24 horas vale me imagino
But what a bunch of people always hang around, man.
pero que gentuza tío siempre se juntan
all the entosa always get together
todos los entosa siempre se juntan lo
same there is no more
mismo no hay más
They sent me some things to see
me mandaron algunas cosillas para ver
go
voy
I'm going to see it here with you to see
a Voy a verlo aquí con ustedes a ver
about Susana your Susana
sobre Susana su Susana
Beijing has it, it has it sentenced
la tiene se la tiene sentenciada Beijing
She has been sentenced, I don't know why it is
se la tiene sentencia no sé el porqué es
I honestly don't know why
que sinceramente no sé el Por qué
We were here looking at the issue
nosotros estuvimos aquí viendo el tema
of Susana when she joined the
de Susana cuando se sumó ella a la
cancellation and the mob against it
cancelación y a la turba de en contra de
auron and Beijing Dani Thank you very much and
auron y Beijing Dani Muchas gracias y
It turns out there were clips of Sugus
resulta ser que había clips de sugus
Susana before they founded Auron and
Susana antes de que fundaran a auron y
everyone would unite against
todo el mundo se uniera en contra de
Beijing and others that were super mudflat
Beijing y demás que era súper fangale de
Beijing greeted Beijing in a
Beijing la saludaba a Beijing en un en
a Minecraft stream and she was
un directo de Minecraft y ella se ponía
as nervous as if her idol had
como nerviosa como que su ídolo le había
I had greeted her in person okay And
la había saludado en persona vale Y
now suddenly it has become like
ahora de repente se ha vuelto como como
very against and apparently in this
muy en contra y por lo visto en esta
Well, it couldn't be less, but in
pues pues no podía ser menos pero en
This area has also participated
esta zona Pues también ha participado
apparently it is worth it or at least it is also worth it
por lo visto vale o por lo menos también
has positioned itself No
se ha posicionado No
I have a plan to see him this afternoon
yo tengo un plan para verlo esta tarde
the truth
la verdad
That is, how do you do it there?
o sea vosotros ahí cómo se hace lo de
put up signs where you can write
poner carteles donde se pueda escribir
Can you help me do that?
me podéis ayudar a hacer eso
Okay, so this afternoon I have a mission.
Vale pues esta tarde tengo una misión
posters
carteles
says Surix, a normal but normal man.
dice surix hombre normal pero normal por
that
qué
but normal why
pero normal por qué
who has done it I would like to know what he did
que la ha hecho me gustaría saber qué le
has Beijing done to her
ha hecho Beijing a ella
so that it suddenly goes from one extreme
para que de repente pase de un extremo
to the other
al otro
if someone likes the image
si alguien linda la imagen
I don't know why but nothing came down for me, let's see
no sé por qué pero me bajó nada a ver
FIFO posters indeed
carteles fifo efectivamente
Indeed no no no I'm not going to put
efectivamente no no no no voy a poner
nothing nor disrespect nor is it done to you
nada ni falta de respeto ni se te hace
Nobody but I want to make posters
nadie pero quiero hacer carteles
near certain bases where it says free
cerca de ciertas bases donde ponga free
[ __ ] they come big
follaca vienen grandes
near certain bases That is to say that
cerca de ciertas bases O sea que se
wants to bring the Beijing home closer to
quiere acercar a la casa de Beijing a
put up posters on posters of the game
poner carteles a carteles del juego de
flush
ras
posters in the ras vale vale game
carteles en el juego de ras vale vale
Okay
vale
let go of anyone in fact
soltar a nadie de hecho
that they didn't invite her to a series there
que no la invitaron a una serie de ahí
Sugus's anger suddenly passed.
el enojo de sugus o sea de repente paso
of loving her so much and getting excited
de quererla tanto y de emocionarse
when I greeted her
cuando la saludaba
to always turn against her because
a ponerse siempre en contra de ella por
a series that series
una serie que serie
real really the responsibility of what
real realmente la responsabilidad de lo
what has happened falls on the people who have
que ha pasado recae las personas que han
I don't think I made this decision.
tomado esta decisión no yo creo
nor are these two posters completely one
ni estas dos carteles uno totalmente
that is going to bother
que va a molestar
But well, if they throw me out, well, look.
Pero bueno que si me echan Pues mira
[Music]
[Música]
Well, this in itself doesn't seem bad to me.
Bueno a mí esto en sí no me parece mal
Here you go two more clicks
te va Aquí dos clics más
I have two climates here that we are going to see
tengo aquí dos climas que vamos a ver a
To me this in itself does not seem bad to me.
mí esto en Sí pues no me parece mal a
see that you who want to be taken away
ver que tú que tú quieras que le quiten
the ban
el baneo
To the truck [ __ ], I think you're good.
al camiones me parece bueno estás
in your right no, that is, it is freedom of
en tu derecho no o sea es libertad de
expression at the end
expresión al final
I mean, I have, I have a plan for
o sea yo tengo yo tengo un plan para
see him this afternoon, really
verlo esta tarde la verdad
a parabellum plan This is the same clip
un plan parabellum Este es el mismo clip
a parabellum plan
un plan parabellum
Let's see. This is another click.
a ver Este es otro clic
what was happening in a chat
lo que pasaba en un chat de
responsibility
responsabilidad
to one of the parties when this type of
a una de las partes cuando este tipo de
comments have occurred on more streams
comentarios han ocurrido en más streams
when they have crossed paths with this person and
cuando se han cruzado con esta persona y
especially when it is happening
sobre todo cuando está ocurrido
for example, let's see if it's true, right?
por ejemplo a ver sí que es verdad no
I can lie, okay? Yes, it is true that
puedo mentir vale Sí que es verdad que
Here I am in total disagreement with that
Aquí estoy en total desacuerdo con que
the responsibility of your chat knows that
la responsabilidad de tu chat sabe que
you are responsible for all things
tú seas responsable de todas las cosas
What people say in your chat is worth it
que diga la gente en tu chat vale
Another very different thing is that the boy
otra cosa muy diferente Es que el chico
He deserved a touch because he doesn't hit him
se merecía un toque porque él no le pega
a tap on the chat when you are viewing the
un toque al chat cuando está viendo las
Disrespect is fine, but I'm not
faltas de respeto vale pero yo no soy
responsible for 3,000 people who are
responsable de 3.000 personas que están
here of what they put
aquí de lo que pongan
I'm not responsible, okay? And yes, it is.
yo no soy responsable vale Y sí que es
It is also true that in almost all cases
verdad también que en casi todos los
live and with almost all streamers
directos y con casi todos los streamers
Things happen that the chat starts to
pasan cosas que el chat empieza a
mention for example when Juan passes by
mencionar por ejemplo cuando pasa Juan
I guard the people of the X streamer chat
guarnizo la gente del chat de X streamer
start saying exploiters exploiter
empieza a decir explotadores explotador
the exploiter getting into that always
el explotador metiéndose a Eso siempre
happens
pasa
I'll tell you one thing to give it a try
ya te digo una cosa que pegarle un toque
someone and another thing is to punish him for
a alguien y otra cosa es castigarle por
what the chat has said that he is
lo que ha dicho el chat que él sí que es
It is true that for me it is permissive
verdad que es para mí para mí permisivo
With what the chat says, for me he [ __ ]
con lo que dice el chat para mí el
trucks no
camiones no
Yes, it is true that you read some
sí que es verdad que leas algún
comment to the chat but it doesn't reach it
comentario al chat pero no lo llega a
incite because the chat already is
incitar porque el chat ya lo está
saying before he follows the
diciendo antes de que él le siga el
I play chat for permissiveness
juego al chat para mí es permisiva la
word
palabra
kind of jokes and it also goes against
tipo de bromas y aparte va en contra de
the new ones because you have to play with
las nuevas porque tiene que jugar con
exact emotes
emotes exacto
I don't know about this kind of jokes on this topic.
este tipo de bromas de este tema no sé
If you remember a very famous clip that
si os acordáis de un clip muy famoso que
He became Juan and I in the game of
se hizo de y yo Juan en el juego del
squid 2 where yo Juan makes a joke and
calamar 2 donde yo Juan hace una broma y
a reference in front
una referencia delante
[Music]
[Música]
then it seems to me to be so double-barreled
entonces me parece tan de doble vara de
measure and so hypocritical so hypocritical
medir y tan hipócrita tan hipócrita
I think so, let's go, I think so, let's go
me parece vamos me parece vamos
does not have
no tiene
That's exactly what I'm telling you
es justo lo que os estoy diciendo
sincerely
sinceramente
and I Juan made the same joke
y yo Juan hizo la misma broma
If you allow it, you are an accomplice, they will analyze it.
Si tú permites eres cómplice ya analizan
but it is not the same as you inciting them to
pero no es lo mismo que tú incites a que
you say it or you allow it is not
tú lo digas o a que tú lo permitas no es
the same It is not the same It is not the same
lo mismo No es la misma no es el mismo
degree of responsibility But well that
grado de responsabilidad Pero bueno que
I'm not telling you that it doesn't stop but for a
no te digo que no para pero para un
I don't see a ban tap on it, let's see.
toque para un baneo no lo veo yo a ver
Another thing is that he had insulted her
otra cosa es que la hubiera insultado él
and I would have said things
y lo hubiera dicho cosas
more out inside insults Imagine
más fuera dentro de insultos Imagínate
who calls her a [ __ ], a [ __ ] pig, or
que le dice hija de Cerda cabrona o
Something like that is a ban there.
alguna cosa así ahí sí está un baneo
Okay, but he's playing along with the joke.
vale pero que esté siguiendo la broma
From the chat, let's see, I don't want to go
del chat A ver es que yo no vamos quiero
at least think that people are not
pensar por lo menos que la gente no es
such an idiot that I'm telling him
tan de que le esté diciendo
nasi Really
nasi De verdad
I mean, I want to think that within the
o sea yo quiero pensar que dentro del
Lore and I tell you about the joke about health
Lore y de la salud te digo de la broma
because he knows that she gets angry and so on
porque sabe que ella se pica y demás
because we are going to think that they have already been born
porque vamos a pensar que ya han nacido
you really are an idiot
de verdad que eres
But Javi later did it again.
Pero Javi ya después lo volvieron a
invite my son and the boy acted like
invitar hijo mío y el chico se hizo el
Worthy and did not want to return now because they are
Digno y no quiso volver ya ya porque son
very worthy all not only is it permissive
muy dignos todos no solo es permisivo la
life
vida
Yes, but then why? Oh, me, Juan.
sí Pero entonces por qué Ay yo Juan
Nobody said he should be banned in Los Angeles.
nadie dijo que deberían banearlo en Los
Squid Games because I Juan
juegos del calamar porque yo Juan
That is, because they Juan can be the
o sea porque ellos Juan pueda ser la
Same joke all over Beijing's face
misma broma en toda la cara de Beijing
If we have the same I know they are not the
si tenemos la misma sé que no son los
same administrators But well, it is known
mismos administradores Pero bueno se
They could have complained no good with more
Podrían haber quejado no bueno con más
reason still because one of the heads of the
razón aún porque uno de los jefes del
Auron's Squid Game
juego del calamar de auron que auron
because no one asked for the expulsion they are the
porque nadie pidió la expulsión son los
same creators of the game
mismos creadores los del juego de
squid and those from Beyún are no no no no
calamar y los de beyún no no no no son
the same but nobody asked for any creator
lo mismo pero nadie pidió ningún creador
He complained that Juan and I did that
se quejó de que y yo Juan hiciera esa
joke has gone too far, it's worth banning him, right?
broma se ha pasado es para banearlo no
Well, it's a joke, you might like it more.
bueno Es una broma te puede gustar más
You may like her less for sure.
te puede gustar menos a ella seguro que
It made them feel bad, okay?
les sentó mal vale
the two parties involved
las dos partes implicadas
I ask
yo pregunto
because only one of the parties is kicked out
porque solo se echa a una de las partes
involved that he intends to have thrown out
implicadas que pretende que echen a
Beijing
Beijing
kick Beijing out
que echen a Beijing
for the comments you have made
por los comentarios que hayas hecho el
another does not make sense what just
otro no tiene sentido lo que acaba de
say there So they should kick Beijing out for
decir ahí O sea que echen a Beijing por
the comments that the other has made
los comentarios que ha hecho lo otro
Oh, but then they do the same thing.
Ay pero luego ellos hacen lo mismo a
other creators for less but I know that
otros creadores por menos pero sé que
Look, I know that the owners of the game
mira sé que que los dueños del juego del
squid are not the same as those of
calamar no son lo mismo que los de
bellum vale the clash was going on
bellum vale el choque se estaba
presenting the chocas was presenting
presentando el chocas estaba presentando
with Jordi Wilde that event
el con el Jordi Wilde el evento ese de
boxing that Jordi Wiley did, right?
boxeo que hizo Jordi wiley verdad el
Chocas was laughing at the humor of
chocas estaba riéndose del humor de
David Suárez, I can really visualize that.
David Suárez verdad puedo visualizar ese
get involved with Beijing in that monologue
mete con Beijing en ese monólogo
He called Beijing a Nazi in that monologue and
le dijo nazi a Beijing en ese monólogo y
the chocas was there laughing
el chocas estaba allí riéndose
the collide was not outraged and stood up and
el chocan no se indignó y se levantó y
he went away
se fue
For me there is something that if they go beyond the
para mí hay cosa que si traspasan los
limits but being told something Nazi is
límites pero que te digan algo de nazi a
See, I understand that maybe she
ver yo entiendo que a lo mejor ella le
bothered because it is believed that it is taken that
moleste porque se cree que se toma que
There are people who are telling you that is
hay gente que se lo está diciendo es
do Well in fact there are people who do it
hacer Bueno de hecho hay gente que se lo
is he saying seriously yes but because
está diciendo en serio sí pero Porque
those stupid people
esa gente
there is no more
no hay más
let's see this other one
a ver este otro
because
porque
I have a grudge against him because a few
yo me tiene tirria porque hace unos
months when this whole area came out I
meses cuando salió toda esta zona yo
I gave my opinion on the subject and he didn't like my opinion.
opiné sobre el tema y no le gustó mi
opinion and asked for a follow on all the
opinión y pedí un follow en todos los
sides and when I react my
lados y cuando me cuando reacciona mi
death The Squid Games you know that
muerte Los juegos del calamar sabéis esa
expression he has when he killed
expresión que tiene cuando mató a
[ __ ] then the same no then you already
follaca pues la misma no entonces ya te
I say that maybe this afternoon the same thing will happen to me
digo yo que igual esta tarde igual en mi
last afternoon again but oh well
última tarde otra vez pero bueno
[Music]
[Música]
I think Beijing will correct me if I
yo creo que Beijing corregirme si me
mistake he didn't even make it when he made the
equivoco no la metió ni cuando hizo la
answer do you remember when Beijing
respuesta os acordáis cuando Beijing
He did the live talk that he dedicated to her
hizo el directo hablando que le dedicó
for a while also to wismichu and that thing
un rato también a wismichu Y esa cosa
Well, I think that, well, I think that
pues creo que pues creo que
Ah but Javier Oliveira Well me in this one
Ah pero Javier oliveira Bueno yo en esta
I haven't asked to enter the series but I
serie no he pedido entrar pero a lo
better the choco He wouldn't invite me no good
mejor el choca No me invitaría no bueno
He might have invited me to this one.
el choca sí puede que me invitase a esta
series if I had asked him eh he
serie si se lo hubiera pedido eh el
Chocas has brought in people who are throwing him away
chocas ha metido a gente que le tira la
[ __ ] on him eh
a él eh
I think you crash Maybe if I
Yo creo que el chocas A lo mejor Si me
I would have put it in, eh?
hubiera metido eh
I don't know, maybe. Well, maybe.
No lo sé a lo mejor Bueno a lo mejor a
I hate myself more, I don't know, I don't know
mí me odia más no no sé no sé
Javi, did you see that Beijing called her a stalker?
Javi viste que Beijing llamaba acosadora
whitmichu Yes of course
whitmichu Sí claro
It's on the main channel I saw it on the
está en el canal principal lo vi en el
I saw the main channel
canal principal lo vi
Well, anyway, I would love to know what it is.
bueno en fin me encantaría saber qué es
what Villegas has done to this girl
lo que le ha hecho Villegas a esta chica
that is, what is the moment in which something
o sea cuál es el momento en el que algo
breaks from this inside this girl and
se rompe de esta dentro de esta chica y
decides to go against Beijing
decide ir en contra de Beijing
When is the time when this is
Cuándo es el momento en el que esta
girl breaks something inside her and
chica se rompe algo dentro de ella y
decides to go against Beijing
decide ir en contra de Beijing
It is South but we have seen it many times already
está Sur pero a ver ya muchas veces a
Uncle Churre will never have respect for you
tío churre nunca lo van a tener respeto
the creators are worth it
los creadores vale
They know very well that Uncle Shure already
Ellos saben de sobra que el tío Shure ya
The Choco knows very well since the guy
el choca sabe de sobra ya que el tío
Shure will never tell any news
Shure nunca va a decir ninguna noticia
that it harms him is fine or so now
que le perjudique a él vale o sea ahora
same you crash explodes okay look so much
mismo el chocas explota vale mira tanto
What do they call me, the Dallas dog?
que me dicen a mí el perro de Dallas
Okay, the other day Dallas exploded and
vale el otro día Dallas explotó y
threatened a boy, that clown, not from
amenazó a un chico al payaso ese no del
courage not
ánimo no
[Music]
[Música]
Well, for example, I gave the news about that
pues por ejemplo yo di la noticia de eso
Well
bueno
give a live reaction that there is later
di reacción en directo que luego hay por
there on Twitter videos manipulating my
ahí en Twitter vídeos manipulando mi
reaction as if it were another and also said
reacción como si fuera otra y también di
the news on the main channel
la noticia en el canal principal de
I even put it in the title.
hecho lo puse hasta de título no
Uncle South No, I wouldn't give that news anymore.
el tío Sur No ya esa noticia no la daría
And if he gives it and they collide, he asks her to
Y si la da y el chocan le pide que la
erase the collide erase it or rather the Chulo
borra el chocan lo borra o sea el Chulo
erase me understand then that doesn't have
borra me entiende Entonces eso no tiene
respect respect It is that they respect you that
respeto respeto Es que te respeten que
respect does not have to mean either
tampoco respeto tiene que significar
fear that the creators are afraid of you
miedo que los creadores te tengan miedo
so that you don't criticize him or so that you don't
para que no le critiques o para que no
I know what it's worth
sé qué vale
which was when she was not invited to
que fue cuando no la invitaron a
tortilla 2 That was the moment that didn't
tortilla 2 Ese fue el momento que no le
they invited me to tortilla 2
invitaron a tortilla 2
Let's see, I'm going to ask something to see if
a ver voy a preguntar una cosa a ver si
they answer me
me contestan
at this time
a esta hora
Well then I'm going to go to I'm going to go to
Bueno pues me voy a ir a me voy a ir a
record newscast for Javier Oliveira me
grabar noticiero para Javier oliveira me
says Karime Sugus She got upset because she didn't
dice Karime sugus Se molestó porque no
They invited her to tortilla 2 After that
la invitaron a tortilla 2 Después de que
She was harassing 8 in tortilla one
ella estuvo acosando a 8 en tortilla uno
harassing 8
acosando a 8
Let's see, 8 let himself be loved, not a little, no.
a ver 8 se dejaba querer no un poco no
false moralists who join funas
falsos moralistas que se unen a funas
for vendettas or because it pays but not
por vendetas o porque les renta pero no
we talk about coscu
se habla de coscu
It's true, newscast, it's true, eh, you
es verdad ya noticiero es verdad eh tú
It's true
es verdad
No
no
[Music]
[Música]
all this is being discussed
se está debatiendo sobre toda esta
move of but I have made you but I have not
movida de pero te he hecho pero no te he
fact they throw him out or they don't throw him out But in
hecho lo echan o no lo echan Pero en
the topic is never brought up for debate
ningún momento se saca a debatir el tema
coconut
coco
There are no eggs there, I haven't seen any
ahí no hay huevos no he visto a ninguno
one of those who bring up the subject, uncle.
de estos que saque el tema coscu tío
There is not one of these that takes out
no hay ni uno ni uno de estos que saque
the uncle coscu topic
el tema coscu tío
be a chocas
sea un un chocas
a clash that became super moralistic with
un choca que se puso súper moralista con
This is not from Beijing and then there was
esto no de Beijing y después había
trucks and others don't want to crash into you
camiones y demás no a ver choca da tu
opinion What do you think about coscu being
opinión Qué te parece que el coscu sea
the star of the evening
el protagonista de la velada
none none none of these none
ninguno ninguno ninguno de estos ninguno
of these from the group of the series
de estos del grupo de los de las series
and no one else gives a damn about yours
y demás ninguno ni mu da vuestra
opinion Hey for better or for worse for
opinión Oye para bien o para mal para
good or bad, what happens is yes
bien o para mal que lo que pasa que sí
that if your opinion is going to be what you think
que si tu opinión va a ser que te parece
well that you are for the best you
bien que estáis por lo mejor te
you risk a funa, not a funita, no
arriesgas a una funa no a una funita no
When is the evening? Well, the evening
Cuándo es la velada Pues a la velada le
There's one week left, or two exactly.
falta una semana o bueno dos justamente
now two
ahora dos
just just two are missing now
justitos justitos le faltan ahora dos
days is Saturday
días es el sábado
the day after tomorrow, Saturday, not the next one
pasado mañana sábado no el siguiente
Saturday neither the other
sábado tampoco el otro
two weeks right now two weeks
dos semanas justo ahora dos semanas
right now my air speaks of the controversy
justo ahora mi aire habla de la polémica
with the truck [ __ ]
con el follacamiones
we were encouraged to see it
nos animamos a verlo
we dare to we dare to see it
nos animamos a nos animamos a verlo
what do you think your position will be?
cuál cree que será su postura
For example, I do what you do.
yo por ejemplo a mí lo que vosotros
You say it in the chat, I don't give a damn, I don't care
digáis en el chat me la suda a mí no me
They can be expelled from any other series
Pueden expulsar de ninguna otra serie
Okay
vale
I also tell you this is something that I
también te digo esto es algo que yo le
He would say that you personally do not want me to
diría él personalmente quieres que no te
expel in a series do not enter
expulsen en una serie no entres en
series in which expulsions make
series en la que las expulsiones hacen
a slightly random form
una forma un poquito pues como aleatoria
but also the position is going to be valid
sino también vale la postura va a ser
Sure. Wait, it's Ana. Thank you very much.
claro Espérate que es Ana Muchas gracias
Ana, a kiss Carlos, the position is going to be
Ana un beso Carlos la postura va a ser
against Beijing the position or that is the
en contra de Beijing la postura o sea la
posture is going to be the posture is going to be that
postura va a ser la postura va a ser que
that they have thrown him at us
que alfonía nos lo han echado
unfairly because it is Beijing that does it
injustamente porque es Beijing la que lo
I hope that's not it, Maria, when
pide Espero que no sea eso María cuando
You don't see what you and your boyfriend gave him
tú no veas la que le diste tú y tu novio
novel that you gave to the team of
novela que le disteis al equipo de
London Hey, so they wouldn't throw me out.
London Ey para que me echaran a mí no
see the one you gave him
vea la que le diste
sending him a screenshot of what we're going to say
mandándole captura hasta de la vamos que
Jackie who sent him told me about it
me lo contó el Jackie que le mandó
capture even of the aini that if I that
captura hasta de la aini que si yo que
If Ainny was a fan of mine, well, tremendous.
si la ainny era fan mía bueno tremendo
Jackie told me about it
me lo contó el Jackie
I mean, I hope you're not going to complain about
o sea Espero que no te vayas a quejar de
that a boy has been kicked out of a series
que hayan echado a un chico de una serie
because Virgin asked for it because
porque lo haya pedido Virgin porque
Billín has a lot of power
billín tiene mucho poder
because you didn't stop until I
porque tú no paraste hasta que me
They kicked out of London
echaron de London
can't fill you with [ __ ] Okay
no te puede llenar de Bueno
technically
técnicamente
I'm sure they can do it.
estoy segura de que pueden hacerlo estoy
sure that if they try they will be able to
segura de que si lo intentan podrán
doing it happens is that I am like a
hacerlo pasa es que yo soy como una
cockroach had tried to kill me many times
cucaracha había intentado matarme muchas
sometimes but no no
veces pero no no
I'm like a cockroach, okay, try
yo soy como una cucaracha vale intenta
kill many times but not
matar muchas veces pero no
Bautista Thank you very much
Bautista Muchísimas gracias
It's just that this thing about the
es que me llama la atención esto de la
cockroach because she sued me
cucaracha porque ella en una demanda me
has said that I call her
ha puesto que yo la llamo a ella
cockroach
cucaracha
This is great because she is in a
esto buenísimo porque ella en una
has filed a lawsuit against me that I have
demanda me ha puesto que yo la he
called cockroach and I never called her
llamado cucaracha y nunca la llamé
cockroach
cucaracha
okay what I said was in a video that I
vale lo que dije fue en un vídeo que me
They had it up to their balls, her mother and
tenían hasta los ella la madre y
all your allies to tell me that I
todos sus aliados de decirme que yo me
I wanted to throw it away and I don't know, I don't know how much and
la quería tirar y no sé no sé cuánto y
in a video up to the [ __ ] for
en un vídeo hasta la para
defend myself I said I would throw myself into a
defenderme dije me tiraría antes a una
cockroach
cucaracha
That's not calling you a cockroach and now you
eso no es llamarte cucaracha y ahora tú
Here in a live broadcast you say I am like a
aquí en un directo dices yo soy como una
cockroach
cucaracha
tried to kill me many times but failed
intentado matarme muchas veces pero no
No
no
tremendously controversial but clear as
tremendamente polémicos pero claro como
They don't mess with the Big Ones or
no se meten con Los Grandes ni
consequences are the hands and the victim
consecuencias son las manos y la víctima
It's big too, I'll tell you one thing, eh?
es grande también te digo una cosa eh o
In general, I see all this from
sea en general yo todo esto lo veo desde
far away and with a lot of cynicism because
lejos y desde muchísimo cinismo porque
I find it very heavy that all the [ __ ]
me parece muy heavy que todos los
years there is a series a role-playing server
años haya una serie un servidor de rol
something like this all these years there has been
alguna cosa así todos estos años haya
a similar move with a creator of
una movida similar con un creador de
different content and all the [ __ ]
contenido diferente y todos los
years people are surprised by conclusions
años la gente se sorprenda conclusiones
that people are coming Now they are
que está llegando la gente Ahora son
conclusions that I don't know were there
conclusiones que no sé que estaban
carved into stone in the age of
picadas en piedra en la edad de
Jesus Christ seems new to me the roll of
Jesucristo me parece nuevo el rollo de
if you bother a content creator
si molestas a un creador de contenido
small Nothing happens
pequeño No pasa nada
But how can you have such a hard face?
pero cómo puedes tener la cara tan dura
But aunt, I didn't tell you anything in London
pero tía que no te dije nada en London
that I completely sweated the la
que me sudó completamente la la
[Music]
[Música]
As the word "[ __ ]" is, I'll tell you that
como es la palabra te lo diré que
I sweated completely
me sudó completamente
the presence of you and Wismichu in the
la presencia tuya y la de wismichu en la
series that if I cross paths with you I'll leave
serie que si me cruzo con ustedes me voy
two streets away that London was very big and
a dos calles que London era muy grande y
You, like me, had much more prominence
tú como yo tenía mucho más protagonismo
that you do not stop this attack Me
que ustedes no para este ataque Me
They kicked me out because you want me to be left without
echaron porque quieres que me quede sin
jobs and you want to close doors on me
trabajos y quieres cerrarme puertas de
everywhere because I withdrew support from you
todas partes porque te retiré el apoyo
of your lies
de tus mentiras
I mean, but how can you take it and you can
o sea pero cómo puedes y puedes
say that they fire people when
decir que echan a la gente a dedo cuando
a great creator asks for it
lo pide una creadora grande
when you with 100 spectators or less
cuando tú con 100 espectadores o menos
You kicked me out of London and I deny it.
me echaste de London y que lo niegue El
Yaqui and after he told me and I have
yaqui y después que me lo dijo y tengo
the conversation with him
la conversación con él
But how are you going to take it? But how are you going to take it?
Pero cómo vas a Pero cómo vas a
take it and you're going to say that if I
y vas a decir que eso Si es que yo
I didn't tell him anything in London or anything.
no le dije ni muy en London ni mu digo
Well, it has already caught me at a time when
Bueno ya me ha cogido en una época en la
that we weren't talking about her or
que ni estábamos hablando de ella ni
nothing because there was no news from her
nada porque no había noticias de ella
But how are you going to take it and complain?
pero cómo vas a y te vas a quejar
that Beijing that she
de que de que Beijing que ella
has simply reported what has been reported to him
simplemente ha reportado lo que le han
done and you did not report what what
hecho y tú no reportaste lo que lo que
what I did to you because I didn't do it to you
lo que yo te hice porque yo no te hice
nothing
nada
I mean, I didn't do anything to you in London. Ah
o sea yo no te hice nada en London Ah
but he has made videos of me outside of
pero es que me ha hecho vídeos fuera de
London
London
ah
ah
Hey, I don't respect you guys where I'm at.
Oye no respeto ustedes en el que estoy
reading some comment that I don't like
leyendo algún comentario que no me gusta
Hey, don't be disrespectful in the chat.
eh No faltéis al respeto en el chat
you
ustedes
It's not necessary, but man, let's see.
no hace falta pero hombre a ver
start complaining is not that
ponerte ponerte a quejarte no es que
Virgin is big so they pay attention to it.
Virgin como es grande pues le hacen caso
But if you kicked me out of the
pero si es que tú me echaste a mí del
deep simply by my presence
hondo simplemente por mi presencia
simply by my presence
simplemente por mi presencia
So it literally happens the sun rises
Así que pasa literalmente el sol sale
every day the nun water instead of
todos los días el agua monja en vez que
Every year a different one bothers him, it's like
cada año le jode alguno distinto es como
people who do not consider anything
la gente que no considera que nada lo
what they have done to you is bad but
que te han hecho a ti sea malo pero
when they do it to someone who is someone
cuando se lo hacen a alguien que alguien
they go crazy but of course but
se vuelven locos sino Claro pero
Listen to this when you see these beards
escúchame esto cuando veas estas barbas
cut from your neighbor Put yours to
de tu vecino cortar Pon las tuyas a
soak Yes yes it is basically that or rather
remojar Sí sí es básicamente eso o sea
but in the end it is also that we return to
pero al final también es que volvemos a
the same thing is that this is the internet this
lo mismo es que esto es internet este
I'm not saying it's a matter of respect.
caso no digo que sea cosa de respeta
trucks, to me, is a kid I like
camiones a mí es un chaval que me cae
pretty good, I think he's nice
bastante bien me parece simpático creo
that when he has had to speak
que cuando ha tenido que hablar
Raquel, a kiss, I didn't expect to be disappointed.
Raquel un beso no esperaba decepcionarme
I didn't expect to be disappointed
no esperaba decepcionarme
out of respect, eh, I mean, I'm going to trucks
desde el respeto eh o sea voy a camiones
from respect Ah Well very well Well
desde el respeto Ah Pues muy bien Pues
Very well, if you agree, I respect it.
muy bien pues si te parece respeto lo
from the [ __ ] truck and I don't know how you are
del camión y no sé cómo andas
demanding nonsense
demandando chorradas
that content that they don't seem to learn
ese contenido que parece que no aprenden
the lesson because I think this boy
la lección porque creo que este chico
Well, he comes from another environment and now he is
pues viene de otro ambiente y ahora está
starting to act like their beaks don't
empezando a hacer como sus piquitos no
to many to many other people Not that
a muchos a muchas otras personas No que
when for example they have done something to me
cuando por ejemplo me han hecho algo a
me, well, a fly passing by and when it is
mí pues una mosca pasando y cuando se lo
have made your favorite content or a
han hecho a Su contenido favorito o a un
your friend who is a content creator or
amigo suyo creador de contenido o a
themselves
ellos mismos
I mean, but I don't believe I am
o sea pero yo no me creo que estoy
saying this eh when more when
diciendo esto eh cuando más cuando
when they did it to me passing by uncle
cuando me lo han hecho a mí pasando tío
and asked to be thrown out he asked to be thrown out
y pidió que me echaran pidió que me
They will throw out but by the face or because
echaran pero by the face o sea porque
I literally didn't come across well no no no
literalmente no me crucé bueno no no no
wait, it's you who is worse. You do respect and
espera peor eres tú Tú sí que respetas y
you correct your chat the F trucks no
corriges a tu chat el F camiones no
always always ran to the chat Let's see no
siempre siempre corrió al chat A ver no
I can control all messages by
puedo controlar todos los mensajes por
There are 2,500 people here and there will be people who
aquí hay 2500 personas y Habrá gente que
post comments to harm
ponga comentarios para perjudicar
our community but listen to me once
nuestra comunidad pero escúchame una
stuff
cosa
even worse
peor aún
wismichu made me meta Gaming
wismichu me hizo meta Gaming
made me meta gaming
me hizo meta Gaming
wismichu caught me at London Ey when I
wismichu cogió en el London Ey cuando me
saw
vio
totally out of character came and hit him
totalmente fuera del rol vino y le pegó
to the doll
al muñeco
and the one they kicked out was me for being there
y al que echaron fue a mí por estar ahí
even the hater channels do it
incluso los canales haters lo
They recognized that Wismichu made me a goal
reconocieron que wismichu me hizo meta
Gaming
Gaming
I didn't remember that, I didn't remember
no me acordaba de eso no me acordaba
literal literal
literal literal
literal and how are you going to have the face of
literal y cómo vas a tener la cara de
my mother
madre mía
This is a matter of points of interest
esto es una cuestión de puntos intereses
as long as it doesn't harm you, you don't
mientras a ti no te perjudique tú no te
you're going to involve And this is the logic no
vas a involucrar Y esta es la lógica no
only from the content channels of the
solo de los canales de contenido de los
influencers but from anyone
influencers sino de cualquier persona
that moves in any environment that
que se mueva en cualquier ambiente que
is closely linked to power, status and
esté muy vinculado al poder al estatus y
to an economic position If you can
a una posición económica Si tú puedes
put that status or power at risk
poner en riesgo ese estatus o ese poder
purchasing power or that share capital by
adquisitivo o ese capital social por
confront someone Even if you believe
enfrentarte a alguien Aunque tú creas
that person is not doing it right
que esa persona no lo está haciendo bien
or even see that you are really companions
o incluso veas que realmente compañeros
yours are starting to fall and are
tuyos están empezando a caer y están
starting to see guillotine blows now
empezando a ver Ya guillotinazos
You didn't even report them on meta Gaming no no
ni los reportaste por meta Gaming no no
I reported it or anything because it seems like a
lo reporté ni nada porque me parece una
It's silly to report someone for that.
tontería reportar a alguien por eso
Well, I would make a joke or whatever.
pues haría la coña o para yo que sepas
being cool with his girlfriend or something like that
el ser Guay con su novia o algo por el
style look how I defend you Not me that
estilo mira cómo te defiendo No yo que
I know something about the thoughts of
sé alguna cosa de los pensamientos de
These people do not
esta gente no
you should have reported it with a ticket
debiste denunciarlo con un ticket te
There was a lack of cunning, but that's not the point.
faltó picaresca pero es que no se trata
I am not going to report any mischief.
de picaresca es que yo no voy a reportar
to a person
a una persona
for that [ __ ]
por esa gilipollez
whether his name is Whitmichu or whoever he is
se llame whitmichu o se llame quien sea
I'm not going to report we're in a
yo no voy a reportar estamos en una
series uncle you have to act with
serie tío hay que actuar con
professionalism Okay and for me to act
profesionalidad Vale y para mí actuar
with professionalism is that they are there
con profesionalidad es que estén allí
people I don't get along with okay And if
gente con la que no me llevo vale Y si
I cross paths with them so I can play my part.
me cruzo con ellos pues hacer mi papel
of my character and say nothing
de mi personaje y no decir nada
You understand me. What I'm not going to do is
me entiende Lo que yo no voy a hacer es
spam like I told you here that he did to
spamear como me contó yo aquí que hizo a
the administrators until he got
los administradores hasta que consiguió
that they threw me out is fine
que me echaran vale
I don't know how to position myself or claim my rights or
no sé posicionarse o reivindicarse o
move away no I mean like it's easier
alejarse no O sea en plan es más fácil
Well, just hope that you don't
pues simplemente esperar que no te
happen to you Strive a thousand times
ocurra a ti Esforzarte de las mil
ways you can think of Although
maneras que se te puede ocurrir Aunque
suppose to humiliate you to enter into circles of
supongan humillarte entrar en ruedas de
manipulations or blackmail whatever
manipulaciones o chantajes lo que sea
so that it doesn't happen to you and
tal para que no te pase a ti y
surprising when it finally happens to you
sorprendente cuando finalmente te pasa
something that was announced to everyone
algo que estaba anunciado a todos los
winds
vientos
has happened to Peña a lot
le ha pasado muchísima Peña
These people will never cease to amaze me.
nunca dejará de sorprenderme esta gente
It will truly never cease to amaze me
de verdad nunca dejará de sorprenderme
These people
esta gente
you didn't open you didn't open ticket F Javi
no abriste no abriste ticket F Javi
you should have opened tickets that no that no that
debiste abrir tickets que no que no que
I don't open and he gave me a ticket for that.
no abro y un tique por eso si me lo dio
a lot of people but I'm not going to open a
mucha gente pero que no voy a abrir un
ticket for that, what are we going to see?
ticket por eso para que vamos a ver
mostly
principalmente
I'm not going to open a ticket mainly.
principalmente no voy a abrir un ticket
so that
para que
my ticket costs him to be thrown out
mi ticket le cueste a él que lo echen de
a series
una serie
with which he is gaining work is with
con la que está ganando trabajo está con
the one who is earning a salary. So
la que está ganando sueldo O sea que
We are literally not going to see a thing that
literalmente no vamos a ver una cosa que
I criticized the gang and another thing is that
yo critique a la peña y otra cosa es que
I wish you lose your job.
yo le deseo que pierdas el trabajo cosa
that they do want me, it's worth it
que ellos sí me desean a mí vale la han
attempted by activity by passive this
intentado por actividad por pasiva esto
it's a thing or this is going you go behind go
es una cosa o sea esto ir tú detrás ir
you behind the companies or well not of
tú detrás de las empresas o bueno no de
the companies in this case of the series
las empresas en este caso de la serie
with which I work, you go behind the
con la que yo trabaje ir tú detrás de la
series with what I worked with the
serie con lo que yo trabajé de los
administrators to kick me out of the
administradores para que me echen del
work is worth it in that case London
trabajo vale en ese caso London
[Music]
[Música]
Okay, and I don't, it's not that I'm not
vale Y yo no lo no es que no estoy
saying I wouldn't do it for posturing
diciendo Yo no lo haría por postureo por
to be on good terms with you no no it's not that no
quedar bien con ustedes no no es que no
I would do it. Not that I didn't do it.
lo haría No es que no lo hice
It's that friend and michu made me meta Gaming
es que amigo y michu me hizo meta Gaming
and I didn't do it, I didn't put a ticket because
y yo no lo hice no puse un ticket porque
I consider that apart from being childish
Considero que que aparte de infantil
apart from being childish and unprofessional
aparte infantil y poco profesional que
I'm not going to take it and I'm going to yes but you
no voy a y voy a sí pero a ti te
They threw and you lost money Well that's it
echaron y perdiste dinero Bueno eso de
I lost money that I lost money I would have to
perdí dinero eso perdí dinero habría que
see it because I probably earn the same
verlo pues seguramente gano lo mismo yo
not if I'm not working from five to
no si no estoy trabajando de cinco a
six in this I'm working on another
seis en esto estoy trabajando en otra
thing And it's probably not worth it or whatever but
cosa Y seguramente no vale o sea pero
that no you can't do that
que que no no puedes hacer eso
I mean, don't ask me to do it because
O sea no me pidáis que lo haga porque
be a person I dislike or not
sea una persona que me caiga mal que no
You can do that because a punch has come
puedas eso porque ha venido un puñetazo
in GTA man
en el GTA hombre
No, it's not about lukewarm, it's about that
no no se trata de tibio se trata de que
I'm not a hothead, so let's see.
no soy un ardido o sea vamos a ver se
It's about the fact that in life there are two options
trata de que en la vida hay dos opciones
Okay, you can live with resentment and that you
vale tú puedes vivir con rencor y que te
consume the resentment, that's worth it, then you'll be fine
consuma el rencor vale eso luego se te
notice my face you notice me on my face and
nota la cara a mí me notáis en la cara y
in my physique that I live with resentment Well no
en mi físico que vivo con rencor Pues no
because because I don't care
porque porque me da igual
you lost twitch momentum on that one
perdiste el impulso de Twitch en ese
moment because most likely I have
momento pues muy probablemente yo he
lost things because these people
perdido cosas porque esta gente se
They will have put it in, yes, probably. But
habrán metido sí probablemente Pero
Well, time puts everything in its place.
bueno el tiempo lo pone todo en su sitio
Time puts everything in its place, don't you?
el tiempo lo pone todo en su sitio no os
worry, each one will have
preocupéis cada uno tendrá
We will see how each one puts time
lo vamos del tiempo cada uno va poniendo
In your sites I know that it is not necessary either
en sus sitios sé que tampoco hace falta
putting yourself like this is okay
ponerse así vale
There's no need to even act like that. Look where
no hace falta ni ponerse así Mira donde
each one is there
están cada uno
It's just that if you think about it, it's ridiculous to do
es que si lo piensas Es ridículo hacer
that
eso
I had 7000 in a viral series you would have
tenía 7000 en una serie viral hubieras
reached 10,000 to 10 or 15,000
llegado a los 10.000 a los 10 o 15.000
on Twitch
en Twitch
I had 7000 in the squid game
tenía 7000 en el juego del calamar los
the squid game we can't know
el juego del calamar no podemos saber
who who did it
quién quién lo hizo
We will never be able to do the squid game thing.
lo del juego del calamar nunca podremos
know who did it
saber quién lo hizo
Okay, people, I'm going to record for Javi.
bueno gente me voy a grabar para Javi
Oliveira, I send you a huge hug.
oliveira os mando un abrazo enorme
We will surely see each other tomorrow after
mañana nos veremos seguramente después
to eat and you are loved very much
de comer y se os quiere mucho se lo
Love a lot is worth a hug people
quiere mucho vale un abrazo gente
[Music]
[Música]